All right. After autumn...
Ask anyone around the area
about accuracy.
Arctic activities
are abundant,
astonishing, astounding and
A‐1 on all accounts.
‐Back up...
‐But before beach bodies,
bros better bundle up
in boots,
blankets, and balaclavas
because a bloody,
bitter breeze
will blow brisk,
blustery and bleak.
‐Careful...
‐Correct and common to cocoon
in a cap, coat and comforter,
because a cutting cold
can consume your character,
occasionally create a corpse
and continually compress
your cock.
‐Don't...
‐Don't you dare dawdle,
dilly‐dally, or dick around
after dark in December,
she's definitely damn drafty
if you're down a duvet.
‐Easily...
‐Each and every earthling's
environmentally enslaved.
‐Fact...
‐It's fucking freezing.
It's friggin' frigid.
You're fit for flu in February
without fleece, flannel,
full‐fledged furnace, or fire.
‐Go on...
‐It's goddamn glacial,
go grab gloves or garb and
gear up for gusts.
‐Hear ya...
‐Hypothermia,
if you don't heat your home
to half hellish it's harsh.
Hibernate in a hoodie,
hot chocolate,
Harry and the Hendersons.
‐Infinitely icy...
‐Inhabit indoors.
Isolated and insulated.
Incubate the igloo.
Illness is an issue.
Influenzas implied.
Infections imminent.
Immunity is impossible.
‐Just joking...
‐Ah, just joshin' jargon.
It ain't jail. Jackets in
January's no jigsaw.
‐Keep calm...
‐Killjoys keep comfy
in their kingdom,
crashing kilos of Kleenex,
keen for cozy kayaking
with their kids
when the key is killing kegs
with your kin.
‐Literally...
‐Losers live life
locked in their layers,
lingering lazy and lifeless,
lost like legit loners,
while the leaders in
larger learning let loose.
(CHUCKLES) Muff.
Earmuffs, mittens and
mucus medicine,
till mighty maniacal
Mother Nature makes
milder, mellower,
and meltier moves.
Motivate your mates, like the
Moose Marc Messier.
Maybe mix a martini
for your maiden,
‐if you've met your match.
‐Nature.
Naturally nippy, but that's
nothin' new up north.
Normal naturistic narrative.
Not national news.
‐Overcast.
‐Overcoats and
‐overshoes, obviously.
‐Polar.
Parkas and pullovers,
particularily.
‐Tried quail?
‐A quantity of quality quilts
is quaint and
quasi‐quintessential
to avoid quivering
and quash quarrelling
if quarantined to
one's quarters. Try quail.
‐Reindeer.
‐Well, not raw rookie.
In a rosemary‐rubbed roast
with radish,
wrapped in rich, rare bacon
after removing
Rudolph's red nose.
‐Sleddin'.
‐So, we're sound.
Sled's a synonym
for snowmobiles.
Snowmobile's a
synonym for sled.
So, a sled is a snowmobile,
a snowmobile is a sled. Super?
‐Terrific.
‐Trust a traditional
turtleneck to maintain a
toasty temperature over time.
‐Ugly.
‐Useful.
‐Vile.
‐Valuable.
‐Whatever.
‐Whiteouts and wind chills,
walk it off, whiners.
Withdraw whimpering and
wake up, wankers.
Wrathful wicked weather.
Wear woolens or
waterproof wardrobe.
Warm your wet
workwear by the woodstove.
Winter is wonderful,
wild and wide.
‐Exactly.
‐Exceptionally.
‐Yup.
‐Yeah.
Zero... Degrees?
Well, sub‐zero.
Aw, zip it.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(HARD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Guess those idiots won't be
bothering us
anymore, nee‐ya‐wa.
‐How are you now?
‐Please don't talk to me
‐like a fuckin' hick.
‐Not so bad.
Are you serious
with that fuckin' turtleneck?
You lose a lot of heat
in the neck.
I'm okay,
if that's what you're askin'.
That's what I'm askin'.
I wasn't ready to have a kid.
Well, that is
your choice to make.
You're goddamn right
it's my choice.
‐Sure, it is.
‐I'm glad I took care of it.
Well, that is your right.
You're goddamn right
it's my right.
I'm not even sure if it was
yours, but thank you.
Thanks for the
smokes and Pepperettes.
I'll see ya when I
see ya, boo...
Over and out.
(COUGHING)
You gots a cold there, Darys?
Hmm, just a cough.
Well, you knows
what they says...
If you don't take care
of a cold,
she'll stay for seven days.
If you take care of it,
she'll be gone in a week.
Yep. We can't promise summers
but we'll guarantees winters.
You fuckin' serious
with that turtleneck?
Yeah, you lose a lot of
heat in the neck.
Jivin' Pete says he pulls a
pikes outta here yesterday.
Heard Jivin's been hanging out
with some degens
from up country.
(DAN GRUMBLES)
He's a decent guy, but
ain't no way he pulled no
pike outta here yesterday.
Says he pulled a pikes,
a perch, a wallseyes and
a trout.
Is that a brook trout?
‐No, it'd be lake trout.
‐Why's that?
'Cause we're on
a fuckin' lake, Dary.
I'm hungry.
There's whitefish
in the cooler.
Well, how the fuck
did that get there?
I pulled outta here before
you's got here.
‐No, you never.
‐Did too.
No, you never. If you did
you'd still be
talking about it.
Oh yeah, well, where'd it
come from then?
Well, you brought it
from home likely.
Well, there's nothin's even to
cooks it on anyways.
‐You gonna let that stop you?
‐What do you means?
Haven't you ever
heard of sashimis?
‐Sashimis?
‐Oh, I got time for sashimis.
‐What about sushi?
‐Sushis.
Oh, I got so much time
for sushis.
Yeah, we should pull it out
and hack it out and
down the hatch.
Oh no,
I knows what it is, I just...
I just don't think
you needs to put an "s"
on the end to that word.
Hey, Dary, you ever had
sushis with shrimps?
Yeah.
You ever had
sushis with unagis?
‐Yeah.
‐That's eels.
Oh, I know that's eels.
I just... I'm pretty sure
you don't needs an "s"
to pluralize those words.
Hey, Dary, you ever had
sashimis with salmons?
Oh, yeah. You ever had
sashimis with tunas?
Yeah. With wasabis?
Oh, yeah. Love wasabis.
I like wasabis, too.
If asks you politelys to
stop this, would you do it?
Oh, you can have yellowfin
tunas, bluefin tunas.
I think tunas make
the best sashimis.
I thinks I'm having
a panics attack.
Well, the Japanese call the
bluefin tunas maguro tunas,
those are kind of like the
default tunas
that they use in sushis.
Yeah, but toro is a
more expensive tuna but
it makes the best sashimis.
Oh, it's way better
than salmons.
Hey!
When's... When's Katy's
gettin' back from the citys?
Oh, she'll come back
when she's good and ready.
She'll figure it out.
I figure she'll be back
for sledding season.
Oh, Katy loves sleddin'.
(SIGHS)
It chap your ass at all that
there's only one shack on the
shed trail through
Letterkenny?
Well, it doesn't chap my ass,
but I guess there could be
another stop along the
trail for a social.
Yeah, like it doesn't
chap my ass either,
but I'm just sayin' that
sleddin' and socials
go together like
piss and a fart.
Yeah.
I guess there could be
another stop along the trail
for a social.
Could be another stop
along the trail for a dart.
Well, it's a great spot
for a darty‐party.
So, we're gonna build
a new shack?
I'm surprised we're not
buildin' a new shack
right now.
That's what I'm sayin'.
I figure it's about time that
we stopped talkin' about it
‐and started bein' about it.
‐Oh, we could just throw up
the structure and get all the
materials paid off
‐sellin' two‐dollar cans.
‐Two‐dollar socials.
Yeah, we could sell
whitefish sashimis
to help expedite the process.
Oh, we could get
real stinky and
sell perch and walleye sushis.
Hey!
Walleye...
Perch...
And whitefish...
Are not...
Sushi or...
Sashimi grade.
(SIGHS)
Well, yeah, I guess you'd
have to do pot
to accomplish
that sort of appetite.
Says you.
‐Pre‐game sandos?
‐Check, buddy.
‐Pre‐game nappies?
‐Check, bro.
Don Cherry's Rock 'Em
Sock 'Em 6 for motivation?
Sock 'Em 6.
Chel Tourney for
game situation visualization?
Second Chel Tourney for
peak performance imagery.
‐Pre‐game dump?
‐No pre‐game dump.
Hmm. No pre‐game cruncher.
No pre‐game deucer.
Better go drop that bomb.
Better go release the
chocolate hostage.
Better bust a grumpy.
Better go
call in a code brown.
‐Better go boost one.
‐Eat. Sleep. Boost.
‐Caffeine.
‐Check.
‐Creatine?
‐Livin' the dream.
Hold my spitter.
All right,
how're we gonna fuck this pig?
Well, you're gonna wanna
starts with dimensions.
‐What're you thinkin' there?
‐14‐by‐16.
What, you wanna play
dodgeball in there, Dary?
14‐by‐16, well,
that's five me's,
five you's and five Dary's.
You wanna play three team
dodgeball in there, Dan?
Call it 12‐by‐14.
You wanna play fuckin'
dodgeball in there, Dary.
12‐by‐14.
That's four me's,
four you's and four Dary's.
You wanna play two‐team
dodgeball with
one sub each in there, Dan?
How about 8‐by‐10?
Well, I'd fuck with
8‐by‐10.
No, you're not playin' no
dodgeball in no 8‐by‐10s.
I never wanted to play no
dodgeball in no 8‐by‐10.
Oh, I got so much time
for 8‐by‐10.
8‐by‐10,
that's three me's,
three you's and two Dary's.
‐Comfortably?
‐You're cozy.
Plus some
wiggle room in there.
Call it 8‐by‐10.
Call it a Texas size 10‐4,
good buddy.
Show you how we're gonna
have the structure.
What we're gonna do is put a
space heater here,
mini fridge here.
Gonna throw the
genny right out there.
What about the
sushis and sashimis?
‐Hey!
‐(DOOR OPENS)
Hey!
‐Hey.
‐How're ya now?
‐Good, and you?
‐Not so bad.
You fuckin' serious
with that turtleneck?
Lose a lot a heat in the neck.
You fuckin' serious
with that hair?
‐Figure it out.
‐You figure it out.
Where you's been?
‐Modeling.
‐How's that for you?
‐Boring.
‐Okay.
There's no money in it.
‐Way she goes.
‐A monkey could do it.
‐Good enough.
‐Missed sleddin' season, too.
I told you she'd miss
sleddin' season.
I was the one who said
she'd figure it out.
‐You figure it out.
Where's your shits?
About that...
These are...
My friends.
Well, what are your
friends named?
Shep and Kingsley.
‐Those are dude's names?
‐Yeah.
They sound like dog names.
I don't like
where this is goin'.
We'll be in my room.
Guys, hang up your coats.
Where's your
fuckin' shirt, Shep?
Where the fuck is
your shirt, Kingsley?
‐It ripped.
‐It ripped?
‐Mine too.
‐How?
'Cause I'm so fat.
Me too, I'm so fat.
I'm a bat fastard.
‐I'm a fat podger.
‐Guys...
Enough, let's go.
If I was a Dr. Seuss book
I'd be The Fat in the Hat.
If I was an arcade fighting
game I'd be Mortal Komfat.
If I was one of the
five boroughs in New York City
I'd be the Fatten Island.
If I was an Italian city‐state
I'd be the Fatican.
Put a fuckin' shirt on!
I don't know what happened
to you dusters,
but, fuck me, do you fuck dog!
Walkin' around poutin' like
your little sister
took your last Oreo.
And not a traditional Oreo,
no, a limited edition Oreo,
or seasonal Oreo
they're gonna take off
the shelf for another year.
Hey, Barts,
did little Natiesha take
your last Halloween Oreo?
You didn't get a chance to say
goodbye to that
delicious orange frosting?
What about you, Yorkie? Huh?
Did little Tamsyn take your
last Reese's
Peanut Butter Cup Oreo?
Well, it gets worse.
Those have been
discontinued forever.
What about you, Scholtzy, huh?
Did little Tay'Rhonda
take your last Ice Cream
Oreo Orange Sherbet?
That is a summertime flavor.
Good luck suckin' back on
one of those in the
next six months.
Fisky, I know.
You're a Birthday
Cream Fudge guy.
They're all gone. What?
Little DeSondra
was the culprit.
And her pal LarawnShawn
took the last Heads or
Tails Mega Stuff, too!
Hey, Boomtown.
You're an only child.
You got your
NASCAR Daytona Oreos?
It's fucking embarrassing!
Let me give you some
advice, donkeys.
Take a page out of
Jonesy and Reilly's book.
My boys, I skipped curfew call
for you last night 'cause
I knew you'd be doin' legs,
and I didn't want
to interrupt.
We've been doin' legs
two‐a‐days since
the first week
of summer, Coach.
Blocked every wheelchair ramp
in the arena so
we'd have to do stairs.
Tenacity.
You can't teach that.
You know, I never thought
those pheasants
would fuck the dog so hard
that you two would become
my studs!
‐Thanks, Coach.
Well, I need one win.
One W.
What are you gonna do
to get me that?
‐Selfish hockey.
That's right. Selfish hockey!
Break it down.
Skate the puck. Don't pass it.
Head man's still gonna be
there when you catch up.
Take it coast‐to‐coast.
Shots from poor angles
are still shots.
Buck and a half,
two‐minute shifts,
three minutes even.
Cruise the blue line
to catch your breath.
Bad bounce,
that's a good breakaway.
‐Gotta get the bounces, boys.
‐Perfect.
And a retaliation penalty
never hurt anyone.
What's our mantra?
BOTH: They don't ask how,
they ask how many.
That's right.
What did I tell you
about stick tape?
You don't need it!
The only people that'll be
worrying about puck handling
are Jonesy and Reilly!
Save it for them! Huh?
W!
Well, let's fuck this pig.
Structure goes here.
Sled parking here.
Pretty good spot
for pissin' over there.
Pissin' outside's for
dogs and degens.
I piss outside
as much as the dog does.
Well, I'm not above it either.
I'm just sayin'.
Fuck, we could really use some
kind of bar in this town, eh?
(PHONE BUZZING)
‐Katy.
‐Big brother.
‐How're ya now?
‐Good and you?
‐Not so bad.
‐My friends need
to borrow clothes.
Give 'em barn clothes.
I won't have barn clothes
in the house. They stink.
Guess you have to
put your friends
in the fuckin' barn then.
They don't have any clothes
of their own.
‐Okay.
‐They don't have any money.
‐Way she goes.
‐Models are always broke.
‐Good enough.
‐You have a baker's dozen
plaid shirts.
They only need two.
Give them the hand‐me‐downs
I got from
Dan's second cousin.
‐Who, Garrett?
‐No, Jarrett.
‐10‐4.
‐Over and out.
These are the
only ones that fit.
‐'Cause we're too podgey.
‐Ugh, don't start.
If I was a major league
baseball team
I'd be the L. A. Podgers.
If I was a major league
baseball pitcher
I'd be Podger Clemens.
If I was a pick‐up truck
I'd be a Podge Ram.
If I was a disguising
clothing pattern made for
hunting and combat
I'd be camou‐podge.
No, better without the shirts.
Okay. Now, go shut
both doors and lock them.
‐STEWART: Roald.
‐(EXCLAIMS)
You'll need to repeat that.
‐He's gone.
‐He's gone?
Along with all his stuff.
Devon is gone.
‐Roald.
‐Dude.
Hysterics are fruitless.
(HIGH‐PITCHED SQUEAL)
Stewart...
Tears are useless.
(SQUEALS) Stewart...
Pain is inevitable.
Where?
Why?
W motherfucking five!
I don't know.
He had everything here.
Hours upon hours of
ultra‐competitive gaming
laced with hip‐hop karaoke.
Add a dash of
late‐night loitering
and a splash of
petty vandalism.
And what have you got?
(SQUEALS) Stewart...
Utopia, Arcadia,
Kingdom come!
Devon hated petty vandalism.
He called it two‐bit.
Shabby. Shoestring.
Mmm, hence the term,
"petty," Roald.
Don't be redundant.
But you're right,
he did hate that.
This was his.
Verify.
Yeah.
Yes.
You got it the summer before
grade six at a
Sidewalk Sale Day.
Went halfsies on it.
Veracious. And this?
‐Roald, substantiate!
‐Yes.
You stole it from his grandma
so you could game
Ecco the Dolphin on Sega CD
in grade three.
Irrefutable.
Well, I guess he didn't take
all of his stuff, now, did he?
(GASPING)
Fuck me, that was refreshing.
Incoming!
(YELPS IN FEAR)
Stink bombs?
(SCREAMING)
Devon.
Fuck, she looks friendly
as a couch, ain't she, boys?
Went up faster than shit
through a goose, too.
‐Lickety‐split.
‐Real nice of Tyson and
Joint Boys to help us out.
More hands make less work.
ALL: Welp...
Fire up the genny, Gary.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Now test out the
motion sensor, Dan.
‐Boss, man...
‐I appreciates this.
Aw, it's tits.
‐Well, there's one step left.
‐Yeah!
‐Christen it?
‐Should we christen it?
Well, are we
gonna christen it?
Should we christen it?
I feel like we should be
christening it.
Well, I'm surprised we're not
christening it right now.
‐Gordie Howe hat trick, ferda.
‐Game puck goes to Gordie.
Yeah. I had 18 shots
on net, boys.
Ovechkin numbers.
Played no less than
38 minutes.
Duncan Keith numbers.
But, uh, 9‐4 ferda.
Ferda other team.
You know, it's sick,
unreal stats.
But, uh...
Be nice to have
a couple of W's, too.
Be nice to have "a" W.
Players only meeting?
Yeah. Coach is right,
I mean, no W's on the season
that's just...
‐Fucking embarrassing!
‐Coach.
Players only meeting.
Oh. Well, that's embarrassing.
Jesus.
All right you pheasants,
what's the problem?
Spill it, pheasys.
My wife left me,
you little bitch!
Feels like someone ran
a coarse glove hustle
on my love muscle. Yorkie?
Same, Barts.
Feels like someone
fork‐gored my
pork sword. Scholtzy?
She's gone.
Feels like someone took
a big snackers on
my little knackers.
Pussy. Fisky.
Out the door.
Feels like someone slammed
a super soccer kick into my
Ron‐Donny long schlong.
Boomtown!
I'm an only child,
as Coach previously and
pitilessly pointed out.
I'd kill for a little
Natiesha, Tamsyn, Tay'Rhonda,
DeSondra,
LarawnShawn, in my life.
But someone did steal my last
NASCAR Daytona Oreo!
That wasn't funny!
But, you all love your wives.
‐What happened, boys?
‐(DOOR OPENS)
‐BOTH: Angie?
‐Boys.
Unreal game.
Who wants to
take me out for a sando?
I'll let you work it out.
BOTH: Angie?
That's my girl,
you little bitch.
She makes me want to rub
slick on my disco stick.
Yorkie?
Correction, Barts. She's mine.
She makes me wanna go
Warcraft
all over my man shaft.
Scholtzy.
Mine.
She makes me wanna take a
low fiver to my deep‐V diver.
Pussy. Fisky?
Uh‐uh. She's mine.
She makes me wanna take a
fresh fruit to my flesh flute.
Boomtown!
You all have sisters.
I hope you're kind to them.
I hope you cherish them.
This one's mine!
(GRUNTING)
This is bad, buddy.
This is really bad, buddy.
I think we've got...
BOTH: A puck bunny.
DAN: It looks darker
out here
than the inside of
a fuel tank.
Head towards
the sensor light, Dan.
I don't appreciates this.
Well, how we
gonna fuck this pig?
We find who did it.
And we beat the
shit out of them.