You were crushin' Gus N' Bru
with your pals the other day.
Pound a round
of Gus N' Bru, Gailer.
(GROUP GROANS)
GROUP: Bonnie McMurray.
Thank you, Bonnie.
No problem, Wayne.
‐How're ya now?
‐Good. And you?
Oh, not so bad.
Bottoms up, super chieftains.
(SIGHS)
Well, I'll go have a pee.
Mmm, breakin' the seal.
I'm gonna go beat the piss
outta the little fella.
Let 'er fly, Dan.
You old porcelain painter,
get the fuck outta here.
Porcelain punishers, Gail.
You got a big number one
on deck there, big shooter?
‐Go squirt, little Curt.
‐WAYNE: Go rock one, Dan.
AM/FM urination station,
get the fuck outta here.
All right. So I'm gonna
make youse all proud
down by the yellow pond.
(GRUNTING) Yup, I will.
‐Whoa, Dad.
‐Hey, Dad.
‐There you are, Dad.
‐Dad. Hey, Dad.
Who's a dad?
GROUP: You are, Dad!
Why? What youse hear?
Only dads grunt like that
when they stand up.
‐Or sit down.
‐Or come...
Over to move the furniture,
get the fuck outta here.
That was a textbook
dad noise, Dan.
Okay, youse guys
have all been eatin'
too many sugar cereals.
Don't!
'Cause if you wanna...
I haven't had
too much sugar cereal.
Sit back down, Dan.
‐Why, Miss Katy?
‐Just do it.
(GRUNTING) Okay.
How are ya now, Dad?
You a minivan
or cross‐over guy, Dad?
Up north for some
father‐son fishin', Dad?
Don't get the kids
all riled up before bed, Dad.
‐And, now to be fair...
‐(MIMICKING) To be fair...
‐To be fair...
‐ALL: To be fair.
Lots of people emit sounds
when they stands up
and sits down, not just dads.
No, it's mostly just dads.
You wanna go toss around
the pig skin there, Dad?
Can you please drive us
to the water park, Dad?
Let's go back
to Disney World, Dad.
Can we, can we, can we,
please? Fuck outta here.
All right, what's about moms?
No, moms would never do that.
Moms don't want
to age themselves.
‐Dads don't care, though.
‐Fuck, no.
Dads don't give a care.
It's like,
"Hey, hon, better go clean up
those lawn clippings."
"All right.
(GRUNTING) "Guess I'll watch
State of Play later."
It's like, uh,
"Hey, hon, I'm gonna scoot off
"to book club there, can you
watch Bella and Edward?"
(GRUNTING) "All right. Just
had Field of Dreams PVR'd."
‐(SIGHS)
‐It's like,
"Hey, babe, I think
we should take a vacation
"without the kids."
"Sure, Karen,
(GRUNTING) "'cause I could
use more financial stress."
"Derek, I'm going to
the Fantasia Party
"with the girls. Can you
unload the dishwasher?"
"Of course, Susan.
(GRUNTING) "I guess I'm
jerkin' off again tonight."
Youse is hilarious.
(GRUNTING) All my friends
is smart alecks.
(GRUNTING) Just a bunch
of smart alecks.
(GRUNTING) Guess I'm
jerkin' off again tonight.
See, like, not all dad noises
are bad dad noises.
So, like maybe
sometimes mom might say,
"Hey, hon, the kids are gone
away campin' for the weekend,
"why don't we do
some toe curlin'?"
And then dad might lean into
a real Tony the Tiger
dad noise.
Like... (GROWLING) "Great!"
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Sure thing, Bonnie.
See you soon.
WAYNE: Hmm...
What's the frequency, Kenneth?
Bonnie McMurray
has invited us
to a hot tub party.
Well, who doesn't love
a hot tub party?
‐Dary?
‐I would love
to go to a hot tub party
at Bonnie McMurray's.
Daniel?
Oh, I wouldn't miss Bonnie's
hot tub party for the world.
Youse two
should take a deep breath.
That's a good way
to get hemorrhoids.
Yeah, that,
or sitting on a cold surface.
Now that's an old wives' tale.
‐No, it isn't. No, it isn't.
‐Yes, it is.
‐Figure it out.
‐BOTH: She's mine!
Let's get these guys
a fuckin' Puppers.
You heard me say it.
Because I heard me say it,
and I know
you heard me say it.
‐I'm sweet on Bonnie McMurray.
‐Oh, yeah?
And how's that workin' out
for you, big shooter?
‐What's the problem?
‐BOTH: Bonnie McMurray.
You're both sweet
on Bonnie McMurray?
BOTH: Yes.
You know,
I have had a busy winter,
but I'd toss my hat
in the ring there, too.
Did youse do pot today?
‐KATY: Yes.
‐BOTH: No.
‐BOTH: Why?
‐Well...
She's a bit young, isn't she?
Well, she's 20.
‐Well, I'm only...
‐Doesn't matter.
‐And I'm just...
‐Don't care.
‐(BANGING)
‐BOTH: She's mine!
Well, she's a pretty girl.
It's just, uh...
Could let the paint dry
a wee bit there, eh?
I'll tell you what, Dan.
What, Dary?
Let's let her decide.
It's always her decision!
The battle
for Bonnie McMurray begins.
Do you know sperms
can stay alive in hot tubs?
‐(SLURPS)
‐(PHONE BUZZING)
‐How're ya now?
‐It's not us.
Not s'bad.
Did you hear me, shirt‐tucker?
All the clown costumes,
the petty vandalism
around Letterkenny,
it's not us.
I've not heard about it,
it mustn't be s'bad.
Remember when I said
it was petty?
See, we've got our hands full
of degens from up country.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Okay...
You do you, boo,
I'll take care of this.
‐Over and out.
‐(PHONE BEEPS)
That true about sperms
in hot tubs?
No.
But the writers of
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
could have kinda run with that
if they wanted to.
‐(CONTROLLERS CLICKING)
‐(GAME BEEPING)
‐STEWART: Roald.
‐ROALD: Stewart.
STEWART: How long have
we been original NES gaming?
ROALD: Two hours Contra,
two hours Ninja Gaiden,
two hours
Teenage Mutant Nina Turtles,
two hours Simon's Quest,
two hours Mega Man 2.
‐Ten hours.
‐Ish.
Yeah.
There's heat on FAK‐U
after our most recent ruckus.
It's best we nest.
‐ROALD: We should stop.
‐(GAE SCOFFS)
‐GAE: No.
‐STEWART: No?
‐(SCOFFS)
‐What do you mean... (SCOFFS)
(SCOFFS) I know
what she means.
No, we don't stop gaming.
‐No?
‐(SCOFFS) Did I stutter?
(SCOFFS) No, you did not.
Too much left to delve.
Now, I'm not complaining,
but these games
are between 20
and 30 years old.
You're not...
Bored?
Far from blase.
Wondrous.
What's next?
We haven't even ransacked
the sports games yet.
‐Guilty pleasures.
‐Pleasures, no less.
‐Tecmo Super Bowl.
‐(BOTH GROANING)
‐Punch‐Out!!
‐Hoops.
‐(BOTH GROANING)
‐Excitebike.
‐(BOTH GASPING)
‐Blades of Steel.
‐(BOTH MOANING)
‐American Gladiators.
‐(BOTH SHRIEKING)
‐California Games.
‐But after that...
‐NES Open?
‐Baseball Simulator 1.000?
‐(SIGHS)
‐Paperboy!
‐(HICCUPPING)
‐No. Let's do something else.
‐(SIGHS)
Do you guys like dancing?
‐Fuck it. Let's go.
‐(LAUGHS)
Hold it.
You're not going anywhere.
Smells like...
Feet in here.
Eh?
‐Players‐only meeting.
‐Players‐only meeting, ferda.
Now, we're close, boys.
We're gonna get that W,
but there's still some
spring cleaning
to take care of before
this team comes together.
Some housekeeping, ferda.
Now... (SIGHS)
To truly come together
as a team...
‐And get W's...
‐Order must be established.
And to establish order,
we must implement fines.
(SNAPS) Reilly
will be your commissioner.
(SNAPS) Jonesy will be
co‐commissioner
plus treasurer.
I'll be collecting
fines, boys.
SHORSEY: Give your balls
a tug, you tit‐fucker.
Shorsey. Hmm.
You bring me
to fine number one.
Boys, I wake up
in the middle of the night
dry‐heaving
at the amount of bush
in this room.
We thought
tummy‐stick hedgehogs
were extinct, boys.
Shave your
fuckin' junk hair, boys.
It's disgusting, boys.
And Shorsey
is the guiltiest of 'em all!
‐(SHORSEY FARTS)
‐Reilly
will be your bush inspector.
And Jonesy will be
your associate bush inspector.
Plus...
GM of bush.
Now, we were really
hard on you guys last year
before we were bush inspector,
associate bush inspector,
and GM of bush, so...
We're appointing Barts
as Senior Director
of Bush Operations.
Appointing Yorkie Senior Scout
in Charge of Bush Development.
First fine goes to Shorsey!
SHORSEY: Fuck your
entire fucking life, bud.
From now on,
$20 fine,
every game and praccy
'til she's
shaved down to the wood.
As bald as a Teenage Mutant
Ninja Turtle, Shoresey!
‐SHORSEY: Tit‐fucker.
‐(SIGHS)
On to the second order
of business.
‐Hmm. Hmm.
‐Hmm. Boomtown.
There are certain things
that stand directly in the way
of a team coming together.
There are certain things
that stand
in the way of W's, buddy.
And if you truly want
this team to come together...
And if you want this team
to get W's...
We're gonna need
to see your junk, buddy.
Don't feel bad.
There are junk hiders
on every team.
But I think I speak for the
entire room when I say...
What are you
hiding down there, bud?
Something weird going on
down there, bud?
Again, don't feel bad.
I mean, some teams have guys
that don't even shower
after praccy,
which is worse than bush.
But, we see
you face the wall in the room
when your junk's out,
and you face the wall
in the shower
when your junk's out.
You've seen my junk.
Let's see your junk, buddy.
‐Pull it out, buddy.
‐Whip it out, buddy.
Let's have a look
at your junk.
Unsheathe it, bro.
(HOT TUB BUBBLING)
You ever got in someone's car
in your wet swim trunks
and had them turn on
the seat warmers?
No.
Kinda makes you
feel like you've peed.
You know, big brother,
that's almost not worth
talkin' about.
‐Over 'n out.
‐Ooh.
(GROWLING) Oh, great!
Well, there's
fuckin' Tony the Tiger.
‐Hey, Dad.
‐You know what?
I got bigger fish
to fry tonight.
Hi, Bonnie.
‐Hi, Bonnie.
‐Hi, Wayne.
‐How're ya now?
‐Good. And you?
‐Not s'bad.
‐Any good dad noises
‐on the way in?
‐DAN: No.
You know what, we've really
got all the personalities
on display in this hot tub.
Like what?
Well, you got the guy who sits
with his chin in the water.
‐Sure you do.
‐Then you got the guy who sits
‐with their shoulders out.
‐Sure you do.
Then you got the guy
who takes up
two to three times more
real estate
than everybody else
because they're just like...
‐Puttin' the vibe out there.
‐Sure you do.
And of course
you've got your edge sitters.
That's me, Wayne.
What's your story
over there, hands?
I'm the guy
who keeps his hands dry
so he can still dig out
and light smokes.
What if it's
an outdoor hot tub?
Don't your hands get cold?
I'm also the guy
who would never admit
that sort of thing.
What about you
keep one hand out of the water
to dig out smokes
and I'll keep one hand
out of the water
so I can light them.
More hands make less work.
‐You're all right, Rosie.
‐So, Bonnie...
What are you
looking for in a guy?
I don't really have a type,
I don't think.
Okay, but if you
had to choose between
someone who was...
More big and hairy...
Versus somebody who's
a lot less big and hairy,
but more pale.
Which... Which way
are you leaning towards there?
Like, muscly big?
(STRAINING) Yeah. Muscly big.
Well, that's generous.
Oh, they're
in there somewhere.
And I like hairy versus, like,
groomed or manscaped.
But how hairy?
‐I could grow a beard.
‐No, you can't.
‐Can, too.
‐Cannot.
‐Can, too. Can, too!
Well, I can always
shaves my beard, easy‐peasy.
Or evens get a haircut.
Let's take about 80% off her
over there, Squirrelly Dan.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, look, bubbles!
Bonnie, what are you
looking for in a relationship?
I kinda like
being single right now.
‐Humor me.
‐I don't know.
I've never really
been in love.
Okay, let's get
this ball rolling.
(CLEARS THROAT) Wayne. Rosie.
What's the key
to making this look so good?
‐BOTH: Space.
‐Like, distance?
Not distance.
Although distance makes
the heart grow fonder.
‐Just space.
‐Space.
So you don't wanna get like...
BOTH: Sick of each other.
Example.
I like to read, a lot.
I like to stay in and read.
It's not easy telling a guy
you don't want to see him
because you want to stay in
and read.
Let's test this theory.
Dary...
Say you asked Bonnie McMurray
out on a date and she says...
I'm going to stay in and read.
‐She up to somethin'.
‐Dan?
Oh, she's
definitely up to something.
‐Wayne?
‐Must be a pretty good book.
Must be like...
‐The Road.
‐Uh, no.
Still suspicious of that.
Yeah, wouldn't that
make you... Wary?
No reason not to trust her
'til she gives you one, bud.
You know, Bonnie,
I had my first girl phase
around your age.
Let's see it, bud.
Is something weird
going on there, bud?
Boom! $20 fine!
Fisky.
‐What?
Oh, I don't know what kind of
pre‐tyke, sub‐amateur hour
Teenage Mutant Ninja
fucking Turtles organizations
you guys have played for
in the past,
but don't step on the logo
is straight fuckin'...
‐It's basic.
‐Don't step on the logo.
Live for the logo,
respect the logo!
‐Fisky.
‐Then why is it on the floor?
That brings me
to my next point.
‐Your jerseys.
‐Oh, yo, buddy.
You should call it
a sweater, buddy.
‐Don Cherry's orders.
‐Don Cherry, buddy.
Your sweater never ever
touches the floor.
Hang up the sweater.
Live for the sweater.
‐Respect the sweater.
‐Mmm.
REILLY: Boomtown!
You're not off the hook, bud.
Do you want us to trust you?
Do you want this team
to come together?
‐You want a fuckin' W?
‐Yeah!
Then we're gonna need
to see your junk, buddy.
Let's see your junk, buddy.
‐Mmm‐hmm.
‐You know what?
‐Team exercise? Team exercise.
‐Yeah. Yeah.
All right, boys, everybody up.
Trousers down,
junks out, boys.
‐Lets help a teammate.
‐Junks out, boys.
‐(SLAP SHOT BANGS)
‐Is...
Someone on the ice, bud?
That's our ice, buddy.
(BOTH GRUMBLING)
REILLY: Hey,
don't move, pheasants.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
So, Bonnie,
what has a guy have do
to get your attention?
I don't know.
Make me laugh, I guess.
BOTH: Turn off the bubbles.
(CHURNING STOPS)
Hey, Bonnie,
have you ever seen
‐It Came from Beneath the Sea?
‐No.
‐(GLUGS)
‐You have now.
(DARYL AND DAN CACKLING)
That was well brought up,
‐too bad you weren't.
‐(CHUCKLES)
Dary actually
stole my joke there.
But lucky's for you, Bonnies,
I'm very funny's
‐and I have lots of jokes.
‐Okay.
Hey, Bonnies, what's another
word for champagne?
Um. Oh, bubbly.
‐If you say so.
‐(GLUGS)
(BOTH CACKLING)
You've got a rich inner life.
(CHUCKLES) You're funny, Katy.
That was funny, Dan.
It was almost as funny
as the first time
that I heard it.
BOTH: Youse shouldn't fart
in front of girls.
That was my joke, Dan.
You stole my joke, didn't you?
(BUBBLING)
Don't you interrupt me.
‐I swear I will... Stop...
‐(BUBBLING CONTINUES)
Stop it, right now!
‐I... Just quit it.
‐Okay, enough!
‐Please.
‐And thank you.
You're not so funny,
are you now, Dary?
How's that book comin' along?
I miss that book.
Did you hear
they're still searching
for the Loch Ness monster?
(LAUGHING) And she's migrated.
Ooh...
Funny, I thought
these were Ogopogo waters.
Guess they are.
Don't make me come over there,
Dan, because I...
If you do that
one more time... Just...
Wink at me again, I...
Daniel!
(EXCLAIMING) Daniel,
stop your fartin'
and telling your jokes!
(BUBBLING)
Are those jets
on auto‐timer, Bonnie?
Nope.
WAYNE: Did you press
the button again, Katy?
Hard no.
BOTH: Over and out.
‐Who's that?
‐What's that?
‐Tanis.
‐What's a Tanis?
Well, aren't you
a little bundle of sass.
You better watch
your little tongue
before I flick you
with my womanhood.
Did your balls drop
finally, Skiddo?
Feel a little fur
on your nut sack?
'Cause that is the only logic
I can think of
behind why you chodes would
terrorize this whole town
knowing that Wayne
would think it was us.
Although I am a self‐admitted
glutton for punishment...
It never crossed my mind.
I will wipe
that smirk off your face
like pixie dust over there
wipes your little asshole.
‐It was just once! I...
‐STEWART: Hey!
No, you were passed out.
‐ROALD: I was...
‐I said stop it!
I was just trying to help.
All right, I need to get
to the bottom of this first.
What, do you, like,
hang out with these losers?
‐Which losers?
‐Peter Pan and Tinker Bell.
They're giving you drugs,
aren't they?
What makes them losers?
Trust me, tart. You don't
want me to answer that.
‐Tart?
‐That's what I said. Tart.
‐Intriguing.
‐What is?
Well, the psychology
at work here.
Yeah, fuckin' right.
It's called intimidation.
No, it isn't.
It's called projection.
Okay, it didn't take me
very long
to realize I don't like you.
‐My mother's a psychologist.
‐TANIS: 'Kay.
You harbor guilt
over your promiscuous impulses
so you can call me a tart.
That's projection
of the sexual feelings
you're attempting to hide.
‐Poorly.
‐For who?
For Stewart.
You like Stewart?
‐No!
‐And you two...
You call my friend Roald here,
Tinker Bell and pixie dust
because you're uncomfortable
with your own sexualities.
His open homosexuality
makes you feel
even more uncomfortable.
That actually
kind of makes sense.
‐No, it doesn't!
‐Yours kind of makes sense.
No, it doesn't.
Let's try an exercise.
Hug Roald.
See how it makes you feel.
You might be surprised.
‐No!
‐No.
Roald, help them out.
Encourage them.
Like... Like, I hug them?
A big hug.
‐Can I be in the middle?
‐Ugh!
It may be
distressing at first,
but you owe it
to yourselves to try.
You could be so happy.
‐Uh‐huh.
‐We should try, too, Tanis.
(CHUCKLES) Fuck, no.
I'm warning you, Skiddo.
Whoa! Second warning.
All right. Do damage, boys.
Let's go!
(TANIS SIGHS)
Oui. Alors... Tart.
I'll be back.
(GRUNTING)
(CHEERING) Oh,
you're the best, Gae!
‐Artistry. Virtuosity.
‐(CHUCKLES)
An undocked dismantlement
of the decrepit.
‐Fuckin', eh.
‐Was all that true?
Is your mom
really a psychologist?
WOMAN: Yes, she is.
And we're going home.
WOMAN: Gae?
(PUCK CLATTERING)
‐Tyson?
‐Joint Boy.
You guys can play?
Boys, hockey's 50% mental
and 50% being mental.
I'm mostly just mental.
(WHISPERS) I'm still not sure
that's PC, buddy, but...
BOTH: Bas McRae!
Buddy...
We've spent the entire season
trying to bring
the team together.
And get W's, buddy.
Maybe the entire time...
We just needed
to add some grit, buddy.
A little sandpaper, ferda?
(SLAP SHOT RICOCHETS)
Boys, how would you guys
like to play
for the Letterkenny Irish?
How would you boys
like to get a fuckin' W?
I'm no stud,
but I can sure as hell
make some room out there
for you boys.
I'm dog shit.
But I can beat the fuck
out of 95%
of the population on Earth.
BOTH: Wheel, snipe,
celly, boys!
‐Follow us.
‐(EXCLAIMS)
(EXHALES) Nice.
‐What's goin' on here, boys?
‐Is this a hazing ritual?
(SIGHING)
Boomtown! (CHUCKLES)
‐Mmm.
‐Okay. Modest.
Nothing weird going on.
No weird j‐hook, ferda.
No mutant,
bobble‐head turtleneck.
No weird long snout anteater.
No disfiguration
or discoloration, ferda.
‐Healthy.
‐That's modest.
Great dick, Boomtown.
Boomtown?
You've just helped this team
come together, buddy.
Feel good about that.
And these guys are going to
help us get that W.
If...
Boomtown...
Is that okay with you?
Boomtown?
Let's do this, boys!
‐(GROWLING)
‐(LAUGHS)
JONESY: Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa! Whoa!
Put your junk away, boys.
We didn't sign up
for a sword fight, boys.
It's gross.
Well.
Congratulations, degens.
Your jokes
just cost us company.
Rosie did say
she was missing her book.
‐Yeah, she's up to something.
‐She's up to somethings.
Regardless...
Full transparency, Bonnie.
You have a number
of interested parties in here.
‐I've gathered that.
‐So...
‐Where do your interests lie?
‐Well, Daryl...
DAN: No!
KATY: No!
You're muscly, big.
‐Yeah.
‐That's generous.
Kinda. Dan.
DARYL: No!
KATY: No!
You're hairy, which I like
more than groomed
or manscaped.
And I can always
shaves my beard.
And Katy...
DAN: No!
DARYL: No!
You make me laugh.
And we haven't even
started tickling yet.
But... I like being single.
GROUP: No!
Because then
you can fool around
with whoever you want
and not get in trouble
from anyone.
(GROUP LAUGHING)
Ah!
‐(CHEERS AND SIGHS)
‐What?
‐Oh, I'd be in trouble.
‐I'd be in troubles.
I'd be in big trouble.
BONNIE: From who?
‐Wayne?
‐Yeah?
Thanks for not turning
the seat warmers on
in your truck.
Kinda makes you feel...
‐Like you peed?
‐Yeah.
Yeah.
‐That was fun.
‐Yeah.
And funny.
I didn't want to admit it
'cause there's...
Such a thing
as an inappropriate...
‐Yeah.
Thank you for a wonderful day.
‐Will you be reading tonight?
‐Yeah.
I hope you'll enjoy your book.
After we make some dad noises?
(GROWLING) Great!