A bit of fuss down
at the church the other day.
Glen.
GLEN: Wayne.
How are you now?
GLEN: Good, and you?
Oh, not so bad.
Ooh, look what
you brought with you.
Hello, Daryl.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck, you're naked
as a jay bird.
Wayne, it's humid.
It's the humidity.
Y'all might want to
think about doing
the same thing,
just pop your
pants right off,
that way no one
gets sticky.
Nope.
It's not so bad.
What's the fuss?
Ma O'Dell mentioned something
about you helping her get
a squirrel out of her attic.
I'm faced with
a similar conundrum.
Right over there.
It seems some kinda
rodent's made his home
over there.
I have not seen him,
but I sure can smell him.
(CHUCKLES)
(ANIMAL CHATTERING)
Hum.
(EXHALES)
It's a possum.
GLEN: Hmm.
DARYL: Possum.
WAYNE: That's right.
Oh, pitter patter,
let's get at 'er.
Do you wanna know what?
I'd reach into a
pirate hooker's chamber pot
before I'd reach in there.
And I'm going to tell ya.
Possums are immune
to snake venom.
They could probably survive
a nuclear blast.
I think it's pronounced
new‐cue‐lar.
Mmm, but it isn't.
They're mutants.
They have forked
fuckin' penises.
(SCOFFS)
We should all be so lucky.
They do this thing called
'Playing Possum'
where they appear dead and
emit a death stink from
their butt holes, fuck.
(SIGHS)
I found one
playing possum one time,
thought it was dead
and buried it.
It dug itself out
a few hours later
and fucked a hen
right in front of her chicks.
Wayne, think about
the swear jar.
You're putting
so much money in.
All right, let me take
peek see?
Pitter‐patter.
Always had a skilled hand
in wrangling vermin.
Thank you, Daryl.
And that doesn't surprise me.
No sweat.
(GLEN LAUGHS) No sweat?
In this heat?
That is rich and it's funny.
Honestly though,
just take off your jumper.
I'll hold it for you.
You crawl up in there,
no one gets dirty.
Glen? Glen?
Yes.
Let's take about 20%
off 'er up there, all right?
Now, you wanna have an eye
because he'll come out
meaner and spit
and go like a hot damn.
Is he likely to bite?
Is a duck's ass watertight?
Get ready to give him the
size nine's if he jukes by me.
How be I give him the size
twelve and a halfs instead?
(CHATTERING)
Oh, I see him.
That's some drunk evolution
right there, bud.
You gotta wonder what
two Christ‐made miscreants
mated to make that.
It's almost not worth
thinkin' about.
Do I just reach for him?
That's a better idea
than going in head first.
Put him where?
Under my boot.
(GLEN SIGHS) Boys, just do
your best not to make too big
a mess, all right?
And I'm sorry again
about all this heat.
Whoo‐hoo!
Oh, for fuck‐sakes.
(CHATTERING)
(THUD)
Ow.
You wish there was a
Pied Piper for possums,
but there isn't, so you're
gonna have to just keep
pickin' 'em off with the .22.
Buckle up
'cause they're fuckin' ugly.
Of course, that's not to say
I have it all my damn self.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Is that a herpe
on your hand, Daryl?
Did you pay a little extra
to go all the way with a
ripper in the back room again?
WAYNE: No, I don't think
he'd make that mistake twice.
Got a little
trouser trauma?
Was she fun
or was she fungal?
(LAUGHS)
Hey, guess what?
A guy's girlfriend
is having a hard time
parking the car, right?
He says,
"You should get tested."
She says, "Well no,
I'm not so bad at driving."
He says,
"No, I have chlamydia."
Is that a bite?
The guy takes
a hooker out for supper.
He gave her his peas,
she gave him herpes.
Daryl, what happened?
Did something bite you?
WAYNE: A possum.
A possum?
WAYNE: That's right.
Well, he could have rabies.
Boo fuckin' hoo.
No, rabies is serious.
It attacks the
central nervous system.
(VOMITS)
(KATY SIGHS)
If he gets puke between
the floor boards
it ain't coming out.
WAYNE: Well, I can't take him
to the clinic.
I gotta do an ice run
for the jamboree this week.
KATY: Oh, Christ.
Well, Daryl, we're gonna
have to take your van.
Oh, yeah?
Where's your nut sack
boyfriend's today, Katy?
They're at an away game
against the Natives.
Oh, I bet they're
looking forward to playing
those tough pricks.
Christ.
(SIGHS)
You sure you're ready
to saddle up to the
jamboree again?
It was kind of you
and Angie's thing.
No sense sittin'
on my hands.
Time to find
a new dance partner.
All right, Daryl.
Pitter‐patter.
Hey, why are crabs
always so tired?
It's 'cause they only
sleep in snatches.
JONESY: Hey, wait a minute.
We're...
We're missing two schmelts.
Where are Deetzy and Burnsy?
Oh, looks like a bad case
of the Native flu, bro.
What's the Native flu?
You're an idiot.
The Natives are
tough as hell.
So another way to say someone
is chicken‐shit to play them
is to say they have
the Native flu.
Mix in a fuckin' clue,
brotato chip.
Keep those fucking bags up,
schmelt.
Wayne.
Bonnie, how are you now?
Good and you?
Not so bad.
This isn't all for you,
is it?
It sure is.
Is it for the jamboree?
If we ever get it there.
Save me a dance?
Yup, sure.
Thank you. I've always wanted
to dance with you, Wayne.
Oh, yeah?
We've all been watching
you and Angie dance
for so long thinking
when's it gonna
be our turns?
Oh, yeah?
But trust me,
watching was enough.
You used to move
her body around like
it didn't weigh a feather.
Well, you know,
I think I got about a dozen
baker's dozen here
I guess we could just
scan them and then
I'll get out of your hair.
Oh, yeah,
I'll scan them.
Okay.
It's broken.
It'll be our little secret.
(KATY SIGHS)
Okay, sit down.
(DARYL BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh.
Stewart?
Katy?
You look grisly.
You look beautiful.
But I can't quite
see you right now.
What's wrong with you?
Meth?
(LAUGHS) I don't know what
you're talking about.
(SCOFFS)
You're not
a teenager anymore.
It's not charming.
I use to charm you?
Wrong takeaway.
You know,
you're not a fuckin' idiot.
You could turn it around
if you wanted to.
You know, I remember
sneaking into your parties
when I was 15,
stealing your mix‐tapes.
All your own music.
I was really impressed.
Guess those days
are over, though.
All right, Dairy, let's go.
Dairy, come on.
(STRUGGLING)
And yeah.
You did use to charm me.
McMurray, how're ya now?
Not so bad, and you?
Not so bad.
I see you back
to the jamboree, now.
A few weeks off there.
Oh, you noticed.
Well, it's hard not to notice
all that Scottish tartan plaid
you seem to enjoy so much.
I wanted to talk about
something important.
Okay.
My sister Bonnie
is back from college,
and she's a damn fine woman.
Oh, yeah.
I just seen her down
at the dollar store, there.
You sure it was her?
I mean, last time I seen her
last she was in a kind of
a DIY maxi dress,
but she may have added
a crochet pattern sweater
on account of the breeze.
Maybe autumn foliage
or an Algonquin green?
Okay.
I think she'd be a damn fine
match for you, Wayne.
That's if you're ready.
You know, 'cause of
Angie and all.
She's a lovely girl.
(INHALES)
(GURGLES)
(BOTH SPEAK)
No, you go ahead.
That is if you...
But you started,
you mind finishing?
Oh, it's just, was gonna say
the space, looks,
looks nice and clean
without the...
Yup.
Run pretty good.
Well, all right. All right.
Yeah. Hey, uh,
I'll let you carry on.
It's a good box of ice. Yeah.
Yeah, good to see you.
Have a good one.
Hey, wait.
You save her dance now,
eh, big boy?
Good enough,
McMurray.
Atta boy.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Does that taste right?
Ya, okay.
Mmm.
(SUCKING)
I think so, I don't know,
I don't know.
I've had an epiphany!
Uh, can you taste this?
No.
Never again.
Okay, okay, okay,
then, can you snort it?
No. I've given up
on the meth business.
I'm going back
to the turntables.
Hmm?
Back to the ones and twos.
DEVON: For what?
To become a superstar DJ.
DEVON:
Oh, okay, okay, uh...
But first, can you...
Let's just try...
No.
I need you guys to tell
everyone you know
that I am hosting
a rave in Letterkenny,
and I will be spinning
under all of my aliases.
How many aliases
have you had?
DJ Pimpy Longstockings,
DJ Peter Blumpkin,
DJ White Power Nap,
DJ White Power Bottom.
They'll all be there!
DEVON: All of them.
Mmm‐mmm, so you're quitting
the meth business?
I've quit the meth business.
But Menergy Spa is still like,
a thing though, right?
Well, how are you going
to get people to come?
I'll post it on my
fuckin' Facebook.
And you guys will post it
on your fuckin' Facebooks.
KATY: Wayne.
Christ, Katy,
put some fuckin'
clothes on.
Not my forte.
Unfortunate.
What are you doing?
Well, I think it's
pretty obvious
that I'm moving hay bales
from here over to here.
Although, that one's
a straw bale.
Why?
(PHONE RINGING)
Well, pick up your
fuckin' phone. McMurray's been
trying to reach you all day.
(SNIFFS)
(CLEARS THROAT) McMurray.
At least I was yesterday!
How're ya now?
Not so bad and you?
Not so bad.
Listen, Wayne.
I've gotta cancel
the Jamboree here.
The Ag Hall's been
booked up.
For the whole week?
Yes, sir.
That's Monday, Tuesday,
Wednesday, Thursday, Friday,
Saturday and guess what else?
Sunday.
What for?
Uh, Stewart.
He's throwing a rave.
I don't know, he says
he needs time to set up
or something like that.
Said something about a
glow stick Segway saunter
across the rainbow road level
of Mario Kart for Nintendo 64?
I don't know, what the fuck.
And you green‐lit
that tom‐fuckery?
Had to. Agricultural Hall
is low on funds.
All‐day bookings
is a big boost for us.
So, I couldn't say no.
Agricultural Halls are
for Agricultural music.
Not for fuckin' raves.
Well, that's no way to get
your communication badge,
boy scout.
(PHONE RINGS)
Dairy.
DARYL ON PHONE: Wayne. Clinic.
Pick up. Not feel good.
Well, he's not gonna get
his communication badge,
either.
(HONKING)
Dairy.
What's the fuss?
Good 'n you?
Where you goin'?
I don't know where I am.
Don't look at your hand.
What's the fuss?
Think I have rabies.
Oh, boo fuckin' hoo,
big shootsy‐wootsy.
But 'cept do you wanna
know what?
What's that?
Nabbing that possum
was kind of a thrill.
I think I could start
a pest removal business.
Oh, Daryl,
that's just silly.
But 'cept do you wanna know
what? I'm gonna help you..
You know Stewart's having
a rave at the Ag Hall?
Agricultural Halls are for
agricultural music.
"Not for fuckin' raves."
That's what I said.
So here's what we're gonna do
and I'm gonna tell ya.
We're gonna wrangle as many
of those critters as possible,
and let 'em loose
at Stewart's rave.
How do we get the word out
about the business?
Oh, you'd have to put it
on your fuckin' Facebook,
likely.
Over and out.
(THUD)
TANIS: Look at this
bowl of fruit salad.
You want a taste, Tanis?
Ooh, better watch
that bark there.
Boy might get bit.
(BARKING)
What's going on here?
You're looking
a handful short.
Caught a bad case
of the Native flu, or what?
You're drunk.
Mix in a water.
Well, it's either that or
you're all tweaking down
that meth town you come from.
What did you say?
Everyone knows Letterkenny
has gone to meth.
You guys a bunch of
fuckin' basics.
At least we keep it clean.
We just sell cigarettes.
Your town ain't nothing
but a bunch of jacked‐up
scab pickers.
Yeah, we'll see what you're
calling us after I bury
a couple of bar down wristers.
Half‐clapper,
top cheddar.
Biscuits top titties,
bar downskies.
Always bar downskie.
Pull out the guns.
Safetys off.
Fuckin' safety
off, boys.
A little three‐on‐oneskie?
A little three‐on‐twoskie?
Hum a high hard one.
Hit the red light district.
You won't make it that far,
slugger.
You either, champ.
Buckets off.
Center ice.
Puck drop.
Shed 'em.
AXE: Go me.
A little fuck me,
fuck you.
Free nose jobs.
Let's dance.
Let's hit the d‐floor.
My balls dangle
harder than you, boy.
(VOMITS)
(TANIS LAUGHS)
TANIS: Like I thought,
bad case of the Native flu.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Devon, we're missing $2000.
Really?
It's a devastating blow to
Menergy Spa, I know.
Hey, I'll call Stewart.
(MUMBLING)
He'll fix everything...
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Stewart?
Hey, Devon.
Hey, we're missing 2k.
Yeah, I took it
for the rave.
2k?
(STAMMERS)
I don't think
you understand.
It's going to be
a massive production.
It's gonna be
like an...
Aurora Borealis‐themed
Salvador Dali drug orgy
with shamans.
(STAMMERING) But that's a
lot of money.
No time,
I gotta go.
Wayne. Daryl.
Gailor, how are ya now?
I'm on a juice cleanse.
Haven't had a drink
in three days.
Had close to
30 shits, though.
So what's the fuss?
Well, timing's right
for your new business.
Saw it up on your
fuckin' Facebook, there.
Got a skunk sleeping
underneath us, right now.
Did you not know skunks
are immune to bee stings?
They even teach their babies
how to raid beehives.
And?
Well, they burrow up
for the winter,
and rip farts on each other
to keep warm.
No way.
Oh, yeah.
They go to mate as soon
as they leave their mom,
so you know they're
probably thinking about her
during sex.
That or their brothers
and sisters which is
even more inappropriate.
(GAIL FARTING) Oh.
There's one knocking.
Make way.
Well, pitter‐patter.
Can you take this one,
please?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Here's the deal.
Stewart's rave is eating up
all our money,
and the business is failing
without his expertise.
We simply aren't making
enough coin selling
the Native's cigarettes.
We need the meth.
Menergy Spa is never
going to happen at this rate.
I officially move to
boycott Stewart's rave,
take it off our
fuckin' Facebooks
and sabotage it.
All in favor say,
"Aye!"
EVERYONE: Aye!
It's unanimous.
How are we
going to do this?
We could put something
on our Facebooks.
We could say the Ag Hall
has asbestos.
Yes, asbestos.
Everyone hates asbestos.
Asbestos is the answer.
Okay.
Let's do that.
Maybe you don't say
asbestos anymore, though.
Okay.
Hey, Katy,
you look beautiful.
You look better.
Um.
I've come to cordially
invite you to my rave tonight.
(ANIMAL CHATTERING)
Stewart.
Fuck, greasiest skid I
ever seen.
Criss Angel mind‐freak‐
looking‐motherfucker.
What are you thinking
holding a rave at the Ag Hall?
I'm thinking I'm doing
the Agricultural Society
a huge favor.
You guys are going broke.
Tits up or not,
it's inappropriate.
Why not the Legion?
Or even upstairs
at the arena?
Or the fuckin'
youth center.
Because they're too small,
shirt‐tucker.
Be prepared, because once
this blows up they'll probably
ask me to do it quarterly.
Bi‐weekly!
Mmm‐hmm.
We'll see if it
blows up then.
It'll probably be pretty tough
to find me through the crowd.
Stage security will be
pretty tight but your name's
on the guest list,
and there's
a backstage pass
with your name on it.
I'll do my best to
make it down, Stewart.
My ass.
And just as a heads up,
it is a rave,
so there will probably be
people on drugs.
You know, MDMA.
What? There's gonna be
MDMA at the Ag Hall?
Yes, there will be MDMA
at my rave at the Ag Hall.
There will be MDMA,
DMT, PCP, LSD,
LED and probably UFC.
But I am clean
and sober.
You are spare parts,
aren't you, bud?
(CLEARS THROAT)
I truly hope
to see you there.
Watch your fuckin'
hands, skid.
Three, two...
RILEY: Fuckin' skids are
turning Letterkenny
into a gong show, buddy.
JONESY: Fucking gonger, buddy.
I'm rattled about that
meth chirp, brotein.
Fuckin' Stewart, bro.
There's fuckin' two
in that pud, hey, boys?
Put 'em away like a
winter coat, boys.
What the fuck
was that?
That was garbage.
That was fuckin' pedestrian.
All this beaking
is kiddie pool shit.
Is that what you want?
Riley, Jonesy?
Huh?
You want to get dropped off
at the splash pad
on the way home, eh?
Get mom and dad
to pick you up after
you all swim?
No running on the deck,
ya fuckin' pheasants.
Fuck!
Bag skate.
Tomorrow, 6:00 a. m.
(DOOR OPENS)
Fuckin' embarrassing!
MAN: Hey, give your balls a
tug, you tit‐fucker!
Fuck!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
You never looked so good.
You never felt so good.
I'm so proud of you, man.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
Save me a dance, Wayne.
(ANIMAL CHATTERING)
You look better.
Where's Stewart, buddy?
Where is he, bro?
Rave's canceled.
Go home.
Bullshit, buddy.
That's not what the
poster says, buddy.
I said,
it's fuckin' canceled.
Now quit your hollering
before I get cross.
DARYL: Hey.
When he give a warning,
he don't repeat it.
Yeah.
Seven of us and two of you.
It's a good time for
a donnybrook, boys.
Tilly time, boys.
What the fuck are you
pheasants doing out here?
It's 10 minutes to curfew.
You think you can dog fuck
all night and then dance?
Dog fuckin'
means no dancin'.
Get home!
It's fuckin' embarrassing.
Well, pitter‐patter.
BOTH: This isn't over.
Jinx, you owe me a Coke.
(ANIMAL CHATTERING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Christ.
McMurray.
MCMURRAY (ON PHONE):
Wayne, I've been told
the rave was a bust.
Something about an asbestos
scare or something.
No one showed up.
Sister Bonnie, though,
she's still in there.
About that dance
you were going to save her.
She'll be in a sort of golden
poppy progressive onesie.
Either way, you know,
get in there, pal.
Give 'er the guts.
Okay.
Bang the very guts
right out of her.
Okay.
Just have at her, bud, like...
The nut‐sack.
(ANIMAL CHATTERING)
Alley oop.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPITS)
This is a grotesquerie.
It's off.
We are going to make
Letterkenny
the biggest meth town
in the whole country.
I love Stewart!
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)