You're packing up
for a fishin' trip
with your pals the other day.
I loves fishin' in Kwee‐bec.
Who doesn't love fishing
in Kay‐bec?
Great fishin' in Kyu‐bec.
‐I fucking hate Quebec.
‐This guy's fuckin' Puppers.
‐Oh, I'm havin' flash snacks.
‐To what?
To last time we went fishing.
On the ride home,
I had to sit in between
a family size
of Salt'n Vinnies
and a party pack
of Dill Picklers.
Admittedly, last time, things
got a little out of whack,
when it comes to the snacks.
We deserve the flak,
but now we're back on track.
We have a new plan of attack.
Everything we pack
has to fit in this sack.
We made a snack pact.
All these have to start
with the letter "C," in fact.
A, stop rhyming. B, why "C"?
‐Well, we trieds "A."
‐Apples.
‐And we trieds "B."
‐Bananas.
But "C" gave us
many choice options.
Cookies. Crackers.
Cheese. Chocolates.
See? And then we're on to "D,"
and so forth.
‐KATY: Mmm. Love the D.
‐Pardon?
‐Why does jerky get to come?
‐It's Caribou jerky.
‐What about the nuts?
‐Corn nuts.
‐And the beer?
‐BOTH: Cold beer.
There's too much
choice in the world.
‐How do you fig, Newton?
‐Well, look at toothpaste.
It used to be
just Colgate or Crest.
Now there's
like 20 kinds of each.
‐Whitening.
‐Brightening.
‐Enlightening.
‐Goddamn right'ning.
It's goddamn frightening.
Nice work, double D's.
Oh, speaking of double D's,
Mrs. McMurray
went to the casino
with her pals the other night,
so McMurray and I
went to the rippers.
When the cat's away,
the mice will play.
Where was my invite?
Get this, one
of the stripper's names...
Tell us on the road.
Let's go fishin'.
I loves fishin' in Kwee‐bec.
Who doesn't love fishing
in Kay‐bec?
Great fishin' in Kyu‐bec.
I fuckin' hate Quebec.
Get this guy
a fuckin' Puppers.
I'll get myself a Puppers.
(DARYL SPITS)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL URINATING)
It's nice to have a break
from you guys
naming your own burps.
On the way homes, we'll be
spelling our own farts.
Hey, you pretty near need
consonants for that.
I's and T's, and some P's.
That's maybe smart.
Anywho, about the rippers...
Oh, tell us
when you get there.
There's lots of time
for telling stories
when you go fishin'.
I loves goin' fishings
in Kwee‐bec.
Who doesn't love
fishing in Kay‐bec?
It's great fishin' in Kyu‐bec.
I fuckin' hate Quebec.
Get this guy
a fuckin' Puppers.
And everybody else in it, too.
What's the problem,
poopy‐pants?
Well, for one thing,
you can never tell
what the hell they're sayin'
half the time,
that's for one thing.
Ignorance is bliss, bud.
Yeah, they should
figures it out.
Maybe you should
figure it out.
Okay, you try to name me
one good guy
that's a French guy.
You try to name it.
Go ahead and try.
I bet Corey Hart's
a pretty good guy.
I'm not sure
that he's a French guy.
DAN: You'd trust somebody's
who wears sunglasses at night?
DARYL: Name me another
French guy that's a good guy.
Go ahead and try.
Well, what's about that guy
from the alien show?
‐3rd Rock from the Sun?
‐That's the one.
‐John Lithgow?
‐Nope.
‐French Stewart?
‐Yeah, that's the one.
He's not French.
Well, his name is French.
That guy squints too much.
Well, they can take a walk,
the whole lot of 'em.
Dary, I think
there's something
much deeper at play here.
‐Can confirm.
‐What's the story?
All right, well,
so this one time...
Oh, tell us when we get there.
There's lots of time
for tellin' stories
when you're goin' fishin'.
WAYNE: Great day
for sleighin', huh, Dan?
It's a toboggan.
So, Dary, what's the story?
Which one?
I'd hear the ripper story now.
Well, I'd hear why you hate
French people so much.
Doesn't hate 'em. He loves
'em, that's the problem.
‐No, I don't.
‐Do too.
‐No, I do not.
‐Yeah, you do.
You love French gals
but hate that
they don't love you.
(EXHALES)
Dary, please explain.
Well, every time there's
a French gal I kinda like,
I have a real hard time
explaining to her
that I kinda like her
'cause she only speaks French.
And I'm not a good enough
lookin' dude
to get by on just my looks.
Aw, Dary.
Give this guy
a fuckin' Puppers.
And, if there's like,
an English gal I kinda like
but there's
a French dude around,
you know she's goin' home
with the French dude
'cause the English gals
love French dudes.
Can confirm.
And English dudes
love French gals.
Can confirm.
That's why they
can take a walk,
the whole lot of 'em.
All right, well let's hear
the ripper story, then.
‐Yeah.
‐Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
Okay, so me and McMurray
went to the rippers
the other night,
and there was this stripper
and her name was...
All‐anus Morissette.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I loves it
when they do variations
on real people's names.
Like, uh, Avril Vagine.
Nelly Furtaco.
‐Alec Baldwang.
‐(DARYL LAUGHS)
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yep,
but, but...
All‐anus Morrisette.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Sm'ellen Degenitals.
Oh, Meryl Strip.
Hannibal Licked‐her.
‐Dongie Darko.
‐Count Dracu‐load.
Oh, that's a fun one, too,
'cause it lends itself
to good costumes.
And that's just so camp.
(GIGGLING) Yeah, yeah,
but no, no, but...
All‐anus Morrisette.
‐(ALL LAUGHING)
‐(DISTANT LAUGHTER)
‐Okay, guys...
‐(GROUP LAUGHING)
(RADIO ANNOUNCER
SPEAKING FRENCH)
‐(ANNOUNCER EXCLAIMS)
‐(GROUP LAUGHING)
Who's that?
The French.
(SNORTS)
(SPITS)
(GROUP LAUGHING)
‐(COUGHING)
‐(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
‐Boys.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
What is that,
you little bitch?
What's the red stuff,
schmelts?
‐Shred the red, boys.
Less meals, all wheels.
Protein powder program.
Meal suppies.
Meal scheddie
looks like this, boys.
Breakfast, Shreddies.
Lunch, shreddie the reddies.
Dinner, spaghettis.
(STOMACHS RUMBLING)
Shit.
(BOTH SIGHING)
(BOTH FARTING)
REILLY: Only thing about
shredding the red
is a few more trips
to the shit shed, boys.
JONESY: A few more trips
to brown town, buddy.
REILLY: (STRAINING) Table
for one at the Poo‐za Hut.
JONESY: (SIGHS) Gotta let the
jerseys out of the barn, bro.
REILLY: You'll be Russian
to a state visit
with Splat‐amir Poo‐tin.
JONESY: Drown a few
brown snakes, bro.
REILLY: Couple of King Cobra
coilers, boys.
JONESY: King Kong
SHORESY:
Fuck my entire fuckin' life,
if you tit‐fuckers
light a match in here,
the whole fuckin'
barn's goin' up.
Give your balls a tug.
REILLY: Fuck you, Shoresy.
SHORESY: Fuck you, Reilly.
‐Fight me, see what happens.
‐(FARTING CONTINUES)
Yeah? What's gonna happen,
Shoresy?
Three things, I hit you,
you hit the pavement,
I jerk off on your
driver's side door handle.
JONESY: Fuck you, Shoresy.
SHORESY: Fuck you, Jonesy.
Tell your mom to top up
the cell phone she bought me
so I can FaceTime her
late night.
(FARTS)
I don't think
we can trust her.
‐Pourquoi, Roald?
‐She's got that look.
What?
You know when somebody
comes to your party
and does all your drugs,
then tells everybody
that you're the drug addict?
Sit.
Stay!
FAK‐U's mission moving forward
is hereby labeled,
"Operation Gae."
Objective?
Find a way to get Gae
back to the city,
‐as per her wishes.
‐Danke schoen.
Danke stop,
you're not even German.
‐Danke shut your mouth, Roald.
‐(GASPS)
Modus operandi,
create mailbox mayhem.
Our Operation Gae HQ is here.
During the last
gasp of daylight,
we will skulk into
our various positions here,
here, here, and here.
Then upon clown sundown,
we will wreak havoc
all over town.
We'll deposit
the contraband in my trunk
and we will dump
our load... Here.
In the Dollar Store
parking lot.
To clarify, you want
to steal mailboxes?
‐Affirmative.
‐That's a federal crime.
(LAUGHS)
‐(SCOFFS)
‐(CHUCKLES)
(SNORTS)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Are you scared?
No.
‐(THUDS)
‐Ooh!
Oh!
Ooh, ooh.
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
Best of all, Wayne et al.,
will assume the destruction
was caused
‐by Tanis and her crew again.
‐It's perfect.
Hey, maybe could urinate
in the mailboxes too,
you know.
To underline
how pissed off we are.
(LAUGHS)
Roald!
You're in FAK‐U now.
It's serious.
You're in...
Or you're out.
I acquiesce.
We are FAK‐U.
Freaks Acting Krazee United!
Give me three good reasons
why you feel you must rebel.
BOTH: I hate the world.
I hate my parents.
‐I hate myself.
‐I hate they.
FAK‐U!
ALL: FAK‐U!
(RADIO BLARING)
(GROUP LAUGHING)
(ANNOUNCER CHEERS)
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Not only are they gal hoggers,
they're louder
than a bunch of...
(STAMMERS) Goat... Goddamn
stranded seals over there.
Get this guy
a fuckin' Puppers.
I got a Puppers right there.
(GROUP LAUGHING)
Hey!
Didn't they teach you
how to pipe down in CEGEP?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
‐(DISTANT SINGING IN FRENCH)
‐(SPITS)
(SINGING CONTINUES)
Hey! He said simmers down,
so simmers down!
Why don't you go
eat some tartars,
you snails suckin'
mime lovers?
Uh...
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I don't know
what the fuck you're saying,
but turn that shit down!
I would rather
have Celine Dion.
(MUTTERING IN FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(GROUP SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
What do they say
about arguing with idiots?
They'll drag you
down to their level
and beat you with experience.
Over and out.
I can be helpful here, fellas.
No we... We got this.
We got this.
I still don't know
what the fuck you're saying,
but you're saying it now
in a hostile tone.
And youse don't speak to us
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
I still don't know
what the fuck you're saying,
but other than
Georges St‐Pierre,
every Frenchman
is a fuckin' pussy!
So youse better simmer down
and I mean right now!
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Well, why don't you go
to a poutine festival
in the Thetford Mines?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Why don't you go canoe
in the three rivers,
you inbred fur traders?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Go eat a Nanaimo Bar
in Kamloops...
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I fuckin' know
what that means.
I love Nanaimo Bars.
‐'Cause you do pot.
‐Yeah.
Then why don't you go
savagely force feed a duck
and then enjoy your foie gras
in a sugar shack, Trudeau?
(GROUP GASPING)
Why don't you go
snowshoe into the Bell Centre
to watch back‐to‐back
sold‐out Simple Plan shows,
then go eat some
Montreal smoked meat,
you bagel‐munching,
rope pissers?
(SNOWMOBILE APPROACHING)
Anik!
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH) Pfft.
‐(LAUGHS)
‐(SPEAKING FRENCH) Pfft.
No, you're a cock on a vine!
You know what, Dan? Sit down.
You know, this one's off
the beaten path a wee bit,
but do you ever notice
how French people
go "pfft" at the end
of a sentence?
Yeah. Yeah, I noticed that.
French people
do that all the time.
They end a sentence
and they go "pfft."
I don't knows if I follows.
Well, like if you
were an English person
going "pfft" at the end
of a sentence,
like French people go "pfft"
at the end of the sentence,
the sentence would probably
be something like,
"You get so drunk some nights
you piss the bed,
"but other nights
you get so stoned
"you can't piss at all,
so pfft."
Yeah, or like your guy says,
"Sex isn't good anymore."
And you're like, "Well,
how do you think I feel?
"All you put into it
is your dick, pfft."
You wanna know what's kind
of fun to make fun of 'em for?
Is if right after they go
"pfft," you go...
(IMITATES)
‐Do that again.
‐(IMITATES)
So like, "You like
having casual sex
"'cause he gives
you some good,
"but at the end of the day,
he doesn't give you
"a God damn, so, pfft."
‐(IMITATING)
‐Pfft.
‐Pfft! Pfft.
‐(IMITATES)
And you know what else?
None of youse knows
where to put the S's
in your God damn sentences.
So why don't
you go get tricked
by a Just For Laughs Gags
before you have
to hold a referendum
to separate
my foot from your ass!
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Choice words, super chief.
‐(FLUSHING)
‐(BOTH SIGHING)
Now that was a big turd,
period, brother.
You gotta have
a big turd, buddy.
Sniped a penalty shit, bro.
Finally got the poo‐er play
clickin', bro.
Almost had
to foreshit the game.
Too many poo‐minute penalties.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
So what? You boys ready
to shred the red?
Shreddy the reddy, boys.
Try it for praccy.
Not sure I want
a trouser brownie,
you little bitch. Yorkie?
Not sure I'm up for smuggling
Fudgee‐Os either, Barts.
Scholtzy.
Not sure I'm up
for squishy poopies.
If it ain't yumsies
in my tumsies,
my poopies go squishies.
Pussy. Fisky.
I've been stocking nut
like Bulk Barn.
‐Boomtown!
‐In.
That's what I fuckin' love
about you, Boomtown.
Love the jam, Boomtown.
Love it!
Shred the red!
BOTH: Shred the red.
GROUP: Shred the red!
Shred the red!
ALL: Shred the red!
She is hot.
I'm pretty sure the French
word for hot is chaud.
I'd like to chaud
her something.
Why don't you invite her
to the chaise lounge, Dary?
I would...
Except I wouldn't
be able to understand
what she's saying
half the time.
And I'm not a good
enough looking guy
to get by on just my looks.
(TUTS) Aw, Dary.
Cheer up, Dary.
Despite those frogs,
whose wives can't even
take their last names.
I'm pretty sure they don't
use middle names
over there either.
No middle names? It's 2015.
No, it's not.
I loves fishin' in Kwee‐bec.
Who doesn't love fishing
in Kay‐bec?
It's great fishin in Kyu‐bec.
I fuckin' hate Quebec.
Get this guy
a fuckin' Puppers.
(SPLATTING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Pfft!
(IMITATES)
‐Pfft!
‐(IMITATES)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Well, I guess everybody
understands body language.
Anik is gone forever.
Aw, next time,
you'll know to strike
while the iron's hot,
big shooter.
I just can't catch a break.
(ROD CLICKING)
‐Oh, you got one.
‐DARYL: Oh... Hey...
(LAUGHING) Eh?
Oh, bother.
Oh! Too hot.
‐I've had a hearty, boys.
‐(FARTS)
Mudslide, budski.
‐Oh, no. I've shit my pants.
‐(FARTS)
You little bitch. Yorkie.
(FARTING)
I've cranked an eight‐ball
in my sports‐shorts.
(FARTING CONTINUES)
Scholtzy?
‐(STOMACH RUMBLES)
‐(FARTS)
Peak behind door number two to
see my little poop de Ville.
It's my little deuce poop.
Pussy.
Fisky.
(FARTS) I've had a blumpy.
A grumpy blumpy.
Boomtown?
(SNIFFS THEN SPITS)
I'm ready to get the lead out.
I'm ready to... (FARTS)
(SPLATTERING)
Wait.
I shit my pants, too.
I'm sorry.
This is on you,
you little bitch.
I'm gonna get you, schmelt!
(GRUNTS)
Cops are so dumb.
Cops are mushrooms.
I'll need you to expound, Gae.
What do you do with mushrooms?
Are we talking Portobello?
Shiitake? Chanterelles?
I can cook, you know.
You give them shit
and keep them in the dark.
Roald. Are you afflicted?
What are you...
Ow!
Roald?
Give me three reasons
why you feel you must rebel.
BOTH: I hate the world.
I hate my parents.
I hate myself!
As you were.
ALL: FAK‐U!
What a bust.
Pretty pedestrian effort,
super chieftains.
Only fish we caught
was the one
Cock Cousteau
tossed over at us.
I fuckin' hate Quebec.
Can't catch a break here.
(SNOWMOBILES APPROACHING)
Oh, bother.
Degens from up‐country.
No ostrich fuckers
in Quebec, hicks.
Well, we are way the fucks
outnumbered, bud.
It's not how many you win,
it's how many you show up for.
‐Is that a No Fear slogan?
‐Likely.
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(CONTINUES IN FRENCH)
(SNORTS AND SPITS)
Bienvenue au Quebec.
‐Your brother's hot.
‐(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Do you speak English?
Oui. Yes.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yes. Oui.
No problem. Of course.
‐(SPEAKING FRENCH)
‐Bon.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Well, it's best
to avoid a scrap
when you're goin' fishin'.
But you hate degens
from up country too, huh?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yeah?
And where exactly
is up‐country Kyu‐bec?
Laval.
My whole life,
I've hated the French.
You can't understand
what they're saying
half the fuckin' time.
And I couldn't land
one of your beautiful women
if my life depended on it.
As far as I'm concerned,
youse can take a walk,
the lot of youse.
But then youse
had our back today...
‐Yeah.
‐Oui.
I loves me fishin'
in Kwee‐bec.
Who doesn't love fishing
in Kay‐bec?
Great fishin' in Kyu‐bec.
I fuckin' love Quebec.
‐Hear, hear!
‐Cheers!
‐ANIK: Sante!
‐Merci, mes amis.
Thank you.
I'm Anik.
I'm Daryl.
I think you're really
good‐looking.
Um, I was looking at you
and I see you
look at me so, pfft.
(IMITATES)
You speak English.
Pretty much everyone
in Quebec does.
Wow.
Do you like Alanis Morissette?
(GIGGLES)
(GIGGLING CONTINUES)
Oui.
(LAUGHING)