You're having thirsty Thursday
with your pals the other day.
It was my cousin's sixth
birthday party yesterday.
‐Which cousin?
‐Samuel.
I fuckin' hate Samuel.
‐Well, Samuel likes you.
‐Fuckin' hate Samuel so much.
Well, Samuel's not so bad.
I seen Samuel in the laundry
room with the cat one time.
You just know
that little fucker's
gonna put him in the dryer.
That's a hasty conclusion.
Not if you seen
Samuel trying to put himself
in there 15 minutes earlier.
I seen Samuel snort a line of
Fun Dip on his fifth birthday.
Well, it's reason
fuckin' five million
I didn't go to his
sixth birthday party.
He was doing
a Fun Dip dry rip.
A what?
Or rippsin' a Fun Dip dry one.
Well, what's that?
Well, in schneef terms,
if you do a line of schneef
before you've ingested
any booze to
alter your judgment,
it's called doing a dry rip.
Or rippsin' a dry one.
Doin' dry rips is
a pretty good indication
you got a schneef problem.
You got yourselves
a schneef issue.
Well, yous
ever done a dry rip?
‐Well, back in the day.
‐In the glory days.
‐Yeah, I done a dry rip.
‐I'd a rips a dry one.
Not sure if rippin'
a Fun dip dry rip would
have the same effect,
but doin' it is still
a pretty good indication
you got some sort of problem.
Well, hoopin' Fun Dip
definitely wouldn't
have the same effects,
but it's
definitely an indication
you got yourselves a problem.
Well, what's hoopin'?
Well, that's instead of taking
the drugs orally's or
intranasally's, you
take 'em anally's.
What the fuck
you talking about now?
Well, instead of down
the hatch or up the nose,
you take 'em in the pooper.
Wait, you put
drugs up your pooper?
That's the fastest
way to absorbs
'em into your systems.
Do you mean like you take
the drugs with your hand...
Well, then you put
'em up your pooper?
Correct.
But you don't poop 'em out?
No, your pooper absorbs 'em.
Well, isn't that curious.
Hoopin' Fun Dip definitely
wouldn't have the same
effect as hoopin' schneef.
But doing it is still probably
a pretty good indication
you got some
sort of a problem.
I guess a Fun Dip dick dinger
wouldn't be
the ends of the world.
You wanna know what? I heard
my friends J. P. and J. W.
talk about Fun Dip
dick dingers one time.
Well, whose dick
was gettin' dinged?
Well, I thought it was
a bit intrusive to ask
whose dick was gettin' dinged.
As long as they're
both consentin' adults,
it really doesn't matter
whose dick's gettin' dinged.
Well, I really hope
the Fun Dip candy stick
isn't going
to waste in all this.
Do you wanna know what?
I pulled my first all‐nighter
with my friend Chad
in grade eight playing
Pokemans and eating Fun Dip.
Oh, waits.
If...
If Samuel's
already been takin'
Fun Dips orally's
and intranasally's...
Yeah, we should probably
go check on Samuel.
I fuckin' hate Samuel so much.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
You got any dates lined up
this week, good buddy?
Nah, I'm gonna
put that bullshit
on the back burner
for a bit, bud.
Soft, literally.
Parks 'er behind
the barn for a bits?
‐Ten‐ply.
‐No.
Gotta find Stormy a stud.
That's a priority.
She's a beautiful dog.
Oh, she's a real beauty.
No, she's a gorgeous dog.
She just tries to kill
her studs, is the thing.
Well, that's my girl.
Maybe you should takes her
in for a fingers in the bum.
Are you fuckin' preoccupied?
That's only
the answer sometimes.
Squirrelly Dan
working' Squirrelly OT.
Not all the time.
‐Just to checks.
‐Sometimes.
Are you fuckin' preoccupied?
Doesn't matter what
you takes her in for.
As sure as a bush
is gonna break your fall,
Stormy's gonna get
some fingers in the bum.
‐How deep?
‐Fuck's sake.
‐What do ya means, how deep?
‐How many knuckles?
Like how many knuckles deep?
Yeah, are we talking
about a one‐knuckler
or a two‐knuckler?
Oh, be at least
a three‐knuckler
to gets to the bottom of this.
Oh, see, now, that's too many.
Is not.
Well, a person's
got two knuckles
so you're saying that
the vet would have to
fire a three‐knuckler
up Stormy's bum
to get to the bottom of it?
A person has three knuckles.
Well, a person
has two knuckles.
‐Figure it out.
‐A person has three knuckles.
You figure it out.
A person's got
two knuckles, okay?
‐One, two.
‐Three.
You forgots about
the little knuckles
underneath the fingernails.
Well, see now, that's not
a knuckle, though, Dan.
To be a knuckle,
you gotta be able to
punch somebody with it.
You can't punch
somebody with the knuckle
underneath the
fingernail, can you?
Can too.
Well, you'll be
looking pretty fuckin' silly.
First knuckle, one knuckler.
Second knuckle, two‐knuckler.
Third knuckle, three‐knuckler.
So then by your logic
the vet would have to
fire a full
finger up Stormy's bum
‐to get to the bottom of it.
‐Correct.
See, I'm just not so
goddamn sure I can stand by
and watch the vet give Stormy
a three‐knuckler up the bum.
No, I don't think
Stormy would need
a three‐knuckler up the bum.
Well, thank you, Dary,
because then you'd think
the vet's a bit funny,
would you not?
Mmm, a person has
three knuckles, though.
Thank you, Dary.
Fuck's sake, go ahead
and have a fuckin' fight
with your first knuckle then.
KATY: You'll be lookin'
pretty fuckin' silly.
Yeah, but when we're
talkin' about a two‐knuckler,
we're talking about
horizontal knuckles.
I'm gonna stop you there.
By your logic,
a six‐knuckler can be dealt
with using these two fingers?
‐Correct.
‐Incorrect.
No such thing
as a six‐knuckler.
A six‐knuckler existed,
I'd know about it.
‐How are ya now, Gail?
‐Good, and you?
‐Not so bad.
‐Got a stud for Stormy.
Comes from the
Baumgartner breeders.
Name's Ken.
‐Ken Baumgartner?
‐Yeah.
Okay.
You're not exposed
to give dogs human names.
‐Can do what I want.
‐Well, sure you can,
I'm just sayin'
you're not exposed to.
Baumgartner's been
breeding German Shepherds
out in Chemmy for six years.
Champion bloodlines. Elegance.
Strength.
Raw food diet.
‐You got him in the truck?
‐Yeah.
Well, pull around back.
See if they'll have a go.
Okay.
Hey, Dan.
Do you wanna know how
I know about a six‐knuckler?
Okay.
Reilly. Jonesy.
You guys been
gettin' a lot of ice time?
‐Well, actually...
‐(MUMBLING)
I'm just kiddin'.
I don't give a fuck.
I stepped down from
your old junior team.
Turns out the senior team
needed a new bench boss.
Real work to be done here.
Real men.
Turns out you guys
have been havin'
a bit of a cake walk up here,
huh?
Is that right, Reilly?
Eh, a little angel cake?
A little angel food cake
with a top glaze? Huh?
Have your mom
mix up the egg whites
and the vanilla?
Huh? Have your mom cut it with
a knife or a small spatula
through the batter releasing
air bubbles and bake?
Light as air? Huh?
Virtually fat‐free?
Fuck you, pheasant!
Come on, man...
Oh, Jonesy's
got something to say.
What kind of
cake are you walkin', huh?
A little Lady Baltimore? Huh?
A little date and walnut loaf?
A little Napoleonshatte?
Coach, it's not that we're...
Cake walk's over, all right,
Johnny Cheechoo
and Chuck Huddy?
Gonna have the boys tossing up
sueys up
the middle all night,
just tossing up
hot suey sauce?
You know why?
(YELLS) 'Cause you've
been skipped leg day?
You think you can skirt legs
and crack the Czech Extraliga?
Huh? You couldn't even crack
the HockeyAllsvenska,
let alone the
Deutsche Eishockey Liga!
Fuck!
You plugs are
gonna learn some jam.
It is fuckin' embarrassing!
I'm sick of
playing' hurt, buddy.
Are you hurt or
are you injured, buddy?
This time it's different.
My feelings are hurt.
No, feelings are injured, bro.
I wanna dust on praccy.
No praccy means
no game, buddy.
I know.
I wanna dust on praccy, too.
What do we do?
Crush a couple sandos?
I don't think I could
crush a sando right now.
But you love
crushin' sandos, bro.
I know.
I'm fuckin' terrified.
Me too.
Hey. Hey.
It's okay.
(WHIMPERS) Thanks, buddy.
(HIP‐HOP SONG PLAYING)
I'm here for a normal reason.
(WHISPERS)
Okay, but sure it's this?
Yeah, it's all cued up.
‐And this is their best song?
‐It is.
Well, it's the one he knows.
Oh.
‐If it fails, it's on you.
‐What?
Hey, we got, uh...
We got Digable Planets
all cued up for you, Stewart.
I'm more into
Shabazz Palaces right now.
(MOUTHING)
Uh, we don't have them.
What about Busdriver?
Milo?
Open Mike Eagle?
You love those guys. Hmm?
Have any Freddie Gibbs?
Vince Staples?
It's darker.
(STAMMERS)
‐Young Thug?
‐(SCOFFS)
Don't act like anyone knows
what he's saying, Devon.
(MOUTHING)
I've got an idea.
Danny Brown.
(SIGHS)
Cue it up.
Cue it up. Cue it up.
Okay.
(HUMMING NERVOUSLY)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
This gets worse
before it gets better, cowboy.
Did she...
Stormy tried to
kill Ken Baumgartner.
Well, that's my girl.
The Baumgartners aren't gonna
be too jazzed about this.
Guess we could
try his brother Nolan.
‐Nolan Baumgartner?
‐Yeah.
‐Okay.
‐No more Baumgartners.
It's not the Baumgartners.
It's Stormy.
‐Fuckin' shithead!
‐Gail...
She's a shithead and I'll
fuckin' say it to her face.
I'll say it to
fuckin' your face.
Fuckin' rip open her face,
take out her eye sockets,
get right in there and tell it
to her fuckin' frontal lobe.
Fuck! Fuck!
It's too nice
a day to get cross.
You should try a sedative.
What?
Are you kiddin' me?
God. Oh, my.
Oh, this is what
we were talkin' about
in my women's
studies class right here.
Let's have a fuckin'
field day with this bullshit,
that's for goddamn sure.
Fuckin' patriarchy.
Professor Tricia
would literally shit a brick!
‐What's wrong with you?
‐I'm very upset.
Sort yourself out.
Gail just said
she wants to roofie Stormy.
‐No, I didn't.
‐Doesn't sound like she did.
If you want to
give Stormy drugs
to the point of impairments
so that Ken Baumgartners can
have his filthy sex with her,
‐well, then, that is...
‐KATY: Don't say it.
We get it.
What about Nolan Baumgartner?
Okay, you think
I wanna carpet Stormy?
Yeah. Sounds to me
like you wants to rope her.
What the actual fuck
are you two talkin' about?
Carpet and rope
are slang for roofies.
Every drug has, like,
a million different words.
‐Name one.
‐Marijuana.
‐Dutch.
‐Keef.
‐Dank.
‐Assassin of youth.
‐K.
‐Name another.
‐Cocaine.
‐Uptown.
‐Nose beers.
‐Booger sugar.
‐Stripper salt.
‐Outstanding.
‐Name another.
‐No, I get it.
MDMA. And don't say Molly.
‐Who's that?
‐Bombers.
‐Hug drug.
‐Mmm, little fellows.
E‐Baums world. Mushrooms.
‐Zoomers.
‐Boomers.
Cracker stackers.
‐Simple Simon.
‐(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Better not call me
Simple Simon,
I'll tell you where to go.
Fuck, yeah.
I've got another
stud for Stormy.
Fuck you.
Give me half hour.
Well, I'll go run 'er.
Might help.
Little exercise.
Discipline and
affection in that order.
Hey, Dan, do you
know another name for
Ecstasy is Dancin' Shoes?
'Cause it makes me
wanna dance.
Makes me wanna hug.
I get real huggy
when I'm on the ecstasy's.
Ecstasy bear.
Somethin' about
that drug, you know.
You just wanna
reach around and
enjoy the tactile sensations
that make up
this fabulous world.
Wide worldy bear.
Yeah, just...
Just wanna hold people.
(SLURPS)
Okay, how can I help?
‐Rock bottom, boys.
‐Rock bottom, ferda.
Ferda.
Boys, do you know
I think that there is a reason
why you found me.
Well, yeah, I mean,
you were waiting for us.
Kinda right by the door.
Okay, I think
there's a reason...
(WHISTLES)
...that y'all found me, okay?
You found me
because you need guidance.
You're... You're lost.
Nowhere to turn.
And do you know what I say to
those who need guidance?
Do you know what
I say to those who are lost?
Who have nowhere to turn?
I say turn to him.
‐Turn to who?
‐God.
Can't we just
talk to you, buddy?
Yeah. Talk to God.
Why do we have to talk to God?
Why can't we just talk to you?
‐You're right here.
‐Well, I...
I understand but we're
all saying the same thing.
I'm here, I'm the one.
I'm a conduit.
I'm the one that...
I'm the messenger that...
Talk to me.
I'm your
spiritual counselor, okay?
‐You can talk to me.
‐Thanks, buddy.
‐Sick, buddy.
‐All right.
So, I think to get to
the root of your problem
we need to figure out here,
together, where did it begin?
‐Sick, buddy.
‐Sick.
‐Boys, where did it all begin?
‐What?
‐Oh, do you mean when?
‐No.
Yes, actually. Yes.
‐Thanks.
‐Surprise.
When, when
did the problem start?
Oh, um... When...
‐When we lost...
‐She we do not speak of.
‐Ooh, Katy?
‐No.
Yes. Just,
we do not speak of her.
Then, yes, but, buddy,
we're talking
about her right now so...
We're speaking
of her to try to make it
so she isn't "she we
do not speak about" anymore.
Yeah, I know, but is
that even okay, buddy?
Oh, my God. Yes. It's fine.
It's fine. It's okay.
It's okay.
I want you to
think about this.
I want you to hear this and
I want you to think about it.
I want you to think about
how many fish
there are in the sea,
'cause there's a lot of them.
A lot of fish in the sea and
there's a lot of fish on menus
and most often
good restaurants
have a lot of fish on them.
And I want you to think,
"Look at this menu.
"Have I tried all this fish?
"Have I thought,
do I want fish?
"Oh, what's this?
Oh, this is a shellfish.
"That looks like calamari,
I wanna try that."
Oh, you mean like
our big city slams?
I guess we could call up
our big city slams, bro.
I didn't... I didn't mean
that at all, but fine.
Do whatever you want.
‐Big city slams, ferda.
‐Ferda!
Hey, it's never gonna
make sense to me.
Where are you going?
He has the car.
See? I told you.
It's his...
(SIGHS)
Worth it.
(COUGHS)
I gagged.
‐Gail, how are ya now?
‐Good, and you?
‐Not so bad.
‐(BURPS AND FARTS)
You gotta rich inner life.
Boy, howdy.
Got another stud for Stormy.
Comes from the
Buchburger breeders.
Name's Kelly.
‐Kelly Buchburger?
‐Yeah.
Okay.
The Buchburgers have been
breedin' German Shepherds
out in Arva for 16 years.
They're outgoin'. Strong.
And heavy‐boned.
‐WAYNE: So he's in the truck?
‐Yeah.
Well, pull around back,
we'll see if
they'll have a go.
Gotta say, Wayne,
if it doesn't work out
with Kelly Buchburger,
you're approaching
the bottom of the well.
Oh, bother.
I was sure you had
a winner in Ken Baumgartner.
You could always use his
brother, Nolan Baumgartner.
If you don't want to sedate...
I've had just abouts
enough of that talks, Gail.
If you're past a knuckle
or two up the bum.
It'd take three knuckles to
gets to the bottom of this.
I'd say Stormy's
just not fit for breedin'.
But she's a beautiful dog.
‐She's such a beautiful dog.
‐A real beauty.
She's a gorgeous dog.
Yeah, but she keeps
on tryin' to kill her studs.
Well...
Pitter‐Patter.
My Instagram
is just blowing up.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh! Yes, Katy.
To be clear, I wanna sign you.
So you're
gonna call me, right,
even if it's just to talk?
I am gonna lay
everything out for you.
All your pretty options.
We're gonna start
with a tour of the office.
Maybe a low‐cal lunch.
But you have
to come to the city.
I really can't do anything
here in Letterkenny.
So you're
gonna call me, right?
‐Yes.
‐Awesome. Cool.
‐Talk soon. Okay?
‐Okay.
Hey, Katy‐Kat?
‐Hey, Katy?
‐(CHUCKLES)
Big city slams, boys.
‐Gail, how are ya now?
‐Good, and you?
Not so bad.
Got the perfect
stud for Stormy.
My cousin up in Tobermory
will be here with him later.
This dog is different.
Strong, silent type.
Hard worker. No bullshit.
‐Fuck, I'd do him.
‐Sounds like a good guy.
Sounds like a real good guy.
Probably a real good guy.
‐This is the one, cowboy.
‐Okay.
You can trust this old goat.
So your cousin's coming up
later with the stud?
Yeah.
What are we
gonna do till then?
Ah, you're fuckin'
lookin' at it, super chief.
Well, you know,
back in the day...
Back in the glory days.
We'd hoover some schneef.
You wanna know what?
I feel like
yous been working
your way towards this
for about six weeks.
It's been a long, long time
since I've
hoovered some schneef.
'Cause you were a fuckin'
degen when you did, Dan.
‐I was skinny.
‐And here's another thing.
You shouldn't
call it "schneef" anymore.
I think you
should call it "schniff."
‐Why?
‐'Cause it's funnier.
I think.
It's kinda like
that word "queef."
See, you can have a lot
of fun with that word queef.
But what's funnier, well,
I think, is the word "quiff."
I could hoover
a bit of schneef.
Schniff.
You ever hoovered
backseat schneef?
Schniff!
I've hoovered
schneef off of the headrest
of a Pontiac Tracer
traveling to SARSfest.
Ever hoovered
backstage schneef?
I've hoovered schneef off of
Jann Arden's
charcuterie board.
I'd have a beer.
You ever
hoovered boat schneef?
WAYNE: Schniff!
I've hoovered schneef off of
Theodore Tugboat's
baseball cap.
I got the NES out for you.
What happened to the 64?
Six hours Mario Kart.
Six hours Diddy Kong Racing.
Have I been
sleeping that long?
He did melatonin dry rips.
You did melatonin dry rips?
‐Did you play GoldenEye?
‐Pointless.
Everyone has the
multi‐player maps memorized.
‐What's on NES?
‐We beat Mario 1.
Almost done Mario 3.
What about Mario 2?
(BOTH GASP)
‐That's it?
‐Desist?
You are amiss.
Super Mario Brothers 2?
What kind of
dismantled, bemused,
lugubrious motherfucker
wants to play that, Stewart?
‐I'm sad, Devon.
‐I know.
Do what you must.
I will.
We will.
‐You will?
‐Mmm‐hmm.
We need you back
at one hundred.
One hunnid.
Zero to one hunnid?
Real quick.
So?
We will get her back.
Roald?
That better be the duck
hunter gun in your pocket.
It's called an NES zapper.
But, no.
(GIGGLING)
I miss Katy, buddy.
I miss Katy‐Kat
in a big way, buddy.
Where have
you been for the past
four and a half minutes, boys?
Gettin' blowies.
I just got
a squeezer, but still.
‐Ferda.
‐Okay, boys.
If I'm Katy,
I don't wanna date you.
‐Bro.
Just saying.
And if I'm Wayne...
(LAUGHS) I don't...
I don't want
you dating my sister.
I think I know
what he means, buddy.
‐But ya don't.
‐I think I get it, bro.
You definitely don't.
We need to go through
Wayne to get to Katy.
Okay, I can work with that.
Maybe we're on to something.
We need to beat the shit
out of Wayne to get to Katy?
Okay, you don't.
You lost me again.
Beat the shit outta Wayne,
ferda Katy‐Kat.
Ferda Katy‐Kat.
(BOTH YELL)
And...
None of it,
none of it makes sense.
Lord, I tried.
I tried. Lord.
Lord knows I tried!
Ah, there will be
no peace in Letterkenny.
No, sir.
Satan has secured his estate.
Thousands below
the asking price.
Our Father, who art in heaven.
Hallowed by Thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread.
And forgive us our debts
as we forgive our debtors.
And lead us
not unto temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For Thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory,
forever and ever.
Amen.
DARYL: You ever hoovered
police station schneef?
I've hoovered schneef off
a sergeant constable's
nightstick.
You should call it schniff.
Ever hoovered airport schneef?
I've hoovered schneef off
a Drakkar Noir display
at the hors taxes.
Well, suit yourselves.
My cousin should
be here any minute.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
It's fuckin' tilly time, boys!
Go time!
Go grab a rake and tidy
that gravel you've upset.
Are you fuckin' deaf, hick?
Let's have a donnybrook!
That tone's unhelpful.
(GRUNTING)
‐Tarps off?
‐Sheddin' the tarp.
Now, as I recall, that's
your ritual before a fight,
and my patience
is wearing thin, so I'll ask.
Are you fuckin' high?
‐No.
We want Katy back.
We'll go through you
to get her.
Unnecessary
as of five minutes ago
but as of right this second,
you should make sure
your shoelaces are tight.
DAN: Bye, Katy.
What does that have
to do with anything?
What?
Air!
Ramped!
Fire!
I've come to
reclaim the Lady Katy.
Fuck you, pheasant!
We've been waitin' a long
time to fight you, pheasy?
We're ready to defend.
So there's a line? If so...
I'm budgin'.
We should breakdance fight.
It's safer. And I'll win.
Too much talkin'.
Shall we?
Oh, shit, I actually do
need to tie my shoelaces.
What the fuck?
Let's get at it!
(ROMANTIC SONG PLAYING)
Wayne, this is my cousin.
What's your
cousin's name, Gail?
‐Rosie.
‐Rosie, how are ya now?
‐Good, and you?
‐I'm not so bad.
Should I pull around back
and see if they'll have a go?
Couldn't have
said it better myself.
Pitter‐Patter.
‐Wayne?
‐Yeah?
‐I want you back.
‐Oh.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
‐Wayne.
‐Yeah?
‐I'm pregnant.
‐Oh.
Oh, fuck.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)