Got a bit banged up after work
the other day...
Did you get that stump
out of the ground today?
I already told you.
Dary and I are
doing it Friday.
You never told me that.
Did too.
You gotta tell her
more than once.
She's a woman, not a robot.
In all fairness, Dary,
that's a two‐way street.
(DAN FARTS)
You know what Dad would say...
Plant the corn. Get her goin'.
So, how are you
gonna do it?
Well, Questions McGarrity over
here, we chain it up and yank
it out like a loose tooth.
(DAN FARTS)
So, what are you
gonna chain it up to?
My van.
WAYNE: Won't do.
DARYL: Why?
'Cause that might be a little
too punk rock, Dary.
What's wrong with my van?
More than a coat of paint.
Go on.
More than
two coats of paint.
Get after it.
Rear end differential.
Front end differential.
Alternator. Battery.
Doesn't matter.
She'll perform.
Well, fucking measure twice,
cut once then, bud.
You said yesterday,
it could win
a demolition derby.
No I never.
I said yesterday it was fit
for a demolition derby.
No you never.
Ain't no reason
to get excited.
It's not what you said.
You better settle down
over there
or I'm gonna come
talk to you...
You know what, there's two
things I don't like about you,
and it's your face.
There's one thing
you're not gonna like about
your own face.
That's when I come over there
and give it the beats.
You boys ever had
a peanut butter sandwich?
You're one end.
You're the other end.
Stick you's together and
you're just stuck.
Really scraping the bottom
of the yoghurt cup for that
nugget of wisdom, aren't you?
You appreciate
my metaphors, Katy.
That's what I appreciate
about you.
Is that what you appreciate
about me?
Stake about five to 10% offer
over there squarely down.
Yeah. No. Huh?
So any other insights for us?
Uh...
(DAN FARTS AGAIN)
Heck! You wouldn't mind
a quick heads up from a fella
who's about
to steam press his Calvins.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
And that's your lesson
for today, folks,
farts always win.
That right there
was an air biscuit.
That was a real ass flapper,
if I do say so, myself.
Some fine colon bowling.
Some real rectal turbulence.
Wayne, you gonna
weigh in on this?
Well there's nothing
better than a fart.
Except kids falling off
bikes maybe. Fuck, I could
watch kids fall off bikes
all day.
I don't give a shit
about your kids.
I wish Gail could hear
that fart.
I've got a couple pals who'd
appreciates it too.
Wouldn't it be kinda neat
if you could like,
catalog your farts?
What for?
Well, I feel like
if other people could hear
that crack splitter
it could have
a positive impact
on their lives.
That may be the nicest thing
everybody has ever
said about me.
You should be able to
keep track of and record
your farts.
And your friends' farts.
Like Facebook?
Exactly like a Facebook.
Just like...
MEN: Fartbook.
(DAN FARTS)
Step one, we got to
builds us a website.
How are we gonna
fuck that pig?
I guess we gots
to calls up
the internets.
Oh, yeah? You got a phone
number for the internet, Dan?
Well, I'm pretty sure they
added me on Skypes
a while back,
I mean, I gots to check
my emails.
Outstanding.
Well, I have an idea,
it's gonna chap a few asses
but,
there's a fella we know
right here in town who can
builds us a websites
so we don't even have
to calls up the internets,
you know.
Skip that middle man.
Right, we'll skip
the middle man.
Who is... The internet.
Who is it, Dan?
Um, Stewart.
Hard no.
You gots a better idea?
Better than going into
business with a meth head?
One or two.
Now hold your good goddamn
horses here, let's put it
to a vote, those for...
Those against...
Get real.
Then she's bought
and paid for.
Two against one.
So, driving Pete's family's
out of town, he had a bit
of a Texas Hold'em Tournament.
And I went over there
with my second‐cousins.
Who, Garrett?
And Jarrett.
Well, Pete gets all
liquored up. Long story short,
me and the cousins,
just standing there
in the kitchen
having a beer watching
Pete hang a piss
down his own basement stairs.
Then he turns the cock on
himself, pisses all over
his goddamn chest.
Then he falls down his own
piss‐soaked stairs.
What are you gonna do?
It's like, "Hey, it's your
fucking house!"
But also, "Fuck!
It's your house."
(STEWART CLEARS THROAT)
So it's Facebook...
But for farts?
That's right.
Cartoonish. We're in.
But, drop the "The."
Just, Fartbook.
It's cleaner.
There was never a "The."
And we want 30%.
Of what?
Amateurs.
Money, generated from
the site!
We are not gonna
be making any money
off the site.
Yes, we will.
Once we get enough members
playing the butt trumpet,
we will sell ad space
and make a fortune.
Now, let's talk about
marketing.
Who should we target to buy
ad space on Fartbook?
Indian food. Greek food.
Asian noodle soups.
What about ring tones?
Instead of putting
your phone on silent,
you put in on silent...
But deadly.
You are an idiot.
He's a...
Wait.
You're an idiot.
Is geo‐stamping farts
a good idea?
Of course it is.
Popcorn, fart location,
movie theater.
That's information
I's wants to know!
No.
Why not?
'Cause it's too complicated.
It's like algebra.
Why you gotta put numbers
and letters together?
Why can't you just go
fuck yourself?
The kids will fucking
love that shit.
Yeah, you know what else
kids love, keys.
(KEYS JINGLING)
Dangling in front
of their faces.
They fucking love it.
Fine.
No ads then.
Shake on 30%.
Anything down the road
will be negotiated
in good faith.
Beggars can't
be choosers.
(GRUNTING)
Meritorious!
Give us...24 hours.
Eduardo.
We're ranking farts.
I need the algorithm.
How are you now?
Hey.
Not too bad.
Good, and you?
Huh?
Oh.
Gentlemen.
Fartbook.
DARYL: I don't...
I... I just...
What's wrong with you?
Seeing it all come together...
Sort yourself out.
Here's what we've done.
I am, at this point,
the only member
of Fartbook.
Each member will be able to
upload three farts.
Each member will post
a picture to their farts.
Members will then be allowed
to friend request each other
and accumulate audiences for
their farts.
For example...
(IMITATING DRUM ROLL)
My profile.
(FART RECORDINGS PLAYING)
WAYNE: Wanna know, that's...
That's mint.
Like the...
Little bull snort there
in the middle there, Stewart.
I really like the placement
of the fizzler at the end.
Thank you.
Now, shall we sign
one of you up?
Oh!
Me. Me. Me. Me. Me. Me. Me.
Me. Me. Me. Me.
Me. Me. Me. Me...
Daryl.
Oh, fuck. Shit. Cunt. Fuck...
Wait a sec. Can I go eat a can
of Chef Boyardee?
Oh! No times.
I can farts on command.
(CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTING)
Okay?
Mmm‐mmm.
DAN: Ready.
Ahem, I recommend recording
through a professional
studio mic
but the internal
computer mic
will work for now.
Okay, Dan.
STEWART: Ready?
Go.
(DAN FARTING)
Oh, very nice.
Boy howdy.
Onto the second one.
STEWART: Go.
(DAN FARTING)
That was a winner.
DARYL: Really nice work, Dan.
Really nice work, Dan.
Fuck, is this awkward.
Onto number three.
(GRUNTS)
(SHORT FART)
No, no, no.
I can do better.
I wants to go again.
No, I think you should
keep it.
DARYL: No one likes a fart
that sounds too staged.
Do you wanna know what?
He's right.
Like that person who just
happens to have burst out
laughing in every group photo
they're in?
Like the camera just happened
to catch that magic moment
in every single one.
That like, "Say cheese."
You're not fooling me, bud.
Nope.
If you think, if you think
it's a good idea...
It's a good spread there.
Like...
It's a good spread.
STEWART: I suggest we, um,
send it out
to a test audience,
before it goes live.
Um...
Get some feedback.
Iron out the bugs.
Suggestions?
Gail. Duh...
What about the Ginger?
Mmm...
What about Boots?
Oh, mmm, the Ginger...
You guys...
Ever heard anything about
that guy fucking an ostrich?
I heard it was Boots who
fucked the ostrich.
No.
The Ginger
fucked an ostrich.
Allegedly.
Let's see...
It'd take more than one guy
to fuck an ostrich.
You think they were
both there?
Like, Boots held down
the ostrich?
WAYNE: I suppose...
If you really wanted to get
to the bottom of it...
We could find someone,
someone who farms ostriches.
Who might know
how they get fucked.
I don't think we need
to invite them, though.
We should get the hockey
players in on this.
Those d‐gens would lap
this right up.
Maybe get Glen.
Get the Christians on board.
Agreed. And we should also get
Katy into the fracas.
I'll talk to her.
The fuck you will.
Wondrous.
You talk to her, then.
We reconvene back here
in 24 hours.
(FARTING SOUNDS)
Yeah...
(GROANING)
(FARTS)
(FARTING CONTINUES)
Oh, yes.
(FARTING)
Go.
(FART RECORDINGS PLAYING)
(CAT FARTING)
Hey, has Katy liked
any of your farts on Fartbook?
No, you?
Huh.
No. Huh.
(BOTH PANTING)
We got a problem.
We need to talk to Gail.
(GRUNTING) Gail.
How are you now?
Good and you?
Not so bad.
Gail, we've summoned
you here today to talk
about your Fartbook profile.
Okay.
Let's listen.
(FART RECORDINGS PLAYING)
Everything about that
so right.
Wrong.
You've attached messages
to each of your farts.
For example,
send this fart to ten people
or you will have bad sex
for the rest of your life.
But see, I had just got that
message from someone else.
So it's like, if I didn't
send it, then I'd be stuck
having bad shaboink forever.
And I enjoy a horizontal
refreshment for my
vertical smile
too goddamn much
to take that risk.
It's called spamming, Gail.
Never heard it called that.
Heard it called spunking
one or two times...
No. Sending annoying messages
to people
who have not requested it
is called spamming.
Okay.
And it's annoying.
No. No. No.
Yes. Yes.
If you continue
to misuse Fartbook,
we'll have
to suspend
your membership.
Suspend my membership?
Why don't you suspend
my fist in your ass,
you little fuck.
If you ever threaten me
like that again,
I'll spread your cheeks
and I'll feed you
a Kentucky Klondike Bar,
you little twat.
I'll drop an Alabama Hot
Pocket in your
deuce maker, Charlie.
I'll fuckin' land shark your
shit house so fast
you'll be crying
for your mother,
you fucking asshole.
GAIL: Fuck you, Stewart.
You drop deuces in every
orifice of your body,
you fuckhead!
Tear you into a Pop‐Tart!
GAIL: And then I will...
We've got another problem.
STEWART: Where's Katy?
What?
STEWART: Katy.
We've summoned you here today
to talk about your
Fartbook profile.
Super.
Let's listen.
(FART RECORDINGS PLAYING)
Problem?
Those are cat farts.
Right.
You've got a picture of your
cat under each of your farts.
It's not my cat.
It's just a barn cat.
I seen a coon having sex
with a barn cat on top
of my truck one time, fuck.
What's the nature of
that, David Suzuki?
No one cares
about your
cat's farts.
But look how cute they are.
Not to be impolite,
but you're the only one
who thinks so.
Everybody whose
got a cat or a kid,
is going to think their cat's
or kid's farts are
super special and unique.
They're not.
They are just a cat
or a kid fart.
In addition, you've been
updating new farts
from your cat almost hourly.
Oh, that's because there's
so many cute farts.
Like I can't even keep up.
(HIP‐HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
JONESY: Katy! What
is this fucking gong show?
We're supposed to be napping
right now, boys.
What?
We are at home.
In the middle of
a 'Chel tournament
with big dingers in...
When we see you've been liking
all this duster's farts
on Fartbook.
And none of this
beauty's farts.
And not one
of this grain fed,
USDA certified,
100% non‐animal
tested, organic beauty.
Not one.
You're welcome.
Thanks, buddy.
So?
So he's gonna think
you wanna fucking wheel him.
He's gonna think that
you wanna turn on the jets.
Because I like
his farts?
Yes.
I'm just pushing a button.
It doesn't mean anything.
What the fuck
are you looking at,
you fuckin' pilon?
Fucking vampire...
Pipe down, idiots.
Get in the house.
Now.
(GROWLS)
I'm gonna get you,
you fuckin' pheasant!
We're comin' phezzy!
(CHUCKLES)
Guys.
Boy, you're havin'
quite a day, Super‐chief.
(SIGHS)
We've got
another problem.
Where's Glen?
Daryl, Rage Monkeys.
Daniel. Wayne.
We've summoned you
here today to talk to you
about your Fartbook profile.
Allons‐y.
You have no photos
and no farts
but are friends
with everyone along
for the test drive.
Hmm. I'm not friends
with everyone.
I'm not friends
with Wayne yet.
But I wanna be.
It seems as though
you were just cruising
through Fartbook
liking and commenting
on everyone's farts but
contributing nothing yourself.
(WHISPERS) Nothing.
I am as God made me.
Blessed with a very healthy
gastro‐intestinal system.
Not super farty.
What you're doing
is called creeping.
Not what Fartbook
is all about.
I genuinely enjoy farts.
You can't just go around
creeping other people's farts.
What the truck
is wrong with that?
If you continue
to misuse Fartbook,
we'll have to suspend
your membership.
Fine. Fine.
Fluff you then.
I have millions...
(CHUCKLES) And I mean,
millions of ways
of hearing unlimited farts.
We're done here, Glen.
Are we though?
Are we?
I think we should
pump the brakes on Fartbook.
That's a Texas‐size 10‐4.
Why?
It's kicking up
too much dust.
We haven't even gotten into it
and already folks
are gettin' chapped asses.
Well, that's their problem.
Not ours.
This is our problem.
We started Fartbook so that
good folks could share farts
with other good folks.
That's it.
Not to creepin' farts,
or spam farts...
Although, if you eat spam,
you'll get good farts.
Farts should never come
between the love of a man
and a woman.
It's not right.
You don't get
to 500 million farts
without making a few sharts.
Exactly.
So, what are you saying?
Fartbook dies today.
Today, Fartbook is dead.
Oh. You think so?
I'm with the fellas
on this one.
It's not why
we invented it.
(SCOFFS)
You invented it?
Our idea.
We built the site.
You know, you really
don't need a forensics team
to get to the bottom of this.
If you were
the inventors of Fartbook,
you'd have invented Fartbook.
Hold your horses there.
Let's put this to a vote.
Those for closing down
Fartbook, raise your hands.
Those against?
But we own 30 percent.
This isn't fair!
(YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
If you want
to sit on our backs
and call yourselves tall,
you have every right to do so.
But don't think that
we're gonna sit here and
enjoy listening to you lie.
You have a bit
of our attention,
you have the smallest bit
of our attention.
When did we ask
for your attention?
The rest of our attention
is back at the offices
of Fartbook,
where my friends
and I are doing things
that no one on this farm,
especially and including
you idiots,
are intellectually,
creatively, artistically,
emotionally, or spiritually
capable of doing.
Have I adequately answered
your condescending question?
What question?
(SCREAMS) Farts!
You better lawyer up, asshole,
because I'm not
coming back
for 30 percent,
I'm coming back
for everything.
I...
I don't know
what happened just now.
(WHIMPERING)
(WHISPERING)
No... No...
DAN: You know, I've been
thinking about Fartbook...
What about it, bigshits?
DAN: I think maybe
we pulled the cord too quick
on that, you parachute.
I miss it too,
three‐point shoes.
I was on there a lot.
Too much, likely.
I was always checking it.
It was very addicting.
Except, did you ever really
stop to think about one thing,
did you?
Rippin' farts
into your computer
doesn't exactly
spike the likelihood
of having sex with girls.
STEWART: Hey!
(BOTH PANTING)
Hey! Hey!
Not now. Need 20 minutes.
STEWART: Okay.
Just wanted to let you know
that Glen stole our website.
It's been live
for more than 36 hours.
Hey! Hey! Fuck it!
WAYNE: (EXCLAIMS)
Oh! Fuck's sake.
Jesus!
(GROANS)
Fucking sort
yourselves out.
GLEN: Cheese and rice.
I can't remember the last time
five men came in this church
so aggressively.
Or can I?
You stole our idea.
Hmm...
Are you referring
to Christian Fart Mingle?
What's that?
It's like Christian Mingle,
but for farts.
DARYL: We asked your help
with our idea
and you went behind our backs
and stole'd it.
(STUTTERING)
I didn't... Excuse...
Oh, my God.
Those are some hairy
allegations you are firing,
at my face.
All your allegations...
All of them, completely
fricken' false. Baseless.
How?
Stewart, I did not
steal anything.
Because the last time
I checked,
taking advantage
of a growing trend
was not stealing.
What trend?
I'll tell you.
But first, let's sing a hymn.
No.
Fine.
Look, y'all had
a good idea, all right?
You had a terrific idea.
Congratulations.
But did you actually think
you were the only ones
in the world to have it?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
Fart culture, Stewart.
It's all the rage.
It's everywhere.
You know...
Nothing...
Glen will show you.
Ever heard of Plenty of Farts?
I've heard of Plenty of Fish.
It's very much like that,
except for farts.
Here. Here's the one
I like the best.
It's called Fart Filter.
And I like it because you can
put different filters on all
of your farts and it's fun.
So, yeah, I'll just
show you how it works.
This one, no filter. Nothing.
(FART RECORDING PLAYING)
Who cares? Not Glen, right?
Vanilla. Pedestrian...
I'm not interested.
However, shove that baby
through the Hudson filter...
What's she gonna sound like?
(FART SCALING UPWARD)
Now there's a renovation.
Now suck on
your Sutro filter...
(DISTORTED FART RECORDING)
(EXCLAIMS)
Now boys, because
I'm feeling generous,
and we're in the Lord's house,
I'm gonna play you
the filter that
I invented myself.
I call it...
Valencia.
(FART RECORDING PLAYING)
Wow.
There is a whole site
devoted to gluten‐free farts.
The point is,
it's out there, boys.
It's happened.
The idea lives in the world.
Y'all are too slow.
Slow on the uptake.
Sad story. Boo‐hoo. Toot‐toot!
Go away.
(HOARSELY) Let's go.
GLEN: Sad face, sad face,
angry face.
(FART RECORDING PLAYING)
Better slow down there,
Big‐shoots.
Tomorrow's gonna be
a great day for hay.
If you can be a man at night,
you can be a man
in the morning.
Wayne, how come you
didn't join Fartbook?
'Cause you're not supposed
to fart in front of girls.
What?
There's certain things that
should stay sacred between
a man and a woman.
So, all things considered,
this whole thing's
pretty fucking juvenile,
if I do say so myself.
If she's always listening
to your ass acoustics,
or even worse,
smellin' 'em,
I guarantee she'll be slower
and slower to crawl into bed
with you at night.
What you just said
is outrageous.
No it isn't. It's true.
I don't wanna be smelling
a dude's ass all the time.
Get real.
What are you?
Some kind of fart purist?
So what are you
supposed to do?
Just hold it in?
Or take a shit,
you fuckin' degenerate.
Speaking of shit,
my second cousin's got IBS.
Who, Garrett?
No, Jarett.
DAN: No.
IBS, the International
Business Solution?
IBS stands for
Irritable Bowel Syndromes.
Anyhoo, when he was a kid,
Jackass comes out on the air,
so it becomes real popular
in his high school,
for kids to start taking shits
in places what weren't meant
for taking shits in.
They calls that
guerrilla shittin'.
Is this a true story?
So, he became real popular
with his friends,
with his ability to take
a shits any time he needed to.
They'd call him up
when they get an idea
of a place that needed
a shits taken in,
and be like,
"Hey, why don't you comes
over here and takes a shits?"
Anyhow, this one time
his pal texts him up,
and he says, "Hey,
why don't you come take a
shits in the girls' bathroom?"
So, he drinks a coffee,
eats a bran muffin,
heads on down
to the washroom there,
but when he opens
the bathroom door,
what does he find?
But this pretty young girl
just dropping a shits,
right there
in the middle
of the bathroom floor.
And that's how he met
his lovely Eunice.
And they fells in love,
and they've been together
ever since.
They raised
three little shits. So...
With all due respect,
Miss Katy,
there is a market
for gentlemens what can find
ladies who like, uh, farts,
or shits,
or even guerrilla shittin's.
That is not a true story.
That is a true story.
God help us all.
You know what, I don't know
why you guys need everybody
knowing your business anyway.
Like why you gotta put
everything on the internet,
while you're doing it,
or after you're done doing it?
Well, if you don't puts it
on the internet,
how's gonna people know
what you did?
Do you wanna know what?
That's your problem
right there.
Should be playing your cards
close to your chest.
Keep the ladies
guessin' a little bit.
Be the mystery man.
Right again.
Oh, if a woman's not gonna
love me for my farts
or for me posting
my bowling scores
on the internet...
Not really sure
I want one.
Well, then it's a good thing
you's two have each other.
(DAN FARTS)
(CAT FART RECORDING PLAYING)