A pack of coyotes
come right up the back porch
the other night,
'cause your dog's in heat
and you know those
fuckin' yellow eyed bastards
will go right through
the screen door
if they're horny.
(COCKS GUN)
Look like you're goin'
to a formal with that
top button done up to 11.
Oh, it's not like I'm gonna
be one of those nut sacks,
sitting around
getting sucked on
by skeeters all day.
Come off it.
Well. Pitter patter.
Let's get at 'er.
Sixty bucks per
dead coyote ain't
gonna collect itselfs.
I think I'll have
a bumper dump
before we get started.
Oh, I don't give a care.
You ever had a bumper dump?
It's not polite
to talk about.
Though I do gotta
piss goddamn bad.
When you have a dump,
leaning up against
the back of the bumper
of your machine.
So, it's pretty near
like it sounds then.
You ever have a stump hump?
You know,
I think I did, but...
I can't remember.
It's when you have sex...
With a girl?
Yeah, with a girl.
Bent over a stump of a tree.
My friend said he had sex
inside a hollowed log
one time and I thought,
"Why, I bet Fred Penner
pulled that off
one time, too."
This right here,
perfect stump
for a stump hump.
I should say.
Wayne?
Dary.
Come over here and
join me for a sec.
Oh, well fuckin'...
Like fuckin' why?
It appears somebody's
been growing marijuana
in your back bush.
You left the barn door open
after chores one time
and your dad thought
you were stoned.
But you haven't smoked
the electric lettuce
since grade eight.
That's a mitt full
of Johnny Red Eye,
all right.
I think it's only appropriate
we call the cops.
Just take about 20% off 'er
over there, mixed berry.
Don't be such a sally.
You know how much shit
needs doin' around here?
Well, shit needs
so much doin' really...
The produce stand
is a fuckin' shanty.
If we sell this stuff,
we can make thousands.
I know a guy
on the reserve.
I don't know.
Why not?
It's 'cause...
Just kidding.
We don't give a fuck.
KATY: If the cops come
around here, people will talk.
Don't want people talkin'.
Call your guy.
(SMIRKS)
STEWART: Hello, Tanis.
TANIS: You know the deal.
Personal use only.
If I hear about yous
turning around
and selling them,
and I will hear about it,
we're gonna have
a hell of a problem.
TANIS: Here's your smokes.
Dime a dart.
Buck a dart.
They're fuckin' ya.
They're fuckin' us.
I've got some photos here.
Of the goins' on.
(SIGHS)
You gonna be upset
if you keep scrolling
to the left, dog.
You gonna see some shit
that you don't wanna see.
This is a big crop.
Whoever planted it,
has done a lot
of sneaking around
and maintaining it so well.
We're busy enough
keeping the worm pickers
off the property.
There's nothing like
good outdoor grown.
It's 5k worth
and ready for harvesting.
You pull it out
of the ground,
I'll pick it up.
Cash deal.
Deal.
Who is this?
WALLY: That's Tanis,
my daughter.
Should say estranged,
I suppose.
What's so stranged
about her?
I'll tell you,
if you find
yourselves in her way,
you oughtta
swiftly get out of it.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Give me a minute.
So, how about it, boys?
Can always count on
old Katy‐Kat.
You delivered.
I'll give you that.
But what type of prick
doesn't stand up and
shake another man's hand?
About Tanis...
What about her?
I think I'm sweet on her.
Yeah? What for, Dary?
What for...
Dary, you don't
need to explain.
She makes
your dick hard,
get after it.
We'll worry
about that later.
Work on the produce stand
starts today.
Still waiting
for you to say...
Thank you.
For being a d‐jen
with a drug dealer.
Now, if you ever hit me
and I find out about it...
(GAGS)
COACH: That's good, Jonesy.
No more kids table
with the big boy moves
like that, huh?
You guys ready to play
like big boys yet, huh?
Maybe pick out
your own outfits
in the morning?
Make your own snacks?
Some solo
back to school shopping?
It's fuckin' embarrassing!
Good news is,
Pee Wee secondary team
just canceled their ice time.
I think we can make
good use of it, huh?
Suit up, pheasants.
Another hour of
the fun stuff on deck.
Might as well bring
your puke buckets with ya.
You fuckin' newbies!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey, schmelt.
What the fuck's
wrong with you?
Nothing, why?
Are you fucked up
right now?
Me?
Yes, you!
Are you on meth right now?
(WHISPERS) Oh, my God.
This is unsee 'er, bro.
Got that fuck, buddy.
If we don't fucking do it,
no one else is going to.
The writing's
on the wall, bro.
MAN: Hey, give your balls
a tug you tit fucker.
Not the right time,
Schwarzy!
How did this happen, bro?
We don't know any
dusters that do meth
and now the fuckin' rookie?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Well, we do know
Stewart and Devon
and all those skids.
But that's it, buddy.
You know, I heard
that Ginger and Boots
used to do that shit.
And look where
it got them, schmelt!
My buddy Royze had a bad
stint for a while, now that
I think about it, buddy.
But that's cause Royze was
hangin' out with Tolzy and
that guy's a fuckin' pigeon.
My buddy Parkzy too.
I guess Belzy was
fucked up for a while.
And he got Welzy into it.
Yeah, Belzy and Welzy
were doing it with Carzy
and his billet sister.
Carzy and his billet sister
got Colzy fucked up once.
Wait, isn't Colzy
still fucked up, bro?
Only when he's with
Kitzy and Burzy, bro.
Colzy is always with
Kitzy and Burzy.
Well, Colzy, Kitzy and Burzy
are always with Carzy
and his billet sister, buddy.
Who are always with
Belzy and Welzy.
Letterkenny is a meth town.
We're gonna go
see the skids.
We're gonna go.
We're gonna do it?
Do you wanna do it?
You want one?
Let's do it!
Give me one!
We're gonna have one.
Give me it.
We're going.
Let's go then!
Let's go!
Better buy all the smokes.
What is this?
This is where
I ruin your life.
Hang on...
No, no, no.
You hang on. All right?
Yous ripped me off.
And I'm fuckin' pissed.
But... (SIGHS)
We can make it right.
As un‐PC as this
market may be,
it's pretty lucrative, so...
If you sell the rest
of the cigarettes
at a buck a dart,
we get ninety cents,
you get ten.
(LAUGHS)
Deal.
No! No deal.
I spent all our
money at that rave.
You're gonna step on some
toes in any business venture.
It's inevitable.
If we want to take
this meth business
to the next level,
we cannot part with
any more coin.
Are you with me?
Always.
Let's get this over with then.
You guys wanna
dance? Let's do this.
(LAUGHING)
We can do this, too.
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Is that how
you think this works?
You just take a beating
and then we're square?
Bunch of basics.
(EXHALES)
Yous been watching
the wrong movies, boys.
Mmm‐mmm!
Pay attention.
(CLEARS THROAT)
This isn't just about
us anymore, all right?
This is about everyone now.
Your friends, your families...
Until we get paid,
they all suffer.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
Let's go.
Let the burning of
Letterkenny begin.
Gotta say, fellas, this is
coming together nicely.
I might actually spend
some time out here now.
WAYNE: With some
fuckin' clothes on?
Not my forte.
WAYNE: Unfortunate.
You brings us
sustenance while we are
hard at work, Katy.
That's what I
appreciates about you.
Is that what you
appreciate about me?
Go easy, squirrely
Dan. Thank you.
Your sister's hot, Wayne.
There, I said it.
DAN: I said it!
I regret nothing.
I regret nothing!
(DAN PANTING)
Too fat to run.
Fuckin' Stewart.
Fuckin' skids.
Where the fuck is this kid?
Fuckin' hate this kid.
Fuckin' wreck this kid.
Fuckin' kill this kid.
No, no. Just get 'em.
Yeah.
We'll hurt 'em.
Yeah. No, it's a metaphor.
Yeah, I get it.
Yeah.
Hey, but then we're here
for donnybrook, not him
and his buddies, buddy.
Oh, fuck.
We don't necessarily need to
wait for them to get here to
wreck the meth lab, buddy.
We can just fuckin'
wreck right now.
True.
Dibs on Devon, bro.
Jonesy, I don't even wanna
discuss dibs right now.
No discussion on dibs?
Buddy, we'll fuckin'
get 'em all.
Oh, yeah, okay, let's
Let's fucking do it, buddy.
(GRUNTS)
JONESY: It's already trashed.
RILEY: I'm not quite sure
how I feel about this, buddy.
JONESY: Bit anti‐climactic.
Isn't it, buddy?
Yeah. (EXHALES)
Shit!
Wonder who smashed
up his place, bro.
Fuckin' long hair
don't care, bro.
We find the skids
and have that fuckin'
donnybrook, buddy.
Buckets off?
Fuckin' rip over there
and just conflict.
Fight. Injure. Kill.
Ball up and bang out, bud.
Bust on. Bust up.
Download the scrap app.
Pugnacity. Truculence. Burkie.
Little squabble.
Little quibble. Smackdown!
Spar. Spat. Schism.
We are at this level!
But we need to
get to this level!
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
(CRASHING)
That's a lotta weed.
Sorry about what
happened here.
Know about the beef?
What beef?
Between your meth pals
and my daughter.
Two things. One,
no one who does meth
is a pal of mine
for fuck's sake.
Two, what are
you talking about?
She was ripped off on
a cigarette transaction by
some fellas from Letterkenny.
(SNIFFS)
And then?
She's owed money
by someone
from your town.
She's gonna make it
everyone's problem.
I'm sorry to be
the bearer of bad news.
Hope this serves as
some sort of consolation.
Count it if you like.
She won't stop until
she gets what's owed.
When Tanis comes
back to collect,
she won't be short staffed.
Us neither.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Fuckin' skids!
(SIGHS) Predictable!
Predictable!
Is this little soiree for us?
And you missed to a better
one at the Ag Hall
last weekend.
You should have come.
You gave the rookie
meth, idiot.
First one's free.
You fuckin' turned
Letterkenny into a war zone.
Got us labeled as
a meth town, idiot.
So, what are you
gonna do about it?
Idiot.
Buckets off.
Fuckin' go time.
Shed 'em.
Go me!
A little fuck me, fuck you?
MAN 1: Free fuckin' nose jobs?
MAN 2: Let's dance.
MAN 1: Hit the d‐floor.
TANIS: My balls dangle
harder than you.
Yeah, sounds familiar.
(WHISPERING) This is what
we've been waiting for.
Hey!
It's time.
You got our money?
Nay!
We do not have,
nor will we ever have,
a dime for you.
And you took away our only
source of income when
you trashed our meth lab!
(ALL LAUGH)
We're all here. So, uh...
It's combat,
let's proceed.
Power stop, Tanis.
We got dibs on the
donnybrook with the skids.
What's a dibs?
A dibs is a dibs is a dibs.
Hey! Pipe down, shit head.
You don't get it, do you?
This is about the money.
So, until we get the money,
Letterkenny will
continue to burn.
All right?
How are you now?
Good, and you?
Deadly.
Is that...
The Ginger and Boots.
(WHISPERS) Those two guys
fucked an ostrich.
Just the Ginger
Allegedly.
Mmm‐mmm. It would take
like two people to fuck
an ostrich. Three even...
It was a sick ostrich.
Allegedly.
You're fucking ruthless
for bringing a couple dudes
like that here.
(WHISPERS) In his defense...
He's usually not
the type of prick I am.
If they fucked an ostrich,
what else have they fucked?
Just the Ginger
fucked an ostrich.
Allegedly.
I ask again.
If they fucked an ostrich,
what else have they fucked?
It's almost not worth
thinkin' about.
(TANIS SIGHS)
Okay, speak.
Yous got ripped off.
It's too bad that happened.
And?
And it's none of my business.
Till it was my business.
Now, we could beat the fuck
outta yous right here.
And mark my words,
one day, we'll get ya.
But that doesn't solve
our problem here. Dary.
Your name's Dary?
It's Daryl.
That's just something my
friends call me sometimes.
We gotta put the damage
you're doing around
Letterkenny to bed.
That's 5k. What are
you's owed?
(SCOFFS) More than that.
We're tough fuckin' sleddin'!
Hey.
We're gonna call it 5k.
Is that what we're gonna do?
We are.
You're gonna take it
and leave Letterkenny.
And if yous come back for
so much as to pump your gas...
When he gives a warning,
he don't repeat it.
We'll get ya.
Deal. (CLEARS THROAT)
Beats fighting
an ostrich fucker.
All right, can we, uh,
part the hick sea here?
Uh, actually wait.
I got to know.
This has gotta sting
a little bit, right?
(CHUCKLES) I mean,
you're short, you're ugly,
you're incompetent,
you're fuckin' broke!
Fuckin' A.
You're a fuckin' addict,
you're hopeless.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
I mean you are
such a tragedy that
even all these people
here who hate you,
will bail you out, just so
they can...
What's the word?
Erase you.
My cousin was born with
fetal alcohol syndrome and
he works at a fuckin' bank.
What's your fucking excuse?
That'll do, Tanis.
Hey! I'm not
talking to you.
Look at you.
You got bloodshot eyes,
runny nose, fuckin' greasy
hair, scabs everywhere.
What is that?
What's that, right there?
You see that?
Is that cum? Dried cum
on your fuckin' zipper?
(TANIS LAUGHING)
I'm so sorry.
(TANIS INHALES)
Oh, you are pointless.
I bet, the second
you popped out,
your mom wished she had
a sewn up snapper.
Probably would've been
better if you grew to a
sickly size inside the womb
and killed the both of you
before you fuckin' rolled out
and started fucking up.
KATE: Bitch.
(GROANS) What?
I'll tell you what's gotta
sting a little bit.
(TANIS SCOFFS)
(GROANS)
Well, fuckin'
get after it, then!
RILEY: Well, Who would've
'thunk it. Fuck.
JONESY: Mmm‐hmm.
That was a top tier
sucker, Riley.
DAN: You too, Jonesy.
Thanks boys. I'd sucker
you guys in your sleep.
Still... Makes my
top three suckers, boys.
An A‐1 box shot,
you fuckin' barbarian.
Never claimed to be a lady.
Did you stop and smoke a joint
for a bit and then jump
right back in there?
Nectar of gods, fellas.
On the house.
All right! (CHEERING)
Well at this rate,
we'll need another one
soon, Gail.
(BANGING)
You know, I gotta say,
I'm looking forward
to a bit of peace
and quiet around here.
DAN: Hear, hear.
There ain't no reason to
get excited, am I right?
Yup.
Yeah.
MAN: All right.
Who the fuck is
the toughest guy in here?
That'd be me.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)