You heard a couple
nut sacks talkin' about
hockey the other day...
This kid.
Kid is a fuckin' stud.
Kid's a fuckin' beauty.
Fuckin' look at this kid.
Fuckin' love this kid.
Kid lights lamp.
Hashtag lamp life.
Eat, sleep, lamp.
Don't give him too much space,
buddy. He'll dangle.
He'll dangle all the fuckin'
way to outer space.
Suck some Martian
titties up there, boys.
Just getting super sloppy
all over our space dinks.
Silky mittens, top
tittens. Ferda boys.
Ferda!
Big roadie to the big city
this weekend, Schmelt.
Do you know
what that means?
Um...
Suckin' city titty, idiot.
Suckin' all that
big city titty, idiot.
All up that big
city slam piece.
Big city slams, idiot.
Big city billet moms.
Big city billet sisters.
Let's get our dinks
sucked on, boys.
Yes.
Hey, how's school going,
Schmelt?
It's going...
Just kidding.
We don't give a fuck.
Get our pops, Schmelt.
Big city slams, Schmelt.
(IMITATING AIR HORN)
How are ya now?
Not so bad.
Good and you?
Not too bad.
Have you shit yourself?
You look like you've got
an awkward boner.
Don't.
Don't what?
Dan?
Did you know that Daryl used
to get boners every morning
in grade nine during
O Canada?
No shit.
Yep. Just
could not get through O Canada
without getting a boner.
Give a young man 30
idle seconds and he's
gonna get a boner.
We talked about this.
Is there something you
want to talk about now?
Well, pitter patter,
let's get at 'er.
Well, I was wondering
if this year we could
skip the birthday party?
Skip your super soft birthday
party? Are you fuckin' high?
Hard no.
DAN: Daryl's super
soft birthday party?
Every year, Daryl's mom used
to throw him these birthday
parties when he was a kid.
Softest birthday party
on planet Earth.
Boy band karaoke, cupcake
decoration station,
charcuterie.
One year, his mom had him
a "Make the world a
better place" party.
One year they dressed
a horse up like a unicorn
and he was never really
the same after that.
It's not funny.
I used to take a lot of
teasing in school for those.
Aw, should I get
you a tissue, Sally?
No, he'll have
one in his purse.
Or maybe his clutch.
Party's happening, Daryl.
You don't fuck with tradition.
DAN: So. The agenda.
After your dust up over
the weekend, safe to assume
you're fighting again?
Co‐rect.
Ten‐four, good buddy.
Well, it's gonna be a busy
week 'cause there's a few
guys walking around town
claiming to be
the toughest guys
in Letterkenny.
I'm the toughest
guy in Letterkenny.
You were the toughest
It's been some time.
Now, it's safe to assume that
that title is as important to
you now as it was then?
Does a duck with a
boner drag weeds?
Ten‐four, good buddy!
Then it's safe to assume
that the challengers will
be coming up around the farm,
as that is how you've
conducted business
in the past.
Well, I was never
one for an audience.
All right, let's talk
about the challengers.
First up,
we've got Sled Ted.
Why's he called Sled Ted?
Well, he likes fixin' sleds,
and ridin' sleds,
and talkin' about sleds.
He just really
likes sleddin', boys.
Uh, he beat up a
guy named Basic Jay.
Why's he called Basic Jay?
'Cause he's a fuckin' basic.
DAN: And now he thinks
he's the toughest guy
in Letterkenny.
After that,
we got Rat Ass.
Why's he called Rat Ass?
'Cause he's got a
hairy ass like a rat.
Can confirm.
He beat up a guy
named Brains.
See, his name's Brian
but he spelt it Brain
in the computer at bowling
one time. It just kinda stuck.
DAN: Now he thinks he's the
toughest guy in Letterkenny.
And after that,
we got Joint Boy.
Because he smokes
lots of joints, Dairy.
Well, just plucking
the low hanging fruit
is what that is.
I've seen that guy take
on four bouncers at
the rippers one time.
He is otherworldly.
Got a dome on him like
an Easter Island statue.
Is he single?
Not that it matters,
I guess.
Look, keep it at the
end of the lane way.
No degens on the property.
That's a Texas size 10‐4.
Over and out.
Well, this is annoying.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR RADIO)
The fuck are they
doin' out there?
They're scared of you.
(SIGHS)
This snipe is
a fuckin' sniper.
Snipe's a fuckin' beauty.
Fuckin' look at this snipe.
Fuckin' love this snipe.
We're snipe selling, boys.
Dirty fucking
dangles, boys.
You're a sniper.
You're a snipe.
You're a skirt,
you pansy.
If you make me walk up
the lane way again,
we're having babies.
Put it out! Put it
out! Put it out!
Fuck!
Those boys need
to give their
balls a tug.
Maybe, check, make
sure they're still
attached right quick.
I'd rather put a mirror down
there and see what's what.
One time,
my cousin...
He tore open his
ball sack trying to
do a skateboard trick
and he had to show
it to his mum.
Was it his scrotal sack?
Well, you know. That dangly
piece of flesh, what hangs
down behind the penis.
Scrotal sack.
The nut sack.
So, he tore his ball
sack open trying to do
a skateboard trick
and he's gots to show it to
his mum because apparently one
of his testicles was showing.
Was it the right one
or the left one?
Why is that
of importance?
Well, because the left
one has more sperm in it.
Spermatozoa is
what it's called.
Tell you what, if I ripped
open my ball sack trying to
do a skateboard trick,
I'd be more worried about
seeing my vas deferens.
Well, you'd have to tear your
ball sack pretty near wide
open doing a skateboard trick
if you wanted to see
your own vas deferens.
I'm not sure I wanna
see my own vas deferens
I think if I saw my
own vas deferens,
I'd be quite worried.
I'd be most worried if I tore
my ball sack open trying to do
a skateboard trick
if I could see my
accessory glands.
Well, you don't want to go
too kooky with accessories
on your truck.
Or your jeep. It's okay
with like, a quad, though,
like my buddy Big T's got
a snorkel kit on his and
that's pretty punk rock.
What's an
accessory gland?
Well, if your vas deferens
is your sperm ducts,
the accessory glands is
what supplies lubricant
to the sperm duct.
I think if I ripped open
my ball sack trying to do
a skateboard trick,
I'd be most worried about
seeing my seminal vesicles.
Oh, like the Florida
State seminal vesicles?
Like the sack that hangs
behind your vas deferens
and contains fructose
which is energy
for the sperm.
Yeah, it's like when you
go in the city there and
they got them charge stations
for the people that
drive the electric cars.
That's pretty much
your seminal vesticles.
I thought it was pretty
funny when I said
Florida State seminal vesicles
and nobody laughed.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Okay.
End of the lane way.
Don't come up the property.
Good.
Sled Ted's here.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Geez, Basic Jay must
have been a shit fighter
to lose to that ass‐hat.
I've known Basic Jay
to be a pretty tough dude.
He's not really
a fuckin' basic.
Guess he could
have had a cold.
Or the flu.
Sled Ted had Bigfoot hands.
Yeah, he's a big grimy brute.
Shit fighter, though.
Do you guys remember
the fragrance Brut?
Or Actif Brut?
Yeah.
Yeah, they still
make that.
I always enjoyed
that fragrance.
You can use it to
dry up zits too.
Did you know you can use
shaving cream to get permanent
marker off your hands?
Why wouldn't you
just dip your hands
in the parts cleaner?
Well, most people don't
have a parts cleaner.
Well, most likely Rat Ass
will be your next dude.
I hear that he is a greaser.
Can confirm.
So fuckin' greasy
I almost don't want to.
I saw him with his shirt off,
swimming at the gravel pit
not that long ago.
His back acne
was extraordinary.
Well, like,
extraordinary how?
Well, like, I thought
about it for a while
after is all.
Well, elaborate,
'cause I'm likely
gonna have to touch it.
Well, like how
it was cultivated.
WAYNE: Well, by not
showering likely.
Likely.
Did you know that men
can wear the fragrance
CK ONE as well as women?
Yeah.
DAN: Yeah.
That's 'cause it's
an unisex fragrance.
It says that right
on the bottle.
But would ya?
Oh, negative.
Me neither.
Would you wear
Gap Dream?
DAN: No!
No, no, Dairy,
that's for girls.
Dairy, that's for girls.
You can't walk around
smelling like pretty girls.
You're not wearing
it right now, are you?
Cologne is too expensive.
I just use sunscreen.
Banana Boat.
Let's get into some of those
fuckin' all dressed chips.
WAYNE: Jesus, Katy,
put some fuckin' clothes on.
Not my forte.
Unfortunate.
Hey, neighbor said
he's not gonna give
us a horse this year.
What?
Well, he said that last year
we returned him and his
breath smelled like alcohol.
Well, it was probably mine.
You could have lit my breath
on fire the next day.
Horse was
half cut though.
He said that he's gonna
give us a donkey.
Nope.
Might be funny.
Gotta be a horse.
You don't fuck
with tradition.
You're really gonna pump
the brakes on a donkey
dressed up like a unicorn?
Oh, I'm stompin'
the brakes.
You put that idea
right through the
fuckin' windshield.
But it's a donkey dressed
up like a unicorn.
Katy!
Well, it's better than
a kick in the pants.
Do you want this to
be the softest birthday
party ever or not?
I want this just
as much as you do.
Well, then find
us a horse.
Please and thank you.
And don't stay out in the
sun too long.
Your skin will
look like an old saddle bag.
Yeah.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
Okay.
End of the lane way.
Don't come up the property.
Good.
Rat Ass is here.
Keep it standing.
This goes to the
ground, we stand up.
Okay.
This goes to a clinch,
we separate.
Great. Let's go!
All right.
So, hit me.
Fight him or
shut the fuck up.
I'll give you
a free one.
What the fuck is this?
Let's fuckin' do this.
Just fuckin'
square off.
WAYNE: Hey! He's pulling hair,
he's pulling hair.
Break 'em up, break 'em up.
Come on, come on!
DAN: I'm gonna clock
this shitty wolverine.
(YELLING)
Hit me. Come on. I love pain.
Look at the
execution, boys.
Look at the hustle, boys.
Ding.
You guys made
the liquor run,
right?
I was Donny
Drives the car.
I was Nicki Navigates.
But, uh...
We couldn't find a lot
of the stuff on the list.
Yeah.
Like what?
Uh, well...
Uh, there's
ingredients
that I don't think you can
get in Letterkenny.
Yeah.
So, go to the city.
Yeah, but we got practice
in a couple of hours.
We're gonna crush a couple
sandos before, too.
Grab some
nappies, maybe?
We haven't had our
pre‐game naps either.
Nappies are nappies. Ferda.
Ferda.
Well, we need
everything on the list.
So, what drinks do you
need ingredients for?
Uh,
Corebelo Love Potion.
Uh, Purple Passion Punch.
Lemon Gingerini.
Apricot Toblerone Cocktail.
Couldn't find
a Flirtini.
Couldn't find Sparkling
Mango Sorbet Float.
Don't...
Don't know really
what that is.
Well, that's all of them.
Ye... Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Look, I have about a million
things to do if this is
gonna be the softest
birthday party ever.
If you guys don't get me
everything on the list,
you'll be pulling each
other's horns from now on.
(PHONE BEEPS)
Pitter patter!
(BOTH GROANING)
So far!
Fuck, was he a beaker.
Like, he would not
stop beaking.
That shit
is the worst.
That was right to stick to
the task at hand, pal.
Keep your trap shut.
Throw bombs.
I wouldn't say shit
if my mouth was
full of it.
I haven't seen that many
hits since Good Charlotte
played Warped Tour.
Yeah, more like...
Not very Good Charlotte.
I always liked NOFX.
YESFX.
Big fuckin' day, Dairy.
Big fuckin' day!
Ow.
Happy birthday, it's your
special day Dairy.
DAN: Birthday beats!
Birthday beats!
Ow. Oh, that's
not polite, Katy.
You really are a Sally.
That's the most action I've
seen since I gave the dairy
cows' teats a good scrubbin'.
I don't need
to know that.
You're pretty good at
wrestling there, Katy,
and that's what
I appreciates about you.
Is that what you
appreciate about me?
Let's go easy over there,
squirrelly Dan.
Yeah. Oh, hey,
look at you, ground.
So, tell me about
this guy, Joint Boy.
Well, I'm not gonna
sugar coats it for you, Wayne.
This guy looks like an
Australian rugbies player,
chiseled out of stones.
Uh‐oh.
Got legs on him
like tree trunks.
Is that a deciduous tree
or a coniferous tree?
What?
Well, there's a difference.
If we're talking about,
like, a maple tree,
which is thick
and deciduous
or a Christmas tree, which
is thin and coniferous.
Yeah, but both is hards
and mades of woods, right?
There's a difference
is all I'm saying.
What type of tree
is a coconut tree?
It's a palm tree.
How do you know?
Well, like the Internet.
Oh.
Anyways, backs to Joint Boy.
How come I've never
heard of him before?
Oh, he just gots out of jail.
He was arrested for assaults
after he beats the shits
out of a guy for
pushin' up on his sister.
Got this big
entourage of guys,
bald‐headed, bearded dudes
what looks like a whole
bunch of surly uncles.
You think we should
call The Ginger?
Mmm.
No.
DARYL: Why not?
He's tougher than hell.
WAYNE: Yeah, but...
Well, like you heard he
fucked an ostrich, right?
He what?
He fucked an ostrich.
Allegedly.
How does a fella get caught
up in that sort of business?
Well, I guess his cousin
had an ostrich farm
when he thought it
might be fun to fuck one.
Allegedly.
So, he got hard
somehow
and he fucked an ostrich.
That's fucked.
That's a felony.
So, we use him in
emergencies only, then.
I should say.
Dairy. Hey, Dairy.
This one's for you.
Oh.
DARYL: Hey, Joint Boy's here.
Which one of youse is Wayne?
We got some business.
You're interrupting a party
for my best pal
that my little sister worked
pretty hard to put on.
Hold it.
May I sort this out
now, please?
Goddamn right you may.
WAYNE: Thank you.
Don't lose.
You had yourself a scrap
the other weekend at Modean's.
What's it to ya?
You left the dude
pretty banged up.
I heard he kicked a slow
learning fella in the bum
while he was havin' a piss.
Now, that slow learning
fella is my second cousin.
Okay.
Being the toughest
guy in Letterkenny is
important to me.
I'm sure it is
to you too
but we're all hicks here.
And you've done me a favor,
so I'd be willing to shake
your hand and call it a day.
I didn't do you no favors.
'Cause I don't know
who the fuck you are.
We done talking?
You wanna come to a
super soft birthday party?
Happy birthday,
Dairy.
It's really more
for them, ain't it?
What is?
DAN: All this.
No, it's not.
It's cream cheese.
No.
That's cream cheese.
Yeah, that's
cream cheese.
Just go...
Jesus!
You remember they
weren't allowed to have
birthday parties growing up.
They had to go
bucky at mine.
DAN: All they do is go
alls out, don'ts they?
DARYL: That's
a Texas size 10‐4.
You know, if Joint Boy
and his pals hadn't
showed up,
I figure this would have been
the softest birthday ever.
That's a small victory
for you, I suppose.
I was worried.
Thought I might have to get
Stewart and the Skids to come
over here and start
hoovering up that
white powder of theirs.
DARYL: Anything for a little
bit of an edge, am I right?
DAN: The white stuff.
The snooter.
The devil's dandruff.
The dander.
I... I hoovered
up a bit of the
schneef in my day.
You ever hoovered
barnyard schneef?
I've hoovered behind the
manure pile schneef.
You ever hoovered schneef
off a sleeping cow's spine?
I've hoovered schneef off
of an awake cow's teat.
What are the odds that
I ride him home bareback?
Gonna hurt
your balls, bro.
Good going.
Oh, yeah.
You ever hoovered
library schneef?
I've hoovered schneef
off of the cover of
Gordon Korman's
This Can't Be Happening
at Macdonald Hall.
You wanna come
home with me?
You can sleep
in my bed.
He'd break it.
He'd break your bed.
His dick alone
would break your bed.
I saw that too.
I... Yeah.
It was really big.
(PHONE BEEPING)
You ever hoovered
Sunday school schneef?
I've hoovered schneef
off the collection plate
in the rectory.
Do you know what
dick dingers are?
Yep.
You know that movie
with the guy who
whispers to horses.
Brokeback Mountain?
No.
DARYL: That's the toughest
guy in Letterkenny.
(BLOWING PARTY WHISTLE)