You were out gettin' good
with your pals
the other night.
It's been so long
since I've had a pair
of tits in my hands,
I popped a lap rocket
opening up a can of tuna
last Sunday morning.
Oh, that's off‐putting.
Not to old Gail,
it isn't.
I'd love to hear your
big bang theory, Daniel.
WAYNE: Ew.
Print it.
This is officially me
callin' down for more mayo.
That's clever.
GAIL: Do you like magic?
Pop that purple
home wrecker over here.
I'll make her disappear.
We should
just be out there
just pole vaultin'
around town, boys.
Wouldn't say no
to a bit of toe curlin'
and I don't mean maybe.
GAIL: It won't be long
before you have the option.
College and university kids
will be home for the summer
next week.
Well, that should
help your spring fever.
Which is a serious condition
if not handled appropriately.
Mini‐skirt and T‐bar season.
Yup. By all means, ladies.
Express yourselves.
Go easy down there,
Squirrely Dan.
I suffered severely
from the spring fever
last year,
had to go into
full cougar mode
with an 18‐year‐old.
Oh?
May have been
my second cousin.
Oh.
It was either that
or be at home flickin' it
to Grapefruit League
baseball highlights.
You know they're all
gonna be in here lookin'
for a bit of
"How's your father?"
Make sure your game
is tight or you'll
be home firing wristers.
Firing what?
Oh.
What say we make
this interesting.
Whichever one of you
grabs a tail first
gets 50 bucks
off their bar tab.
In.
That is a Texas
sized 10‐4.
No, you two
get after it.
Here's a tip.
When the gettin's good
around here, stay close
to your pal Wayne.
Kid's got more spunk
than a hotel room
hand towel.
Well, here's a tip.
Don't fart in a spacesuit.
Here's a tip.
Don't sneeze when
you're taking a piss.
Here's a tip.
It's really hard to get tuna
out of your dick hole.
This place is about to be
crawling with snapper.
Let's hope
this is the last night
you'll be going home
to make a bald man puke.
You naturally
prefer companionship,
but I guess there's
a lot worse things
than playing a little one man
couch hockey in the dark.
REILLY: Wearing number 22
for the Tackville Tornados...
(SPITS)
Who fuckin' cares.
Dig deep, bare down,
you fuckin' hero.
You're my fuckin' hero,
two‐two.
Nice flow,
you fuckin' donkey.
Take a lap.
TEAMMATE: Hey,
give your balls a tug,
you tit fucker!
What the fuck are you
lookin' at, twos, huh?
You lookin' at my cock,
you fuckin' sally?
Mix in some class,
you fuckin' cock looker!
You're a fuckin'
cock looker, two‐two!
Hey, shut the fuck up.
You're a fuckin' hero,
twos.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Fuckin' suck at hockey,
two‐two!
Loser.
REILLY: Ever wonder why
Katy doesn't come
watch us play anymore, bud?
Makes no fuckin'
sense, buddy.
Just fuckin' stud army
born to go silky shelf.
Silky studs.
I mean Italian silk.
Just rippin' ched.
Just chuckin' mitts
and suckin' tits.
(SPITS)
Tossin' mitties,
suckin' titties.
Just look at
the snipers up there.
Here to support
the boys.
Must be nice Ferda.
Ferda...
It'd be pretty sick
to see Katy
up there again.
So sick.
Atta be sures, eh?
First thirsty Thursday
of the season, boys.
How's team morale?
I'm most excited
for Buck Hunter.
Boy, I'm gonna tell ya
that's what I'm gonna do,
holy fuck.
You guys know if Gail's
making pickled eggs
or pickled sausages?
Bear in mind there
is no wrong answer
to this question.
I'm gonna be posting up
and looking for love,
and I don't care
who knows it.
Don't set the bar
too high, mutant.
That's fair.
KATY: You guys going to be
wearing belts?
Hard no.
Why don't you guys
wear belts?
'Cause we buy pants
that fucking fit.
Why would I buy
a piece of leather
that costs $25,
when I have a perfectly good
skate lace at home?
$25? No.
Fucking $25,
you're lucky to have
a $25 bill.
Fuck, you've been
to Winners lately?
You're talking
about $35, $45.
Winners. Slow down there,
Mr. Rocketfeller.
I go down to
the flea market
at St. Jacobs,
$25 could get you
at least five belts.
Plus, a commemorative
belt buckle says,
"Jesus holds up my pants."
For Sunday morning.
Boy, howdy.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
REILLY: Ten losses
in a row, bro.
JONESY: Two's a streak, bro.
REILLY: Like where the fuck
Schultzy been out there?
Schultzy's dog shit.
Soupy's a plug.
Smitty's a pile.
Millsy.
Cartsy.
Burnsy.
Deetzy.
Brooksy.
Brooksy's got
a hern‐dog.
Seri‐dog?
He's having off‐season surgery
for a sports hern‐dog.
He's out
four to six.
Four to six for.
Best plan.
Where's Coopsy been?
Playing like poopsy.
Playing like
Milan Poocic.
P. K. Pooban.
And Ryan Poo‐gent Hopkins.
Pookka Rask.
The brothers Miko
and Saku Koi‐poo.
REILLY: Joke, bro.
JONESY: It's embarrassing.
Katy!
How come you don't
watch us play anymore?
'Cause you're dog shit.
We're not dog shit.
I mean, the boys
are dog shit.
But we're pretty good.
Is that why they always play
and you guys never do?
She might be onto
something there, bro.
Not seeing a whole lot of
special teams time, buddy.
I haven't killed
a penalty all year.
I mean, we wanna score goals,
but we'd just end up
killing them boys.
Mmm‐hmm.
Would you come watch
if we play a regular shift?
Duh. The fuck else
am I going to do
around here?
Time to set up
a meeting with the Coach.
Buh‐doo!
(BOTH SPITTING)
We're the biggest
Pantene pros
in the league.
Mix in some big minutes
for a couple stick
and pucksters.
You guys don't give a shit
about winning.
You just like the hockey
player lifestyle.
You are posers.
So what are we
gonna do?
COACH: You need
to get in shape!
Study the tape!
Play with
some intensity!
Hold my spitter.
So basically what
you are saying is...
We're at this level.
But we've got to get
to this level.
(CLAPS HANDS) Done!
You're a fucking beauty.
Registered beautician.
What do you guys
think of the program?
Well...
Uh...
Just kidding,
I don't give a fuck.
Gutty.
Yeah, a little gutty.
That's a little gutty.
Fuck.
(BOTH SPIT)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
DAN: That's when you
cut off her balls.
Cut off her balls?
Correct.
DARYL: I think you mean,
"Cut off his balls."
DAN: Incorrect.
Oh, no?
Oh, yes.
That is why you never give
a sword to a hooker.
Hey, Wayne.
How many planets
are there?
WAYNE: Well, with the whole
Pluto debate.
Give or take,
eight planets.
There'll only be seven
after I destroy Uranus.
Buy you a drink?
Okay.
Who's that?
WAYNE: Who?
Kyle Schneidstiller's sister?
DARYL: Is that
who she is?
That's Kyle Schneidstiller's
little sister.
You know,
he's a decent dude.
She's finer
than frog hair.
Have an eye
for the fertility, boys.
She's been
knocked‐up twice.
She's a one‐shot Sally.
WAYNE: Also...
She dated Boots
for a little while
before he went to jail.
You guys ever hear
anything about that guy
fucking an ostrich?
No...
The Ginger fucked
an ostrich.
Allegedly.
It would take more
than one guy
to fuck an ostrich.
We've heard
that it was
a sick ostrich.
Well, it would take
two guys to fuck an ostrich.
Three even.
Again,
we're hearing it was
a sick ostrich.
Still, it's a three‐man job
to fuck one.
But wait...
Was that before
or after he dated
Kyle Schneidstiller's sister?
Oh, it's almost
not worth thinkin' about.
WAYNE: Oh, we have an eye.
She's sweet
on you, Dary.
Is that what she is?
That's your next sweetie
right there.
Go talk to her.
What's your
logic there?
You see what she's doing
with her hair?
That's called
a hair show.
When a gal's sweet
on a guy,
and she wants to
get his attention,
she just starts fucking
with her hair whole bunch.
What for?
So you notice more
about the way they look.
Like how her face is framed
with her hair up or down.
And also make you
think like...
Well, I wouldn't
wanna touch it.
Well, yeah, I think
I would like to touch it.
Well, get after it.
But don't lead
with the touchin', though.
All right. I will.
Just, not just yet.
Maybe after a couple.
There.
JONESY: Okay, bro,
workout program.
(WATER RUNNING)
Go.
Gotta start with burpees,
buddy.
Just ripping burpee
boxshums, buddy.
50 burpees,
50 pushups.
50 pushups...
Stairs.
Protein break.
Just ripping
skull crashers.
Just rippin' forced reps.
Forced rep super sets.
Bird up.
Just rippin'
anti‐gravity press.
Advanced Kettlebell Windmill.
Just rippin' barbell
half‐squats.
Just rippin' drop sets.
Just rippin' Swiss ball
jackknifes.
Just rippin'
silly animal stack.
Just rippin' bent over
rear delt raise
with head on bench.
Fuckin' delts to die for,
buddy.
Just rippin' cable rope
overhead tricep extensions.
#Noexcuses.
#Beachbody.
Legs?
Hate doing legs.
Let's skip leg day.
TEAMMATE: That's the best
ass‐wash of your life
right there, boys.
Good work,
Shoresy.
Look at the hustle on,
Best ass‐wash
of your life.
(VIDEO GAME GUNFIRE)
Ooh.
Scored a perfect score
in the bonus round.
Don't think I've ever
seen that before.
Remember what happened
here today.
You can't forget
something like that.
Seen Angie in here
with her new boyfriend
again a couple nights ago.
Oh, who gives a care.
Remember I told you
he was in a '94 Jeep YJ with
a wave decal on the side?
He made an upgrade.
Short trip.
Pulled in here with a 2003
aquamarine Audi wagon
with a magenta "Fear this"
sticker on the back.
Ain't no reason
to get excited.
Came in here wearing
a pair of Fandango
pink pastel khakis
with a white, gold
leather chain
fuckin' wallet,
and a Creed T‐shirt on.
Remarkable.
I know.
He had a deep carrot
orange fedora with
a burnt orange stripe
and a little cauliflower
blue feather
with a fucking,
I don't know,
looked like to me
some kind of
a black‐bearded titmouse
or some kind of shit.
Did you know
there's a type of bird
called a Bushtit?
I did not.
It's a type
of chickadee.
He also had
an imperial purple...
That'll do, McMurray.
Oh, I'm just sayin'
it must suck balls
to lose to a fucking
douchebag like that.
Hi.
Heard you doin' all right
at Buck Hunter.
What say I give you
a quick squeezer in
the parking lot there, eh?
Could be worse.
Could indeed.
There a vet around
here, ladies?
These puppies are sick.
Christ, I would
snort her dandruff.
DARYL: Dandruff is a fungus.
I think you mean you'd
sniff her flakes.
Then you are giving me
far too much credit, my boy.
(LOUDLY) Oh, oh.
Lookin' some comely
tonight there, big fella.
Do you wanna know
what, Gail?
I think you've got a case
of the spring fever.
Can I get you a drink?
Okay.
You see that one?
She's like a Middle Eastern
rebel army.
'Cause there's a political
uprising in my pants.
Well, shoulders back.
Here she comes.
Excuse me, boys.
She's sweet on you.
Get after it.
You think so?
You see what she
just did?
Touched your back
and then, moved on?
That's called the
unnecessary squeeze‐by.
Is that what
it's called?
Mmm‐hmm.
You noticed she had about
half a fuckin' soccer field
to get past
but instead leaned in close,
got a bit handsy
like there was only
a tiny lane to get by?
The unnecessary
squeeze‐by.
Go talk to her.
Let's fire back
a couple of shots first.
Well, this is
swiftly becoming
a counterproductive practice,
but okay.
Look at Coopsy
out there.
Just dog shit.
You mean
Claude Gir‐poo?
Roberto Poo‐ongo.
I mean, look at you.
You're fuckin' Kenny
coast‐to‐coast
out there, buddy.
You're Harry High‐Sock buddy.
Cory clap bombs.
Thank you.
Sniper.
Snipe!
Didn't your coach
tell you to get in shape?
It's our cheat day.
We'll be rippin'
silly plyometrics
right after this
so they cancel
each other out.
Then it's arms.
Just rippin'
concentration curls.
Just rippin' cross body
hammer curls.
Just rippin' alternate
dumbbell bicep curls.
Just rippin' lying close grip
bar curl on high pulley.
Just rippin'
alternate one‐arm
dumbbell preacher curls.
Just rippin' standing
one‐arm bicep curl
over incline bench.
You're an idiot.
We're smoke‐bombing over
to throw some weights
around now.
You wanna come?
Okay.
Ninja dust.
Resistance training!
Muscle atrophy!
Take some snaps
of us, snipe.
Yeah, take some snaps
for our Facebooks, snipey!
Take your shirts off.
Tarps off, boys.
Sheddin' tarp, boys.
(BOTH PANTING)
Take a knee, boys.
Grab a knee boys.
(EXHALES)
Those beta‐blockers
really helped you up your
explosive potential, bro.
Muscular endurance,
muscular strength, bro.
Really working those
fast‐twitch
muscle fibers, buddy.
Isokinetic exercise
to really test your
lactic threshold, buddy.
You're never gonna plateau
with that overload
principle, buddy.
Rate of
perceived exertion.
You really hit
your target heart rate
with vigorous intensity.
JONESY: Thanks, buddy.
REILLY: (EXHALES) So?
We got in shape
and studied the tape.
You gonna come watch us
play with intensity tomorrow?
Yeah, I could do that.
Wheel, snipe,
celly, boys!
Fuckin' dangles, boys!
Ninja dust.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi.
Hmm? How are you now?
Good and you?
Not so bad.
Um... Do you know
where the washroom is?
Sure,
just right
back there.
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
And I'm Jessica.
Wayne.
I know.
Now tell me
you saw that.
GAIL: What?
She's givin' me
the big eyes.
Is that what she was doing?
Big eyes?
You know, when a gal's
sweet on a dude
and she's shorter than him?
Instead of tilting
her neck up
to look at him,
she'll just keep her head
straight and look up
with her eyes.
Like puppy dog eyes.
It's like...
"Do you know where
the washroom is?"
Versus...
"Do you know where
the washroom is?"
Okay. Yeah.
Big eyes.
Wayne, she's still
giving you the big eyes.
Well, don't have
to tell me twice.
It's about time
one of you showed
some finish.
She's so hot I'd jerk off
her dad just to see
where she came from.
Who? Jivin' Pete?
No.
That's her dad.
Jivin' Pete.
Yeah.
Got his nuts are
all bunned up
after a donkey
kicked him.
Ruptured the hydrocele.
One of them swole up
to look like
a ripe avocado.
Other one looks like
a peach pit.
I'll get him
to show it to you.
He'll show to just about
anybody when he's drunk.
Either way, whole unit's
more cauliflowered than
a UFC fighter's ear.
(PLAYERS SHOUTING)
Nice, nice penalty kill,
boys.
I love the hustle!
Love the hustle!
Look at that hustle, eh?
Well,
piece of shit...
Who brought the
fuckin' rocket, boys?
TEAMMATE 1:
Holy fuck, boys.
Who's billet sister's
a fuckin' rocket?
TEAMMATE 2:
She's a fuckin' rocket.
I got a fucking rocket
in my pants, right now.
TEAMMATE 2:
Hey, dibs on digis, boys.
TEAMMATE 1:
Already dibs'd digits, buddy.
No, I dibs'd
her in warm up,
you were throwin' sauce
at the blue line.
I was dibsing digis.
Who the fuck
you dibs 'em to?
TEAMMATE 2: A dibs is a dibs
is a dibs, buddy.
Who gives a shit.
If a dibs falls
in the forest
and there's no one
around to hear it,
is it still a dibs?
Well, fuck, yeah, buddy!
Fuck, no, buddy!
Give your balls a tug,
you tit fucker!
Wake up,
you fuckin' pheasants!
BOTH: Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
(THUDDING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Wake up, you mutants.
You're missing out
on all the girls
who do not want to
have sex with you.
Awfully pedestrian effort
from our boys tonight, Katy.
No discount on bar tabs
tonight, Chester and Charlie!
What was
your problem, big shoots?
He did all right.
Didn't you, Wayne?
He spent some time
in the bathroom
with a little
blonde spinner
who had such
a butt on her.
I took one look at it
and I thought,
"Jesus Christ, woman,
"you shit with
that ass?"
Attaboy!
Boys!
Sniper.
Snipe!
KATY: Gotta say, I had
a fucking hoot at the game.
Two fights.
Hockey players have
the nicest asses.
Okay, we don't want you
coming anymore.
Too distracting
for the boys.
Ferda.
What?
Uh...
It's too distracting.
For the boys.
KATY: Yeah, no,
I heard you.
I heard you say
that I'm a distraction.
Okay.
Well, guess I'll have to
find one of your teammates
to dibs my digits.
BOTH: But we dibs'd
those digis!
You did a decent job
with these d‐gens tonight.
Thank you, Gail.
I said decent.
You forgot the
most important thing.
Don't get so drunk you
couldn't use it even
if you had the option.
Mmm‐hmm.
I'll tell you what
and I'll only tell you once.
You've got the pick
of the litter around here
so you may as well
get pickin'.
I've got this fifty bucks
and no one to claim it.
What say we put it
in your jeans
and see what else is
hangin' around in there
while we're at it?
No.
Like what's in your jeans,
big fella?
Nothin'...
I mean it. Cripes,
I may not go down
in history,
but I'll go down on you.
Okay.
(CHUCKLING)
You want to do 68?
I'll help you clean up.
You'll go down on me?
And I'll owe you one.
Where's that rag?
There it is.
Wake up, big shoots
and really big shoots.
More hands
make less work.
Call me cake!
'Cause I go straight
to your ass, cowboy.
There's cake?
No.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)