We were discussing headlines
from the city newspaper
the other day...
DAN: Damn shame
about MoDeans
burning down.
Do you know what?
It's really something
how we keep losing
those locations
to drink at.
The Ukrainian Center
is a healthy
consolation, though.
Well, everybody knows
the cheapest beers are
at the Ukrainian Center.
With the Legion being
a close second.
When's Gail getting back
from her South American
singles resort?
When she's
had her fill, I suppose.
Delicious pun.
Thank you, Wayne.
ALL: Thank you, Bonnie.
(DAN GRUMBLING)
Now, was that
your tummy grumbling?
Or was that you proper?
DAN: That'd
be me proper.
A little grumble
in the jungle over there.
Little grumble
in the Bronx.
A little
royal grumble.
DAN: It was
a grumble proper.
Now, I'm a devout pupil
of Social Justice Warriors,
Professor Tricia.
The devoutest.
But dare I say things
in the city is getting
wee bit out of hands.
What's the frequency,
Kenneth?
Well, the story I just read
here is quite the incredible
chain of events.
You know, there's
so many causes now.
They're just tripping
right over each other.
Well, it's better than
driving into each other.
That was
a bit dark, Dary.
What's the scoop, Dan?
Here's the scoop.
Bunch of gals said that
they were gonna stop
tweetings for a day
out of protest
for sexual abuses
towards womens.
And they encouraged mens
to stops tweetings
in supports of the womens.
So, what's
the problem?
Oh, I wasn't finished.
Well, what
happened next?
DAN: I'll tells you
what happens next.
Some black gals joined in
on the protest,
but they got mad
at the white girls
protesting,
because womens of colors
didn't receive the same
supports on similar issues.
I think I see where
you're going with this.
Well, did something
happen even after that?
DAN: Something
did happen after that.
One of the white gals
asking for supports
got supports from one guy,
but she told him
he could fuck right off
because apparently he used
to call gals "broads"
back in high schools.
But they are tweeting
about not tweeting.
Do I have that right?
I got a feeling something
even happened after that.
Yeah, me too, Dary.
Me too. I got that
same feeling.
Well, here's what happened
even after that.
The President of Iceland
sends out
a happy birthday tweet
to his daughter, Alfheiour.
And now all the gals
saying that you
shouldn't be tweetings
turns hims into
public enemy number one.
And it's on Twitter
they're doing that?
And to the President
of Iceland,
they're doing that?
Icelanders are the most
lovable fucking people
on planet Earth.
One more thing
even happens,
so help me God.
So help me God.
Something else
did happen after that,
because it turns out
the President of Iceland's
daughter, Alfheiour,
has got herself a case
of the Down syndromes.
So here comes the Special
Olympics advocates,
and they're
in a real bad way.
As they should be.
If you wanna go at Iceland,
you better have your fucking
facts right.
Well, here's the kicker,
turns out the President of
Iceland's daughter, Alfheiour,
is also a refugee
from war‐torn Somalia
what he's adopted.
So that increases
the tension between
the womens of colors
not tweeting
and the white gals
not tweeting.
To top it all off,
here comes World Vision,
and they're
coming in a'swinging.
Fuck every duck.
What next?
Oh, here's what
happened after that.
Remember that first guy
that they told
to fucks right off
'cause he used to
call gals "broads"
back in high school?
Turns out he's paralyzed
from the waist down.
So here comes the war amps
saying, "You better back
the fuck off our guy."
Enough's enough.
I can't handle anymore.
Well, there's no way
there's more.
There's no goddamn way.
Wait. There is more.
Turns out the President
of Icelands
is paralyzed from
the necks down,
so now everybody's back
on Iceland's sides again.
Oh, right where
they should've been
the whole fucking time.
Now, it's from the neck down
that he's paralyzed, you say?
So, how does he
even make a tweet?
And they're all
doing this on Twitter?
Where else but Twitter
would this be happenings?
On the day they're not
exposed to be tweeting?
On the very same day
they're not exposed
to be tweeting.
ALL: Jesus!
DAN: (GASPING)
Look what's happening
in local news!
ALL: What?
Stay tuned to find out.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Well, the Letterkenny Chiefs
is changing their names
and logos.
That sounds
about right.
Probably for the best.
They had a good run.
The only constant in life
is change, as they say.
"The only constant
in life is change"?
It's a wee bit to wrap
your head around there.
Well, the only constant
around here is everything
stays the sames.
Any‐who...
According to the writers
of the Letterkenny Banner,
the whole world's going to
hells in a hand baskets.
DARYL: Sounds
about right.
KATY: Probably
for the best.
WAYNE: We had a good run.
As long as we're
going in a hand basket.
As opposed to
what kind of basket?
Well, there's a bazillion
different kinds of baskets.
Hand and waste paper.
What else?
Okay, so maybe
there's not a bazillion
different kinds, but...
Yeah, it's
definitely not a bazillion
different kinds...
Yeah, that's what
I just said,
"There's not a bazillion
different kinds of baskets."
Well, don't come in here
saying "bazillion" unless
you mean a bazillion...
Okay. I was just for
emphasis. I was saying,
"Bazillion different
kinds of baskets."
Go ahead and name
five kinds of baskets
besides hands
and waste paper.
Okay. Floor basket,
hanging basket,
wall basket,
bike basket,
basketball basket.
All right.
I withdraw.
Bamboo bakset,
britan bakset,
liquor bakset.
Bakset?
Yes, that's one of
two words that Dary
can't say right.
What's the other
one, Dary?
Brefekst.
Yeah, Dary can't say
the word "breakfast" either.
You wanna
try, bud?
Brefekst. Bakset.
Attaboy.
So, what are they
changing the name to?
According to this, they're
letting the publics decides
with an onlines polls.
Ooh, boy.
Not a
good idea.
Is there a worse idea?
Currently, the Letterkenny
Rough Riders is leading
by a hair.
(WAYNE GRUMBLING)
Is that your tummy grumbling?
Or is that you proper?
No, that'd be me proper.
What's the rumpus,
grumpus?
Don't you think that there's
already too many Rough Riders
in the area as it is?
You got
the Redford Rough Riders.
And a one.
You got
the Welno Rough Riders.
And a two.
And don't forget
the Greater Maddawascow
Rough Riders.
And a three. And that's
just off the tippy tops
of our heads.
Does get a bit confusing
during playoffs.
People like to root for
a Rough Rider.
Yeah, but if we're all
going to be Rough Riders,
why even have teams?
Why not just be
a big bunch of
Rough Riders?
Why don't you just
name the whole league
the Rough Riders?
Why even stop there?
Why don't we just go ahead
and name the whole
human race Rough Riders?
Like, you see
what I'm saying.
Yeah. Today,
we're all Rough Riders.
What exactly
is a Rough Rider?
I don't know. All's I'm saying
is that there's too many
of them. Don't you see?
KATY: So, what else
is in the running?
DAN: Ah, second place
is the Letterkenny
Muff Riders.
Yeah, I can get
behind Muff Riders.
Hmm. What else?
Third place goes to
the Letterkenny
Foot Fuckers.
Shouldn't that be
in first place,
on account that it
has foot in the title,
and it's a soccer team?
What else?
Well, fourth place is a tie
between the Big Nickelbacks
and the 69ers.
(CHUCKLING)
Both good choices.
KATY: I don't know
who to root for.
DAN: People likes
to root for a 69er.
(GRUMBLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I don't have a problem.
I don't have...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
I don't have a problem.
(SHOUTING)
Where is it?
It's right here.
First, the meth.
(WHINING)
(SHOUTING) I think
you do have a problem.
I don't have a problem!
You've never acted
like this before the...
This is all because of the...
(INAUDIBLE)
I've never seen it
get its claws in so deep.
(GRUNTS)
Give me the dark web.
Stewart!
I need the dark web.
You're killing him!
(MOANING)
It is killing you!
Give me the dark web.
Take the dark web.
The dark web is yours.
(COUGHS)
(GASPS)
Okay, so you keep
the meth over there, right?
We do. Let me show you.
I'm in.
Letterkenny, the hard right
is inside of you.
Fuck!
These stooges again.
I don't see a video request
from them.
How am I hearing their voice?
Must be some high‐tech
dark web shit.
Stu? Stu!
Appreciate the
Stooges reference.
Everyone knows Curly was
the original skinhead.
Plus Ron Asheton from
Iggy and the Stooges had a real
Third Reich obsession.
Good Christ! It smells like
somebody's been smoking
gate waves in here.
The Chiefs are changing
their name.
Who?
Your beloved junior soccer team.
BOTH: Who?
Ah! Nobody cares about
anything anymore.
What about the history?
The tradition?
What's a junior soccer team?
Some people
still care, all right?
You best believe.
And we are recruiting.
So, gentlemen, are you ready
to join the hard right?
Politics?
(SCOFFS)
We're anarchists.
(SCOFFS) Yeah. Who cares if the
soccer team changes its name?
The hard right, that's who.
Chiefs is a strong name.
I remember a time when
being called a chief
was a good thing.
People like to root for a chief.
(EXCLAIMS)
This used to be the heartland.
Now, it is just the
other heartland
of far‐left liberal cucks.
Did somebody get their
feelings hurt?
Did somebody sign a petition?
Uh, news flash,
you're all caving to PC culture.
You're just a bunch of
far‐left liberal fucking
pinko snowflakes.
Oh, we've been called worse.
But might as well just change
the name to Letterkenny Cucks.
Regional champs
of Cuckistan!
Okay.
This is what the failed
patriarchy looks like.
I'm so sick of you
beta male SJWs.
We're not SJWs.
I actually identify
as a wood nymph.
Super weird.
Be gone.
Oh, we'll be gone.
Just as soon as you betas
show us where the alphas are.
I'll see myself out.
I assume all of you
are following suit.
(SHOUTS)
He talks more than I do.
That was weird.
Ah, yes! Now we're talking.
The alphas. Real men.
No matriarchy in sight.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm Hard Right Jay,
and I represent the Hard Right,
a group with
far‐right ideologies
that rejects mainstream
conservatism and endeavors to
promote white nationalism.
Oh, white nationalism?
Good thing Gail,
the owner of the old bars
ain't here.
Oh, small town bar owner,
what is she, like a good
sixth‐generation Scottish woman?
No.
What are you's getting on
about over there?
Did you dinks
bring these dudes here?
What's the first
meal of the day,
Daryl?
Your mom.
Attaboy.
Breakfast!
Ah, that's it, right.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, yeah.
Run away like true socialistas.
At least your actions
are consistent with
your failed ideologies.
You edgelords
are a walking horde
of participation trophies.
Go back to giving out
hand jobs for free.
We're not socialistas.
I'm still with her.
We're anarchists.
And our hand jobs aren't free.
So...
Forg...
Forgive...
Forgive them. They don't
see the big picture. Yet.
What's the big picture?
You wanna see how deep
this rabbit hole really goes?
Or are you guys globalists?
What's that?
Ah!
I'll admit, I was anticipating
the low energy, country cuck
road show, but you're curious.
Color me glad.
It's time to wake up.
It's time for you to spit out
all of the toxic sludge
you've been spoon fed
by the Ian Hanomansings
and the Gloria Macarenkos
of the world.
We are a movement.
Bowel movement
by the looks of it.
Ah, hachi‐machi,
I like your fire.
We could use more women
in the movement.
We have next to none,
for reasons we can't
quite decode.
Pitter patter.
Yes, pitter patter.
All lives matter.
News flash,
the out of control PC police
are forcing your beloved
Letterkenny Chiefs
to change their name.
Yeah, we caught that.
Yeah, well, we're here
to protest that.
Our legions of brothers
will be joining me
at John Letterkenny Field
later.
And we want you,
the salt of the earth alphas,
the stewards of traditional
morals, traditional values,
the silent majority, to join us.
The fight against poor,
uneducated libtards
requires nothing short
of a massacre.
Now you're a bit
fucking dramatic, eh?
Why is keeping the name
of the Chiefs important to you?
ALL: It isn't.
Oh, oh, it's not. It isn't?
Well, not really,
in the long run.
Nor the short run, really.
Yeah, no need to get your
jimmies all out of joint.
Well, but you... You understand
why it's important
to fight the left? Yes?
I didn't know it was necessary,
much less important.
The point is
the government
is trying to keep you
and your humble agricultural
livelihoods thoroughly cucked.
It's time to wake up
and smell the chem trails.
It's time to stand up
for your God given right
to have kick‐ass names
for all your favorite teams,
and fuck anybody whose feelings
get hurt along the way.
Oh, is that what time it is?
Oh, you think I don't have
feelings? You think my feelings
don't get hurt?
My grandfather has
a pacemaker, right?
Every time I watch
the Indiana Pacers
play basketball,
it makes me think of Papi.
And his irregular heartbeat.
And it fucks me up, big time.
You see me complaining
to the Indiana Pacers
or anyone in the NBA?
Mmm, suck it up, buttercup.
So?
So what?
So join us.
Tell you what.
I'll fight you for it.
You and me.
Sorry, what?
What I'm saying is,
I'll fight you.
And if you win I'll come
to the field with you.
But if you lose,
we're not asking for
anything in return.
Ah, you SJWs are a lost cause.
I'm going to troll!
Letterkenny Chiefs!
We can do this, buddy.
We can establish order,
buddy. I know we can.
HARD RIGHT JAY:
Of course you can.
(INHALES) Ah.
Hockey, eh?
Fastest sport on Earth.
And the whitest too, arguably,
so bonus points there.
Okay, the Catholic school games
are on the other rink.
Uh, we just, uh,
thought you strapping alphas
might want to know
that the globalists
are trying to turn your
small town into a hive
of post‐castrati extremism.
What the fuck's castrati?
Uh, it's a pasta, bro.
Uh, it's pronounced
"pah‐sta," bro.
Is it?
Today, it's the Letterkenny
Chiefs. Tomorrow, it'll be
your beloved Shamrocks.
Well, you know, the Chiefs
is kinda not PC though, buddy.
We try to keep it, like,
kind of in touch there.
What if they decide to get
butt hurt over the Letterkenny
Shamrocks name next
and force you to change it
just because they don't know
how to control their... Their
fragile beta male emotions?
What then, huh?
You don't see a bunch
of Irish people protesting
here, do you?
No, you don't.
They're not,
(IMITATING IRISH ACCENT) "Argh,
please change your name!"
None of that's happening.
You wanna know why?
Because Irish people don't
fucking complain about
anything, all right?
Irish people know how to
take it like a champ, okay?
You take their potatoes away,
they don't say a fucking thing.
It's pronounced
"po‐tah‐to."
Is it?
It's called "manning up,"
gentlemen. You might want
to look into it.
What do you think, buddy?
I think this guy's
a goof, buddy.
Cool, buddy.
Yeah, but...
On that note, I'm not really
a fan of the Shamrocks name.
‐Really?
‐Yeah.
Me too, buddy. I mean,
if we're talking about
some kind of negative
stereotype attached
to that name, you know?
Right? It's like,
just because
my name is Reilly,
that doesn't necessarily mean
that I'm a drunken leprechaun.
Maybe we should change
the name, buddy.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
What's this about a name change?
If anybody should
change their names,
it should be us.
What the hell's a
Shamrockette anyway?
A leaf with tits?
Oh, this isn't your
matriarch, is it?
You can't just add "ette" to
the end of the men's team
and expect women to like it.
We should change our names
to something fierce and feminine
and powerful.
Like the Screaming Banshees.
That's good, Mary‐Anne.
Impressive creativity.
Couple of hens clucking away.
Especially for a girl who
had to start kindergarten
two years late
because she couldn't
grasp coloring.
I've plenty of good ideas,
Betty‐Anne.
Like convincing your dad
to get a vasectomy
so I wouldn't have to worry
about another you coming into
the world while I fucked him.
We were just starting
to get them under control.
You're screwing it up, bro.
You're getting them all
fired up again.
Bringing family into it now,
Mary‐Anne? I would never
stoop so low,
especially with the
recent passing of your mother,
who told me before she died
that my dad is your dad too.
You're fucking up
our progress, man.
Just get out of here.
It's only gonna get worse too.
Thanks a lot.
Ah, these Tumblrinas
have lost the plot anyway.
Letterkenny Chiefs!
(SIGHS)
Where the fuck is everybody?
This is supposed to be
a protest.
We need people to protest
and piss off and agitate.
Ay, ay, ay. Whose idea was this
stupid name change anyway?
TANIS: Ours.
S'up, Nazis?
Nazi? Hilarious.
Ain't nothing funny
about this, honky.
No, but Nazi, really? Nazi?
Would a Nazi ride
a Yamaha scooter?
A pansy Nazi? Sure.
Would a Nazi have
a Jew for a lawyer?
Could you refer me, asshole?
'Cause I'm gonna need one
in a minute.
Would a Nazi own a game‐worn
Tim Duncan jersey?
You sniff that shit before
bed at night, cupcake?
Would a Nazi's favorite snacks
include ramen, pad thai, or pho?
It's pronounced "pho‐e,"
"Pho‐e," dummy.
Oh.
All right, would a Nazi
get turned on by
interracial gang bang porn?
Who fucking doesn't?
All right, I think we all
need to chill out here.
We're getting
ahead of ourselves.
We are an inclusive movement.
I think you should join us.
Is that what we should do?
Yes.
Think about it, Sacagawea.
(STAMMERING) We share a lot.
We have a lot in common.
We both pride ourselves
on traditional values,
traditional morals.
We share a very
anti‐immigration stance.
You know, if you think about it,
we actually share a lot
of common ground.
(SCOFFS) Historically,
sharing ground hasn't
been your strong suit.
If you guys are here,
then who's jerking off
in your mom's basement?
Somewhere there's a
men's rights meeting
missing their door greeters.
Yeah, look. I get it.
You're frustrated.
It must be really exhausting
never paying taxes
your whole lives.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
All right.
Enough chin‐wagging.
Another hen cluck,
cluck, clucking away.
Hey, no one had a problem
with this. No one had a problem
until you's came to town.
That's it. The Hard Right,
coming to a town near you.
Yeah, we didn't come here
to counter‐protest.
Ain't nothing peaceful
gonna happen today.
Hey, we don't
practice violence.
We do.
We don't practice violence.
But we are prepared for it.
All right. Let's go then.
Let's do this.
You and what army?
That one.
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Golden pastures from here.
It's all I see.
Nary a chem trail in the sky.
Possibility of
a gentle Nor'Wester.
Oh, three to five clicks
by the look of her.
(ALL BANG TABLE)
Well, times to check in
on the Letterkenny Banner.
What's the latest?
(DAN GRUMBLING)
Was that your tummy grumbling
or was that you proper?
That was my tummy.
Good enough.
Well, it looks like they
canceled the online polls
to pick the new team name.
Oh, is that what they did?
Yeah, it seems like the
Muff Riders was
runnings away with it.
Foot Fuckers made
more sense by far.
I'm disappointed.
What are they
going with instead?
Rough Riders.
Of course they are.
Playoffs start next week.
Who they playing?
Runforough Rough Riders.
That's gonna be
a really good game.
DARYL: Must be hard kicking
the ball in the snow.
My money's on the Rough Riders.
You're crazy. I got the
Rough Riders by a mile.
Care to make it interesting?
DAN: I'll put ten bucks
on the Rough Riders.
Make it twenty.
I'll take that.
I'm in too.
DAN: See, Wayne, people love
to cheer for a rough rider.
The world's going to hell
in a hand basket, big brother.
In a what, Dary?
Brefekst bakset.
Attaboy.
(THEME SONG PLAYING)