You were sippin' suds
with your buds
the other day...
WAYNE: Hey, Dary,
real quick.
"Blank, lunch and dinner."
Breh‐fekst.
Oh, boy.
Can I be honest
with you guys
for a sec?
Oh, careful, Dary.
DAN: I'd suggest
everything you've said
up until now
has been a lie.
And you've said
lots of things.
Like, when someone
starts a sentence
with "Don't take this
the wrong way..."
Guess what?
I already did.
Yeah, the same thing
if people start a sentence
by saying, "You're gonna
hate me for saying this..."
Guess what? I already do.
Or, when people
start a sentence
by saying,
"You're not gonna
wanna hear this..."
Guess what?
I already don't.
No, it's just
an observation.
Well I'm curious as to know
why you thought
it required a preface.
Well, because I'm aware
of how it might sound.
Quit beatin'
around the bush, Dary.
Yeah, Dary, I don't remember
you been such an
around‐the‐bush beater.
Oh, fine, now
I'm not even gonna say it.
ALL: Say it.
The only thing
worse than saying,
"You're not gonna
wanna hear this,"
is when someone says
they have something to say,
and they don't say it.
You're digging
your heels in like
a 12‐year‐old girl.
When in doubt, spit's it out.
Okay, fine,
I'm gonna say it.
Okay, here goes.
You know micro‐brewing?
Like, craft beer?
Yeah.
I always thought
it was "craft beard,"
on account of the guys
who make it always have beards.
So, it was all that
for just this then, eh?
Thank you for inviting us
into the circle of trust, Dary.
I believe the
preferred term is,
"lumbersexuals."
Well, "craft beard" makes
a pocket‐load more sense.
DAN: You know, craft beards
doesn't really bother me.
But it's the clever wordplay
that goes into
the naming of it
that I finds hard to swallow.
Like, "So hoppy together,"
or "Barley breathing."
Now, why don't you
just call them what it is?
It's fuckin' beer.
"Beer and headlights."
Yeah. I'll contribute.
"Ale by comparison."
Stout and about.
Sounds actually pretty good,
"Stout and about."
Stout and about's
not bad at all, actually.
I'd drink some
stout and about.
I'm surprised
we're not drinking a
stout and about right now.
I think what you wanna do is
you wanna put
an animal in the name
'cause people love animals.
Like, "Cute Koala Cream,"
or "Happy Hamster Honey."
No, no. What you wanna do is
you wanna put
a berry in the name
'cause people love berries.
"Partridge Berry Pilsner,"
or "Alderberry Ale."
Pleasing to the ears
and the mouth.
No, Dary.
Dary, no.
No, Dan. Dan, no.
No, Katy. Katy, no.
What you're exposed to do,
is put something
cozy in the names
'cuz people like
being cozy, right?
Like "toque" or "mittens."
And then, if you really wanna
double down on it,
you put something
outdoorsy in the name
because people love
being outdoors.
Like, "lake,"
or "mountains."
So what it's really
gonna boil down to
is "Toque Lake Brew co,"
or "Mountain Mittens
Alpine Ale."
"Blanket Fire Light."
There you go, Dary.
The other ways
to go is to use
a clever,
but ironical statement.
Like, "I'm bitters."
See, I'd go suggestive.
Like, "Slip‐it‐in cider."
Katy.
What?
Let's get this gal
a fuckin' puppers.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Dary, have a shot?
I'd have a shot.
Dan, have a shot?
McMurray, have a shot?
(SLURRING)
I'll have a shot.
Tyson, have a shot?
JB, have a shot?
I'll have a shot.
Fuck, boys...
let's have a shot.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
G'day?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Et Jean‐Carl.
Et Jean‐Pierre.
Mes amis.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Are you's up at your chalet
in the Laurentians
having a Laurentide, or what?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
You know, you's got
some pretty choice gins
there in Q‐bec.
You ought to hammer
on one of those.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Can do.
What, like,
a buck‐and‐doe?
(ALL SPEAKING FRENCH)
Numbers?
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Well, I happen to be sitting
with the first team
all‐stars as we speak.
A bientot.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Who wants to go to
a buck‐and‐doe in Q‐bec?
Stag‐and‐doe,
I'll never say no.
A Jack‐and‐Jill,
always a thrill.
Drink‐and‐dance
till you shit your pants.
Love a good
turn‐and‐stomp.
Love a sip‐and‐spin.
What's a sip‐and‐spin?
Who the fuck are you?
A sip‐and‐spin...
Stag‐and‐doe...
Jacks‐and‐Jills...
Drink‐and‐dance...
Turn‐and‐stomp...
Or a buck‐and‐doe,
is a pre‐wedding party
thrown by the best man
and maid of honor
to raise money
for the bride
and groom's big day.
Oh, cool.
Get the fuck
out of here, dude.
In Winnipeg,
they call them "socials."
Can confirm.
You know, Winnipeg
has a very large
Ukranian population.
Not too many people
know that.
Hey, Jewish and Italian, too.
Not too many people know that.
Whose gulp and grind is it?
Remember Anik?
Oh... (GROANS)
Well, that's why
you gotta strike
while the iron's hot,
big shooter.
Another French gal
that got away.
I can't catch a break.
Who's drivin'?
Oh, fuck, not me,
I'm hammered.
Dary, you hammered?
Oh, I'm hammered.
Dan, you hammered?
McMurray, hammered?
(SLURRING) I'm hammered.
Tyson, you hammered?
I'm hammered.
JB, you hammered?
Fuck, boys,
we're hammered.
And how's that for ya?
Well, it's not
too bad for me,
but right about now
it's not smart, really.
Well, I'm not missin' out
on French boys.
Look, I'll drive,
but I'm not fittin'
all of youse in my truck.
Pete and Repeat.
Guys wanna go to
a buck and doe?
Oh, fuck, yeah.
I didn't even know
there's a
drink and dance tonight.
How we not know
about a swing‐and‐sway?
It's not here,
it's in Quebec.
I got no reason
to say no.
Let's slam some
rheumy skin.
Let's get our meat
smoked, boys.
Fire a little batch of
Celine Dijon.
Let's go.
Okay.
Good. You're drivin'.
(SLURRING INDISTINCTLY)
Hold your horses now,
hold your horses.
All right?
McMurray, how are you, now?
I'm a teensy bit
concerned, Wayne.
How's that?
What's the problem, McMurray?
Youse guys
got some French pals
who want us English dudes
to go to their party
in Quebec, right?
Right as Dan's jerk hand.
Right.
Except, youse gotta realize
that, in all likelihood,
your French pals
probably have
some French pals
who doesn't want
us English dudes
to go to their party
in Quebec. Right?
Left.
Right.
Quebec
damn near left Canada.
Separatism is alive and well
in Quebec right now,
mon freres.
Well, they just had
the referendum
damn near yesterday.
Mmm.
If, by "yesterday," you mean
a quarter of centuries ago,
then, yeah,
I can back that.
I said, "It feels like."
No, you didn't.
Did, too.
DARY: Did too.
DAN: Did not.
See? The French
is causing separation
separatism
right here, right now...
Settle down, McMurray.
Alls I'm sayin' is,
if they're not
happy to see me,
then I ain't pretending
to be happy to see them.
You heard it here first.
When a friend
asks for help,
you help him,
and that's all
there is to it.
Dary, you'll
have a scrap?
I'd have a scrap.
Dan, you have a scrap?
Tyson, have a scrap?
I'd have a scrap.
JB, you have a scrap?
I don't even know
what your fuckin' names are.
We'll have a scrap.
Fuck, boys.
Let's have a scrap.
I'll have a scrap, too.
My terms are non‐negotiable.
This is gonna be
a long drive. (CHUCKLES)
Wait up, sum'bitches.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoopsie Goldberg.
Hey, come over here
and shake my hand,
good buddy.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Oh, it's Stompin' Tom.
Is that fella Cock Quacin
still bummin' around?
How's Jim Cutey
and Micheal Bubbly?
About as good as Kim Mitchell,
there, Cocket Richard.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Yeah, long live the hip.
Here we go now.
So you guys got Celine Dion
all cued up in there?
What's the scoop?
We've got All‐anus Morissette.
(SLOW INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
Who are youse?
Excusez‐moi. Cute.
Jean‐Guy. (SPEAKS FRENCH)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Jean‐Pierre. (SPEAKS FRENCH)
Jean‐Carl. (SPEAKS FRENCH)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
That's Anik.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
McMurray.
Yeah, I guess
that makes me Jean McMurray.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
McMurray.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I've been called worse.
And Jean Daryl?
Jean Dan?
That's Jean
Squirrelly Dan.
I'm Jean C. Reilly.
I'm Jean Bons Jonsi.
Actually,
my middle name's John.
You know, French people
don't have middle names, right?
Anik.
Jean‐Claude.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Jean‐Lance.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
"Buck and doe."
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
He wouldn't let me invite
English family to the wedding.
So I said we have to have
a buck and doe
so they could be included.
Well, how very charitable
of you.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Wow, si, mon frere.
Youse go grab us a pint.
I'll get the tickets.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Very good old boy.
Oui.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
No girlfriend?
Pourquoi?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no. (LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Okay.
Mo.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Very hot.
Okay.
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
My niece. Beautiful.
But...
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Merci, monsieur...
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Jean Claude...
What is it?
Drink it.
(ALL CHEERING IN FRENCH)
I'm gonna have a piss.
Throw a few darts
first, maybe.
(MCMURRAY
MUMBLES INCOHERENTLY)
Jesus H!
That is fucking good.
Sortilege.
Maple‐syrup whiskey.
What a pairing!
Mm‐hmm.
That's good.
Isn't that good?
WAYNE: Isn't that good?
No, that's good.
Isn't that good?
That's good.
Fuck, boys.
That's good!
I'd have another round.
Next round's on us, boys.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Let's go!
So what do youse guys
do for work?
Jean‐Pierre works
at Jacutsue.
And what about you,
Jean‐Carl?
Uh, me? You know TD?
TD Bank?
Huh?
TD.
TD Bank.
Titty Bank?
Yeah. "TD."
Titty Bank.
TD Bank?
TD Bank.
Huh?
TD. TD Bank.
TD Bank.
Huh?
Come on.
TD Bank.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I wanna make sure
I'm hearing this right.
"Titty bank"?
Titty bank.
Oui. TD Bank.
(MOUTHING INAUDIBLY)
I'm not happy.
No?
But it's your
bock et biche.
I thought I was.
Planning the wedding
was a nightmare.
And then, I saw you.
Titty bank?
So like, a rip club...
That's what I thought.
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
TD Bank.
It is "TD Bank."
ALL: Oh...
ALL: Tee‐Dee Bank.
BOTH: Yeah. TD Bank.
(TABLE RUMBLES)
(RHYTHMIC RUMBLING)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
Jean‐Guy,
you have a scrap?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Jean‐Carl,
have a scrap?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Jean‐Pierre,
have a scrap?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
BOTH: I'll have a scrap.
Fuck, boys,
let's have a scrap.
So what was
all this talk
about a titty bank?
Is it close by or...
MapQuest it? Or...
Should we get a motel,
and stay the night, or...
McMurray.
Katy.
So you know?
You hear that?
(FAINT RUMBLING)
Oh. That's the most
aggressive two‐step
I think I ever heard.
That's no two‐step.
Huh?
It's showtime.
You must forgive me
for not washing my hands...
We gotta go!
Roger.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I told him
I couldn't
marry him.
Is that what you did?
I told him
I was not happy.
Good enough.
I told him I was in love
with an Englishman.
Good enough?
I told him I was
in love with you.
(CHUCKLES)
That's good stuff.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Do you like to dance?
I fuckin'
love to dance.
Let's go.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
(FRENCH MUSIC CONTINUES)