(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(FIRECRACKERS EXPLODING)
Hats off to Tanis,
boys.
It's certainly a great day
for Thunder Bay.
Yeah, Tanis has
outdones herself.
She sure did.
Say, where is Tanis?
Well, Tanis the
Tough gal.
Homewrecker.
Rocket.
Sniper.
Alpha female.
Temptress.
A bit rough around the edges.
Tried to lure you
in to the barn for a...
Round of the bases.
Homewrecking.
Slam.
Crush.
Roll in the hay.
Lay in the biblical sense.
Toe curl.
And the truth is
you kinda wanted to...
Pet heavily.
Wreck your home?
Rack up a kill.
Score a take down.
Have the best sex
of your life.
Fondle?
Become one.
But you didn't.
Because that's not what a...
Good 'ol boy.
Real man.
Straight shooter.
Team player
Seriously?
God‐fearing gentleman.
Stand up guy.
Does.
On the contrary, a...
Good 'ol boy.
Real man.
Straight shooter.
Team player.
Pussy.
God‐fearing gentleman.
Stands‐up guy.
Doesn't cheat.
So while you walked
towards the barn for what one
would assume was a...
Poke.
Terrible fucking idea.
Easy kill.
Quick mash.
Whatever you are into, baby.
Lustful encounter.
A lot of character
is undertaken.
You didn't.
You got in the truck,
drove over to Rosie's and...
Now, Rosie is a...
Real pretty gal.
So fucking cute.
Ten.
Damn.
Book reader.
Goddess.
Fine woman.
You can't be
with one woman
and have feelings
for another.
You are of the opinion
that cheaters are...
In the wrong.
Like, 95% in the wrong.
Bad?
Or...
Seduced.
Fair and square.
Antagonized.
Likely a good persons
who just mades a mistake.
And you shouldn't very well
go down that road.
So...
BOTH: Here's the thing...
BOTH: Okay, you go.
BOTH: No, you go.
Okay, I'll go.
I'm gonna move
to the city.
You are gonna move
to the city?
I'm gonna move
to the city.
What city?
Vancouver.
Well, you won't get
many random snowy summer nights
like this in Vancouver.
Nope.
So what's in Vancouver?
Pit bull rescue.
I'm tired of reading
about it every day.
I wanna help.
You're
a great fucking gal,
Rosie.
You're
a great fucking dude,
Wayne.
When will I see you?
When you see me.
Good enough.
And that's what
a get out of jail free card
looks like.
Boy, howdy.
Well, I should say.
Sick buddy.
Sick, bro.
Can we bang now?
Wondrous!
I likes Monopoly.
So, as for Tanis...
Get after it.
Sure.
Killzone?
Poundtown?
We should be
banging right now.
Tanis.
You could do much worse,
good buddy.
You and Tanis
are gonna give her
the old college try.
Good enough.
BOTH: Good enough.
Good stuff.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
DAN: Finally,
a non‐summer weddings.
I'm smilings.
Well, it seems
a little bit unfair
that at summer weddings
gals get to wear
a nice, breezy summer dress
and then we're stuck
being sweaty
and sticky in some
three‐piece wool suit.
I guess it can gets
quites pongies down there.
Yeah, it can get
a bit moist.
No.
Who do you think
is gonna moist the Stanley Cup,
this year, Katy?
I'm thinking Calgary.
I swear to fucking Christ
Oh, did you
never see
Moist Story?
Or Moist Story 2,
starring Tim Allen
and Tom Hanks?
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
I will fight you.
We don't fight
at weddings.
So, Dary,
are you gonna be
wearing your dad's suit?
Do falling timbers
make tambers?
Who the fuck are you?
Yes, Katy.
I got it
for a grade 13 semi‐formal
from the Letterkenny Op shop.
Loves the Op shops.
I'll take the Sally Ann.
You know what?
That suit is so dad
the last time you wore it,
it told me the Dire Straits
were the greatest band
of all time.
That suit is so dad
it ate all the lunch meat
on the way home
from the grocery store.
The suit is so dad
it owns a VHS copy
of The Hunt for Red October.
So, Dan,
are you gonna
cold rock a kilt?
Like my Grandpas
and his grandpas
before him.
A little class,
a little sass
and a lot of ass
all in one
tartans garments.
Wayne,
I assume you'll be wearing one
of only two suits that you own.
Two will do you.
One for weddings
and one for funerals.
A good suit lasts you
the rest of your life
if you take care of it.
What would you wear
for a court appearance?
I've never been arrested.
What would you wear
to a job interviews?
I've only ever had one job.
KATY: What would you wear
to a bar mitzvah?
Not Jewish.
Bat mitzvahs?
Still not Jewish.
Graham's from the city.
So there's gonna be
a lot of citiots
at this thing.
(GROANS)
I fucking hate citiots.
They're always going on
about how we're saying,
"fucking mud in our
fucking hammies".
Fucking riding
our sleds down to
a fucking pit party, bud.
Giving her tits.
I was climbing the ladder
up the hay mound
behind your brother and ew!
Ripped a fart
that sounded like
a creaky door opening
inside a hot air balloon, but...
We do not fight
at weddings.
No, but we can get laid
if we're keen to.
Sexy just wafts around
at weddings.
Plenty of opportunities
for people looking
to do some yessing.
A little bit
of wedding spreading.
A little bit of matrimonies
and hide the balonies.
Oh, sure,
maybe some exchanging of rings
and rubbing of things.
KATY: Clear eyes.
Full Windsors.
ALL: Can't lose.
Clean up well,
Cowboy.
Well, a good suit
will last the rest of your life
if you take care of it.
And me?
Well, I wouldn't kick you
out of bed for eating
fucking crackers, Tanis.
Top shelf ceremony,
boys.
Short, sweet
and not too much God.
I'm told God
doesn't have much time
for gays these days, so...
Par for the course,
I guess.
Real prouds of Dax and Ronsford
jumps in the brooms like that.
Good guys.
Good grooms.
I wonder what
that must be like.
What?
Getting hitched?
No, being into dudes.
I've got so many questions.
Yeah,
and I wanna hear
exactly zero of them.
It's like,
what if you
are attracted
to somebody
with the same name as you?
Is it like,
"How fun"?
Or is it fucking weird?
It'd be fucking weird.
Quite likely.
That's never happened to me.
Guess the closest I ever came
to it was almost doing it
with a gal named Sheryl.
Yeah, I suppose
it'd kindsa be
like the time
I almost hooked up
with a gal who had
the same names as my Grandmas.
That would be
fucking off‐putting.
It was.
It was distracting
at inappropriate times...
With...
Ruth.
I wish there was
a goddamn way
I could do it with a Katy.
Ew!
Or a Kate
or a Caitlin.
I guess Katherine
would even be
walking the line.
There's no way
I could do it
with a Wayne.
Ew!
Unless it was Gretzky
or Rostad.
Or Newton.
(CHEERING)
I'd bow to the great ones.
I'd bend right over.
I'd like Gretzky
in my office
behind the net.
I'd be a jar of curry
in a fucking hurry just
feeding him all night long.
I promised Mess
I wouldn't do this.
I just promised
to mess.
I'd let Gretzk
leave my ass
seriously McSorely
I'd let that lady
Bing lady bang me.
That's 69 with 99
into overtime.
I'd just straight up
let him 99 me.
Howdy who.
Ah, what's a 99?
It's just fucking
while spooning.
(CHUCKLES)
All right, boys.
Show me
what you can do
with a cock.
(ALL GASP)
Hail!
ALL: Hey‐ho.
Oh, good day, lads.
Did you ride
your fucking sleds here?
Oh, are you fucking
matting her?
Is she
a charity ride,
like, "Holy Fuck"?
Just about clear putting it
in the fucking rhubarb.
Yous just gonna stand there
rubbing your peckers or what?
Oh, she's
fucking tits,
eh?
D'you give her beans, bud?
D'you give her boots, bud?
Do you give her
fucking torque?
MAN: Do you wanna get
fucking smoke?
Or are you
taking her easy?
If she's easy,
take her twice, bud.
We'll call you
toonie two times.
Let's do her manure.
Isn't this the part
where you...
We don't fight at weddings.
Those citiots
can fucking tie
their dicks in a knot.
They can go
piss up a rope.
Gretzky, Rostad
and Newton
for Katy, eh?
I'm surprised
Lil Wayne
didn't make the cut.
What?
Great dress, Bonnie.
Thanks.
Op Shop.
You look like
the girl who punched
my V ticket.
What's your nationality?
You ever seen
the back seat
of a BMW X3?
You should be honored.
My buddy here
only fucks tens.
Only tens.
Right in the X.
Seriously,
come outside.
I'll show you the 3.
It's actually
the exact same
as the 5.
(WHISPERS) X5.
(WHISPERS) BMW.
Just way better on gas.
Living the Beem.
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Stewart, I know
you are the world's
foremost fire selector,
but this is a wedding
and I promised the grooms
we'd play songs like
Brown Eyed Girl
and Shout
and Lean on Me,
Ain't No Mountain High Enough
and Mambo No. 5
Yous guys
got the Chicken Dance
ready to play yet?
I fucking love that song,
I'll tell you.
I put it on in the barn
for the cluckers
when them pecker‐faced bastards
ain't dropping eggs,
I just love it.
Are you
being facetious?
Huh?
Can your vestigial minds
even comprehend the derogatory
nature of your requests?
Or maybe
you could compromise?
Do something cool
like beat juggle
the Chicken Dance?
Here, take...
Enough!
Deejaying is an art form.
A medium in which
the most prolific audio auteurs
of our time can speak through.
A deep connection
of the soul of yourself
and the gyrating asses
of the great unwashed
who eagerly thirst
for your deafening
compositions.
I like gyrating asses
but I'm pretty sure
it ain't art there, bud.
Yeah, wouldn't you have to
have written the songs yourself
for it to be art?
I'm sorry,
composed?
I think the word
is produced.
Right, or at least
didn't download off the Internet
so you could profit off them.
Yeah, you are
more like an art dealer
than an artiste.
Or like
an art gallery curator.
Selling stolen paintings.
That you printed
off the Internet.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Whoa!
If you do not
fall back,
and fasten that lip.
Your other,
thinner lip.
I'll turn this elegant, soigne
ceremony of the coming together
of two bonded souls
into a straight up blood rain.
Hey!
Over here.
Chicken Dance.
Get it?
(MUTTERING)
Just wanna go
(CLUCKING)
Good game
you fucking beauties.
Way to tape your
sticks together, boys.
You two make
a hot pairing.
Five minute major
and a lifetime misconduct
for butt ending.
You boys
enjoying yourselves?
Acting single.
Seeing double.
Drinking triples.
Daxy, I gotta say,
solid work
on the big city
slam prospects.
Solid big city
slam scouting, Daxy.
Boys, a little, uh,
players only here.
You are not
pulling tonight.
BOTH: Yes, we are.
These are
modern city gals.
None of them
have any interest
in hockey player types.
Boys, big muscles haven't
been popular with the ladies
since Jersey Shore.
The only way to get
any attention from a
cosmopolitan, college gal type
is to get in touch
with your inner twink.
You need to be less
power forward
and more power bottom.
We'll get
our wedding stylist
to help them out.
So we need to...
Spruce up our look?
No.
You gotta bruce
up your look.
So Professor Tricia says
that Letterkenny has developed
into quite the homosexual scene
and we can rightly expects
a Pride parades next springs.
Never been to
a Pride parade.
What's it like?
It's like a Santa Claus parade.
Except instead
of handing out candy,
they hand out condoms.
I should probably start
thinking about a name
right now.
Great Day for gay.
A Hard Gay's Night.
Eyes Pride Shut.
Pride Green Tomatoes.
Pride of Chucky.
Independence Gay.
Ferris Bueller
Gets Off.
Star Wars
Rogue One.
The Princess Pride.
Pride of Frankenstein.
Pride and Go Seeks.
Carlito's Gay.
Night of the Giving Head.
Lay Anything.
Final Mantasy.
Third Cock from the Sun.
How fella Got
His Groove Pack.
The Gay the Earth
Stood Still.
Eat, Gay, Love.
Dr. Strangelove
or how I learned
to stop wearing,
"Love the Bum".
Bonnie and Pride.
ALL: Oh, Bonnie McMurray.
You boys tried
the catering yet?
I am chomping at the bit
to get one of those cupcakes.
Nots to be impolite,
Dary
but it's actually
champing at the bits.
Oh, you got those
pits ready for your
fucking ponies?
How many ponies you got
under your hood? You got
a frigging hemmy under there?
How many
CCs is your sled?
Do you fucking pin her
when you get pickled there, bud?
Oh, I really fucking gave it
to her last night.
Working hard
or hardly working?
What happened
to the part where...
We don't fight at weddings.
I gotta piss.
KATY: I'll come with you.
BONNIE: Yeah, same.
Okay, let's go. (CLEARS THROAT)
My cock he lives now.
(CHUCKLES)
Redux.
What's up,
ladies?
What is
your nationality?
Grow up
around here?
Have any tattoos?
I got a Celtic symbol
on my calf.
I got a Nike swoosh
right above my heart.
I got you a drink.
I swear it's not
a roofie.
Yes, it is.
Of course, it is.
Hey, that's
a real nice dress.
Look a lot nicer
on my hotel room floor.
You ever seen
the front seat
of a Honda del Sol?
I'll have a roll
in your hay any day.
We don't fight
at weddings.
I got a Harman Kardon
system in the 3.
X3.
BM motherfucking W,
baby.
It's actually
way better than Bose.
Dickskin?
Dickens.
Fellas, a list
of my requests.
To be played back two,
back two, three, four,
well I have five songs...
No requests.
How dare thou
come into
my private roost
of penetrating beats
with an audacious act
of social and musical treason.
Every single one of these
is a Brooks and Dunn song.
Starting with
the Boot Scootin' Boogie.
I didn't realize
they had other songs.
Of all the boogies,
the Boot Scootin'
is the last one I would
and will ever torture
myself or others with.
I'll give you
a Boot Scootin'.
What about
Blame It on the Boogie
by the Jackson 5?
Boogie, Oogie, Oogie,
A taste of honey.
Boot Scootin'.
Boogie Wonderland,
by Earth Wind & Fire
Elton John's
Street Boogie.
This wedding needs a boogie
and it's gonna be Boot Scootin'.
Born to Boogie,
T Rex?
Boogie Woogie Wu,
Insane Clown Posse.
Zip Gun Boogie,
T Rex again.
Take the damn boogie
and make it
a Boot Scootin'.
I'm Your Boogie Man,
KC and the Sunshine band.
I'm Your Boogieman,
White Zombie.
I hoped it wouldn't come
to blows over a boogie.
But I'll damn well
go to blows.
For the Boot Scootin' Boogie.
Not happening,
Dickskin.
Dickens!
I got it.
I got the Chicken Dance.
Went home and got it
out of the cassette player
in the tractor.
You play it now or later.
Either way, you'll play it.
Or you'll die.
What's with
the super sad
glassware, boys?
What's with your hair?
Oh, just got some
big city prospects.
Don't wanna risk
putting a big goose egg
up on the board.
Don't wanna fan
on a yonny cage, buddy.
So, we bruced up
our looks.
What does that mean?
Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it, yeah.
How's that
going for ya?
Uh, good.
We got bites.
Yeah.
Well,
we got like, a...
A bite.
They were 50 though.
I took down
an older lady once.
It was kinda fun.
Kinda weird.
Why?
Well,
after she made a pizza.
Sick, buddy.
She ordered a pizza.
No, made a pizza.
From scratch, buddy.
I had to sit
and talk
while she made
a pizza.
You two
look like dandies.
You look
like pansies.
You know,
the landscape
might be changing
but manly men
never go out of style.
Hello, ladies.
Yeuch, I can't drink
this shit anymore.
What am I
a ballerina trying
to get skinny?
I'm gonna get
some rye, babe.
Cheers.
Katy got hit on
by a top hat guy.
A top hat.
A guy in a top hat.
I'd rather take down
a city than a guy
in a top hat.
Oh, I don't know,
Ms. Katys.
Some men looks
quite statelys
in a top hat.
Scrooge McDuck
comes to mind.
Mr. Peanut.
Slash.
The guy from T Rex.
Abe Lincoln.
Uncle Pennybags
from Monopoly.
Willy Wonka's.
The Cat in the Hat.
Guy from T Rex again.
Oh, hey there,
buds.
Is she a manual?
Or are you driving
a bitch stick?
You like bud lite?
You like butt holes
around here.
Oh, did you get
your pecker stuck
in a bottle of brew?
Where's your sweety bud?
Did she leave you
to your John
and your John Deere?
Where's your John queer, bud?
I was brought up on
Looney Tunes and only dancing
when nobody's around.
Learned the heck
out of it that way, Dan.
I am fucking irritated.
We don't fight
at weddings.
Right.
We don't fight
at weddings.
Ten four?
Over and out.
Hello, ladies.
Ladies.
Can we interest you
in a shot of sourpuss?
Perhaps a half glass
of white zinfandel?
Have you looked at
any interesting furniture
lately?
I admire his eye
for interior design.
What are you two
going on about?
You are really
missing the mark.
You know,
metrosexuality
went out of style
with the Von Dutch
and Chingy.
We are into men.
Classic men, athletic types.
You don't look like
you can fix my car.
You don't look
like you can fix
a sliding screen door.
What?
Wha... What?
We're ...
We're hockey players.
We're the snipe,
celly boys.
Dirty fucking
dangles boys.
What are you guys
going on about now?
Now you are
just being posers.
It's pretty pathetic.
Even if you are hockey players,
we are not puck bunnies.
Or lacrosse‐titutes.
I don't even drink...
I drink beer. (GROANS)
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Where are you guys
staying tonight?
There's only motel
in this shit hole,
so that one.
I've never ridden
in a BMW X3 before.
What about a BMW X3
with a luxury leather package?
She just said
she'd never ridden
in one, idiot.
Take me home.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The song
for the first dance...
Chosen by...
The grooms.
(GUESTS APPLAUDING)
I can't wait
to take sauce
from you
and slot from now
until the horn blows
at the end
of quadruple overtime.
Playoff rules,
nice.
There was
always an open bet.
I'll take the tender
tonight.
A six man, you know
what I am talking about.
As long as you can bury.
Oh, we will find a hole.
You can't slip one past me.
Let's steer this back.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ Sucking on my titties
♪ Like you wanted me
♪ Calling me all the time
Like Blondie
♪ Check out my chrissy behind
♪ It's fine all of the time
♪ Like sex on the beaches
♪ What else is in the teaches
Of peaches?
♪ Huh? What?
♪ Sucking on my titties
Like you wanted me
♪ Calling me
All the time like Blondie
♪ Check out my chrissy behind
♪ It's fine all of the time
♪ What else is in the teaches
of peaches?
♪ Like sex on the beaches
♪ Huh? What?
♪ Huh, right
♪ What?
♪ Huh? What?
♪ Right
♪ Fuck the pain away
♪ Huh? What?
♪ Right
♪ What else in the teaches
of peaches?
♪ Like sex on the beaches
♪ What?
♪ Right
♪ SIS, IUD
♪ Stay in school
♪ 'Cause it's the best
♪ IUD, SIS
♪ Stay in school
♪ 'Cause it's the best
♪ IUD, SIS
♪ Stay in school
♪ 'Cause it's the best
♪ IUD, SIS
♪ Stay in school
♪ 'Cause it's the best
♪ Sucking on my titties
Like you wanted me
♪ Calling me
All the time like Blondie
♪ Check out my chrissy behind
Yous looking for trouble?
So what if we are?
We don't fight
at weddings.
Wouldn't dream of it, bud.
♪ Fuck the pain away
♪ Huh? What?
♪ Right. Uhh
♪ What else is in the teaches
of peaches?
♪ Like sex on the beaches
♪ What? Right. Uhh
♪ Fuck the pain away
♪ Fuck the pain away ♪